{"id": "search_qa_0", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm tired of Cuisinart and grey pans, got anything else? Give me a product ID for a different brand and color.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Cuisinart\" AND NOT color = \"grey\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Cuisinart\" AND NOT color = \"grey\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Cuisinart' AND color <> 'grey' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_0", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set appropriately sized for preparing meals for a large family?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Pan Set is designed primarily for creating individual or two-person servings, making it less suitable for the needs of preparing larger family meals where more servings are required.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_1", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm not messing around with cheap brands. Give me a pan from Copper Chef or Lodge that can handle temperatures above 600F.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Lodge\") AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Lodge\") AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Copper Chef', 'Lodge') AND oven_safe_temperature > 600;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_1", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the stainless steel pan resistant to warping when exposed to high heat?", "long_answer": "The stainless steel pan is generally resistant to warping under high heat, as indicated by the majority of reviews which do not mention warping issues, especially under normal broiling conditions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_2", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is there a warranty included with the purchase of the T-fal Handy Pot?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Handy Pot is accompanied by a Lifetime Limited Warranty which guarantees the pot's quality and performance over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_2", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I ain't paying more than 10 dollars and I only want either a black or green one. Give me the pan that matches these specifics.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND color IN (\"black\", \"green\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND color IN (\"black\", \"green\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND (color = 'black' OR color = 'green');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_3", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "What is the depth measurement of the pan?", "long_answer": "The pan has a depth of 1.5 inches, which is considered suitable for various cooking processes such as broiling and roasting.", "short_answer": "1.5 inches", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_4", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the Cuisinart Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan has an aluminum encapsulated base, which makes it induction-ready and thus compatible with induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_5", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for cooking a steak to medium-rare doneness?", "long_answer": "The Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet can indeed be used to cook steaks to medium-rare or to any other level of doneness you prefer.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_6", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is the non-stick surface of this ceramic-coated pan resistant to damage from acidic foods when used according to the manufacturer's instructions?", "long_answer": "The ceramic-coated pan features a non-stick surface that is specifically designed to be durable against the effects of acidic foods, provided that it is utilized in accordance with the manufacturer's guidelines.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_7", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Can the T-fal A8572494 saucepan be used for cooking on high heat?", "long_answer": "The T-fal A8572494 saucepan should not be used for high-heat cooking as it may compromise the non-stick surface. It is designed to cook evenly and efficiently at medium heat, which is adequate for most cooking tasks without necessitating high temperatures.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_3", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I gotta roast some veggies and need a pan that can stomach a solid 400F in the oven. Oh, and it's gotta be green, don't ask. Got anything like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND color = \"green\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND color = \"green\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND color = 'green';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_0", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I am in search of eco-friendly cookware. Do these pans align with that objective?", "long_answer": "Certainly, purchasing these pans aligns with your aim for sustainable cookware. Made from aluminum, these pans are highly recyclable and contribute significantly to environmental conservation, in harmony with sustainable principles.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's environmental considerations are not recommended for those who prefer to minimize their environmental footprint through recyclable and sustainable cookware options, highlighting aluminum's advantage as it can be recycled effectively.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_1", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is it safe to prepare all kinds of food in this pan without concern for flavor changes?", "long_answer": "When you're thinking about using a cast iron pan, keep in mind that it's not suitable for all kinds of food. Cooking acidic dishes such as tomato sauce, for instance, can erode the seasoning of the pan and might lead to the food having a metallic flavor. Hence, it's best to steer clear of extensive cooking of acidic items in cast iron cookware.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being made from cast iron cannot be used for acidic foods like tomato sauce for extended periods, as the acid can strip the seasoning and cause the food to take on a metallic taste.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "cast iron", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_2", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is this pan durable enough to handle frequent use for preparing various cuisines?", "long_answer": "For the majority of culinary styles, the pan ought to be durable. Nonetheless, should your cooking regularly feature acidic or alkaline components, it might be wise to opt for a treated or anodized pan to prevent problems with metallic flavor transfer and discoloration that could affect the pan's longevity with consistent exposure to these ingredients.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with reactivity to acidic and alkaline foods feature a potential for metallic taste transfer and discoloration, rendering them less suitable for long-term cooking of tomato sauces or citrus-based dishes unless they're treated or anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_8", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the pan suitable for both baking and broiling?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be versatile, making it suitable for use in various cooking techniques, including both baking and broiling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_9", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "What is the maximum oven-safe temperature for the Copper Chef pan?", "long_answer": "The Copper Chef pan is designed to be oven-safe and can withstand temperatures up to 850 degrees Fahrenheit, permitting a range of cooking techniques from stovetop searing to oven baking.", "short_answer": "850°F", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_4", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I got a soft spot for ZWILLING J.A. Henckels and Norpro, but I can't drop more than 30 dollars. What's the cheapest pan you have from either of those brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"Norpro\") AND price < 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"Norpro\") AND price < 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('ZWILLING J.A. Henckels', 'Norpro')\nAND price <= 30 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_3", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I seek an easy-care option for kitchenware. Would this pan be a suitable selection for my needs?", "long_answer": "Should low maintenance be a priority for you, it may be worthwhile to explore alternative options. This pan is not dishwasher-safe, necessitating additional upkeep including hand washing and regular re-seasoning to maintain its optimal performance over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" fail to meet the requirements for easy maintenance and may involve extra steps like re-seasoning or careful hand-polishing to uphold their performance and appearance standards.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_10", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is there a manufacturer warranty included with these pans?", "long_answer": "These pans usually include a limited manufacturer warranty. However, to obtain precise details regarding the warranty, you should contact Ozeri customer service.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_5", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I ain't paying more than 10 bucks for a pan, and it sure as hell ain't gonna be from Copper Chef. So, what's the largest pan you can offer for that price?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand != 'Copper Chef' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_4", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is this pan suitable for acidic sauces, given that it's not dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The design of the pan facilitates hand washing and offers advantages like effective heat retention, suitable for traditional cooking techniques. However, you should be aware of its potential reactivity with acidic ingredients. Depending on its material, taking additional precautions when cooking acidic dishes may be necessary to preserve the lifespan of the pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are ideally used for traditional or specialized cooking methods that take advantage of their unique material properties, such as the heat retention of cast iron.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_11", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is the Anolon saucepan suitable for making candy that requires precise temperature control?", "long_answer": "The Anolon saucepan is well-regarded for candy making due to its ability to distribute heat evenly and its nonstick surface. These features make it particularly useful for recipes where precise temperature management is crucial.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_12", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "What is the material composition of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is manufactured using stainless steel, which provides the product with robustness and longevity.", "short_answer": "stainless steel", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_13", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "What type of warranty is included with the purchase of these pans?", "long_answer": "These pans include a limited lifetime warranty, reflecting the manufacturer's assurance in their product's durability and overall quality.", "short_answer": "limited lifetime warranty", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_6", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm all about the big guns when it comes to pans and I dig Anolon and Ozeri brands. Hook me up with the largest one they got that's over 10 inches.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Ozeri\") AND size > 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Ozeri\") AND size > 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Anolon', 'Ozeri') AND size > 10 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_7", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm in the market for a large pan, needs to be blue or silver, anything over 12 inches will do. But it's got to handle some heat, what's the highest oven-safe temperature pan you got in those colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"silver\") AND size > 12 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"silver\") AND size > 12 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"silver\") AND size > 12 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND color IN ('blue', 'silver') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_8", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm looking for a big pan, preferable in grey or black color, but I don't want it if it's from Tramontina. What's the biggest one you got that matches what I'm looking for?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") AND NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") AND NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") AND NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'black')\nAND brand NOT LIKE 'Tramontina'\nORDER BY size DESC\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_14", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Does the pan's actual weight correspond to the listed weight of 2.6 pounds in the description?", "long_answer": "The pan's weight is indeed listed as 2.6 pounds in the product description, and this weight has been validated by the product's official specifications, confirming its accuracy.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_5", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm in search of kitchenware that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "long_answer": "Should low maintenance be a priority for you, it may be prudent to explore alternative choices. This pan lacks a dishwasher-safe attribute, necessitating additional attention, including manual cleaning and regular re-seasoning, to maintain its optimal functionality over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" fail to meet the requirements for easy maintenance and may involve extra steps like re-seasoning or careful hand-polishing to uphold their performance and appearance standards.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_6", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is this pan designed to be presentable on a table setting?", "long_answer": "This saucepan is designed to optimize the cooking process, yet it is not intended for table presentation. For an attractive table arrangement, consider exploring pans or dishes specifically created to enhance serving aesthetics.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan are not recommended for serving food directly due to their construction, as they are primarily designed for cooking rather than table presentation.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_15", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Do users report any balance or weight distribution problems when handling these pans?", "long_answer": "A number of customers have reported that the pans can be somewhat heavy which may impact their balance and weight distribution, although experiences with this may differ among individuals.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_7", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is it possible to utilize this pan for cooking on the stovetop as well as presenting food at the dining table?", "long_answer": "As a saucepan, its design is centered around cooking, favoring heat distribution and cooking efficiency over table presentation. Therefore, serving food directly from it is not advisable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan are not recommended for serving food directly due to their construction, as they are primarily designed for cooking rather than table presentation.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_16", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does the pan become non-stick after proper seasoning and use over time?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to attain non-stick qualities once it is seasoned correctly, and these non-stick properties are expected to enhance with continued use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_17", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does the frying pan become non-stick following seasoning?", "long_answer": "Proper seasoning can result in the frying pan becoming non-stick, as evidenced by customer experiences. Some customers might need to season the pan multiple times to obtain the optimal non-stick performance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_18", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is the Tramontina pan compatible with gas cooktops and does it provide even heat distribution when used on them?", "long_answer": "The Tramontina pan is designed to work with gas cooktops and is reported by numerous users to perform excellently, achieving even heat distribution during use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_19", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "What material is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set features a construction of stainless steel, which provides the product with strength and enhances its durability for long-term use.", "short_answer": "stainless steel", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_20", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Are there any common customer complaints about the pan's durability?", "long_answer": "The general consensus among customers is that the pan is sturdy and durable, with a significant number of users reporting that it lasts for many years without issues.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_9", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm a big fan of Lodge, what's the cheapest pan they have in your store?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Lodge\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Lodge\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Lodge\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Lodge' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_10", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm looking to add a pop of color to my kitchen. Do you have any blue pans in your product line?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_8", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Can this pan withstand frequent washing if I regularly run my kitchenware through the dishwasher?", "long_answer": "Certainly. This pan is designed to withstand frequent usage. It's crafted to be resilient against extreme heat and the harsh chemicals found in dishwasher detergents, ensuring it remains resistant to warping, rusting, or deterioration, even when subjected to daily cycles in the dishwasher.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute feature resistance to both the high temperatures and strong chemicals typical in dishwashers, which ensures they do not warp, rust, or degrade quickly when exposed to such conditions regularly.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_9", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this pan, or is it better to refrain from doing so?", "long_answer": "It is recommended to refrain from using metal utensils on this pan, as it is constructed from copper and is susceptible to scratches. To maintain the integrity of your pan's surface, it is preferable to use utensils crafted from materials such as wood, silicone, or plastic.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with copper material fail to meet the requirements for carefree handling as they are susceptible to developing a patina and scratches, necessitating careful usage and upkeep.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "copper", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_21", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Can the tempered-glass lid be used with different sizes and brands of cookware?", "long_answer": "The tempered-glass cover is indeed versatile and can be utilized with other cookware, provided that the sizes are compatible and match the lid.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_22", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Can the heavy-gauge, hard-anodized aluminum saucepan be used on a glass top range?", "long_answer": "The saucepan, constructed with heavy-gauge, hard-anodized aluminum and having an uncoated bottom, is indeed suitable for use on a glass top range. This material composition ensures that the saucepan can safely be used on such stove tops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_23", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Can the pan safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit in the oven?", "long_answer": "The pan is confirmed to be oven safe and can safely withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit (232 degrees Celsius). However, it should not be used under the broiler as it is not designed to handle the direct intense heat of that setting.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_10", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is it acceptable to clean this pan using only soap and water, or does it have specific cleaning instructions?", "long_answer": "Stainless steel pans require more than just soap and water for cleaning, as they can become discolored over time. Maintaining their appearance will necessitate regular polishing in addition to your standard cleaning regimen, an important factor if you prefer to minimize maintenance tasks.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with stainless steel material are not suitable for those seeking the easiest maintenance, as they can develop discoloration and require regular polishing to keep their appearance pristine.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "stainless steel", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_24", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan capable of withstanding high-heat cooking methods such as rolling boils and liquid reductions?", "long_answer": "Yes, the Cuisinart saucepan is particularly designed to handle high-heat cooking applications, including but not limited to rolling boils and the reduction of liquids, both of which require the pan to be subjected to high temperatures.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_11", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm a bit of a home chef, and I need a pan that can withstand the heat. What's the top pan you have from either Presto or Tramontina that can handle over 400F in the oven?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Tramontina\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Tramontina\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (brand = 'Presto' OR brand = 'Tramontina') AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC, price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_11", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm in search of sustainable cookware options. Would purchasing these pans align with that objective?", "long_answer": "Indeed, purchasing these pans would align with your objective of using sustainable cookware. The aluminum composition of the pans is notable for its recyclability and plays a significant role in efforts to conserve the environment, thereby adhering to sustainable practices.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's environmental considerations are not recommended for those who prefer to minimize their environmental footprint through recyclable and sustainable cookware options, highlighting aluminum's advantage as it can be recycled effectively.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_12", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I do a lot of high-heat cooking, so I need a pan that can handle at least 400F and is larger than the average size. What's the best option you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_25", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Can using cooking spray damage non-stick cookware surfaces?", "long_answer": "Employing cooking spray is advised against since it may sometimes lead to the deterioration of non-stick surfaces. Instead, it is suggested to use alternatives like a small amount of oil or butter for cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_26", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Does the pan's exterior offer the same durability and ease of cleaning as the interior?", "long_answer": "The exterior of the pan is constructed to be durable; however, it may display signs of wear and discoloration over time, particularly after heavy usage and consistent exposure to high temperatures.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_27", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the T-fal pan compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The T-fal pan is specifically designed to work with various cooking methods, and this includes being fully compatible with induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_12", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Can this pan be safely used for recipes that call for broiling?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the pan is also safe for use in broiling. The stainless steel lid can withstand the high temperatures of a broiler without suffering damage. Nonetheless, ensure that if the pan handle is not constructed of stainless steel, it too can withstand the broiler's extreme heat.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a stainless steel lid are ideally used for oven recipes due to their high heat tolerance, provided that the handle is also oven-safe if it is not made from stainless steel.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "stainless steel lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_13", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I need a new pan, but I'm a loyal Presto fan and my wallet can't handle anything north of 20 dollars. You got anything that ain't gonna break the bank?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Presto\" AND price < 20 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Presto\" AND price < 20 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Presto' AND price <= 20;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_14", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Listen, I've had enough of Norpro. Get me the most affordable pan from another brand that can handle at least 450 degrees in the oven.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Norpro\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Norpro\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Norpro\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Norpro' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_28", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is the pan suitable for baking submarine sandwich loaves?", "long_answer": "Customers report success with the pan when baking a variety of bread types, which includes the making of submarine sandwich loaves, indicating its versatility in bread-making.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_29", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Can the Stone Earth Frying Pan's non-stick coating withstand the use of acidic ingredients such as tomato sauce without damage?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Frying Pan is designed with a non-stick coating that enables it to handle the cooking of acidic foods, including tomato sauce, without sustaining damage to the surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_30", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "What is the duration and type of warranty provided with the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan?", "long_answer": "The USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan is accompanied by a warranty that is limited in nature and extends for the lifetime of the product.", "short_answer": "limited lifetime warranty", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_31", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is this T-fal pan dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The T-fal pan is designed to be dishwasher safe, enabling easy cleaning. Despite this, it is advisable to hand wash the pan in order to extend the durability of the nonstick coating, as frequent dishwasher use could potentially reduce its lifespan and effectiveness.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_32", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "What type of protection is included with the pans for storage?", "long_answer": "The pans come with scratch protectors, which are foam pads that serve to protect the non-stick coating from scratches during storage.", "short_answer": "scratch protectors", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_15", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that's bigger than 8 inches, doesn't cost more than 20 dollars, and can handle some heat in the oven. Give me your best option.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND size > 8 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND size > 8 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND size > 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND price <= 20 AND oven_safe_temperature > 350 ORDER BY price ASC, oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_16", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm trying to save some money and can’t afford anything over 10 dollars. What's the cheapest pan you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_33", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does the non-stick coating on this pan maintain its durability over time with proper use?", "long_answer": "The non-stick coating tends to remain durable when the pan is used according to the manufacturer's instructions. Notwithstanding, some users have noted that the coating becomes less effective when the pan is not maintained properly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_34", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Are use and care instructions included with the purchase of this cast iron skillet for first-time users?", "long_answer": "The skillet includes use and care instructions designed to assist first-time cast iron users in the proper maintenance and seasoning of their new cookware.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_35", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Are replacement parts available for purchase for the Presto 5900 Electric Wok, like new legs or a glass lid?", "long_answer": "Replacement parts for the Presto 5900 Electric Wok, including legs and a glass lid, can be acquired by contacting the manufacturer's customer service, which will assist in obtaining the correct components.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_17", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I ain't too impressed with Ozeri, so show me some other brand's pan that's at least 10 inches. And no funny business, show me the first one you find.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Ozeri' AND size >= 10 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_36", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is this pan compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "This pan is confirmed to be induction-ready, meaning it is designed for use on all types of stovetops, including induction cooktops, thereby ensuring its compatibility.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_13", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "If I don't maintain this pan consistently, will its appearance alter over time?", "long_answer": "Indeed, because the pan is not dishwasher safe, it may need to be polished to maintain its look, along with routine upkeep such as seasoning, based on the material, to avoid aesthetic degradation.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" do not have a function of self-maintenance and will need regular seasoning (for cast iron or carbon steel) or polishing (for aesthetic reasons) to maintain their best condition.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_37", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the red Thermo-Spot on the cookware designed to maintain its color over time with regular use?", "long_answer": "The red Thermo-Spot on the cookware is engineered to remain visible with regular use. Its durability ensures it should not fade quickly. However, factors like abrasive cleaning methods or exposure to excessive heat can result in wear and potentially affect the color over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_38", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does the cooking surface maintain its non-stick properties over time?", "long_answer": "The cooking surface of the product is designed to be non-stick and customer feedback suggests it performs well initially. Nevertheless, over time, the effectiveness of the non-stick feature may diminish, and it is essential to follow proper maintenance guidelines to sustain its non-stick quality for as long as possible.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_14", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is this pan ready for immediate use on an induction cooktop straight from the packaging?", "long_answer": "Should you be interested in our aluminum or copper frying pans or skillets, be aware that they are not compatible with magnetic induction, which is crucial for induction cooktops. To use them on these types of stoves, you will need an extra ferrous disc to facilitate the required magnetic response for heating.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_18", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Look, I'm not shelling out more than 30 dollars for a pan but it's gotta be larger than 12 inches. What's the best option you got for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND size > 12 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND size > 12 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND size > 12 ORDER BY price ASC, size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_39", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "How does the weight of these die-cast aluminum pans compare to cast iron pans for handling?", "long_answer": "The pans are constructed from die-cast aluminum, which is generally lighter than cast iron. They are designed to provide the benefit of even heating while also being easier to handle due to their less burdensome weight.", "short_answer": "lighter", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_40", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are the pans in the Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The pans in the Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri are equipped with a magnetized base specifically designed to be safe for induction cooktops, which facilitates quick and efficient heat transfer.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_19", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm trying to match my kitchen decor and I want a big, blue pan. What's the cheapest one you got that's 12 inches or bigger?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND size >= 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND size >= 12 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND size >= 12 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' AND size >= 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_41", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Does the product's nonstick coating contain PFOA?", "long_answer": "The product is equipped with a high-performance reinforced nonstick coating that is free from PFOA, thereby providing a safer cooking experience and facilitating easy cleanup.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_42", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Are customers generally satisfied with the non-stick quality of this product?", "long_answer": "The customer feedback reflects that satisfaction with the non-stick quality is high among the majority of customers, especially when they adhere to the provided care instructions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_43", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is this product compatible with induction cooktops as well as other types of cooktops?", "long_answer": "This product is indeed versatile when it comes to compatibility with various cooktops. It can be used on gas, induction, ceran, halogen, and electric cooktops, allowing for a wide range of applications in different kitchen settings.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_44", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the interior of the pot include measurement marks?", "long_answer": "The product metadata does not detail whether measurement marks are present on the interior of the pot, and reviews do not frequently mention this feature, thus it is not possible to confirm that the pot comes with interior measurement markings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_20", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I don't want any black pan, and it needs to handle at least 450F. What's the cheapest option does your store offer?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'black' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_45", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan prone to warping?", "long_answer": "The ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan is constructed with a robust aluminum core, which ensures even heating and serves to resist warping. Customer feedback indicates that warping is not a common problem with this pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_21", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Look, I gotta avoid grey, but I'm keen on either Presto or Bialetti brands for pans. Which can tolerate the highest oven heat from these specific brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Bialetti\") AND NOT color = \"grey\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Bialetti\") AND NOT color = \"grey\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Bialetti\") AND NOT color = \"grey\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Presto', 'Bialetti') AND color != 'grey' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_46", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the pan lighter or heavier compared to similar cookware products?", "long_answer": "The pan's design balances sturdiness with ease of handling, implying that it is neither too heavy nor too light but provides the right weight for comfortable use during cooking compared to similar cookware products.", "short_answer": "balanced", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_47", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Does the non-stick surface of the pan maintain its performance over time with proper care?", "long_answer": "With the proper maintenance and adherence to care instructions, the non-stick surface tends to perform well according to the majority of customers. Nevertheless, there are reports from some customers of a decrease in non-stick performance as time passes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_15", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Should I follow any specific precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "long_answer": "To preserve the condition of the pan's surface, refrain from using harsh detergents or abrasive scrubbing tools that may mar the anodized aluminum. For best results, employ a gentle touch, cleaning with a soft sponge or cloth to maintain the pan's non-stick and non-reactive qualities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with anodized aluminum are not suitable for use with metal utensils that can scratch the hardened surface, potentially compromising its non-reactive properties.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_48", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Does the pan's ergonomic handle successfully ease the handling of the pan's weight?", "long_answer": "The ergonomic handle on the pan is engineered to offer a comfortable and secure grip, which facilitates easier handling and management of the pan's weight as experienced by the majority of users.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_49", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is the Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet can indeed be used on induction cooktops due to its cast iron construction, which not only allows it to work on induction surfaces but also provides exceptional heat distribution and retention, leading to more precise cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_50", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is this saucepan oven-safe?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is crafted from high-quality stainless steel, which allows for its use both on the stovetop and in the oven, indicating its oven-safe properties.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_51", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are the silicone-coated handles of cookware resistant to high temperatures?", "long_answer": "The cookware comes with handles coated with heat-resistant silicone, designed to endure typical stovetop cooking temperatures and can sustain moderate oven use. But it is recommended to consult the maximum temperature guidelines provided with the product.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_52", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Can the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan be safely placed in an oven?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti 12-inch saute pan features handles that are heat-resistant, meaning they can withstand a certain degree of heat. However, these handles are not oven-proof, which implies that the pan should not be used in an oven as it is not designed to be oven-safe.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_22", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I don't have a lot of dough to spend, but I need a Utopia Kitchen pan that won't cost more than 30 dollars and can handle high oven temperatures. What's the best one you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch` with asin: B00X4WQMAS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" AND price <= 30 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_23", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I don't want a Tramontina, show me the cheapest alternative you have in your pan range.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Tramontina' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_24", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm hunting for a black pan. Preferably All-Clad or USA Pan. Which one of those can withstand the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black` with asin: B0170TFNXM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" AND brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"USA Pan\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" AND brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"USA Pan\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" AND brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"USA Pan\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'black' AND (brand = 'All-Clad' OR brand = 'USA Pan') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_53", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Do the pot's handles provide comfort and safety when handling?", "long_answer": "The pot comes with ergonomically designed handles which are specifically created to offer a comfortable and safe grip while being used.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_54", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is this pan designed to withstand repeated use for batch baking?", "long_answer": "The pan's capacity to bake 12 items simultaneously, alongside its durability and ease of cleanup, suggests that it is suitable for repeated use when batch baking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_25", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm not messing around anymore with pans that warp under high heat. Which one of your pans can handle temperatures of over 500 degrees Fahrenheit? Give me the first one you get.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_55", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Does cooking with this wok provide energy savings compared to using a traditional stove?", "long_answer": "The wok is designed to heat up rapidly and allows for meal preparation without the necessity of engaging the larger stove, suggesting that it could lead to energy conservation. Nevertheless, there is no mention of explicit energy efficiency ratings for the wok in the provided information.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_56", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is this pan designed to be dishwasher-safe?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be dishwasher-safe, allowing for convenient cleaning. However, to maintain the non-stick surface and the exterior finish in optimal condition, hand-washing is recommended over machine washing.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_57", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this cast iron skillet without scratching it?", "long_answer": "Metal utensils can be used with a cast iron skillet, but it's important to avoid aggressive scraping which could potentially harm the protective seasoning layer on the skillet's surface over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_16", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I frequently encounter issues with pans failing to heat uniformly on my stove. Does this design assist in promoting even heat distribution?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the pan's round shape assists in the even distribution of heat across its surface, enhancing compatibility and heating efficiency on various stovetops, encompassing both conventional and contemporary induction cooktops, provided it is made with suitable magnetic materials.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_26", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I've got a thing against All-Clad and I'm dead set on grey. Show me the first pan that you've got that fits that description.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray` with asin: B000069RBK", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"All-Clad\" AND color = \"grey\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"All-Clad\" AND color = \"grey\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'All-Clad' AND color = 'grey' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_58", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Are any accessories, such as a lid or spatula, included with the purchase of this frying pan?", "long_answer": "The frying pan is sold as a single item, and the product metadata does not specify the inclusion of any accessories, implying that a lid or spatula is not provided with the pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_59", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is a metal spatula suitable for use with this non-stick pan?", "long_answer": "The non-stick surface of this pan is specifically designed for use with utensils made of nylon, silicone, or wood in order to preserve its non-stick quality. Using metal utensils is not recommended as it could potentially damage the pan's surface.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_60", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is it necessary to season the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan in the same way as a cast iron pan?", "long_answer": "Unlike cast iron cookware, the All-Clad Stainless 10-inch fry pan is made from stainless steel, which does not need seasoning to create a non-stick surface or to maintain its quality over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_61", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "What is the weight characteristic of this pan as reported by users?", "long_answer": "Users frequently describe the pan as relatively lightweight, which contributes to ease of handling and facilitates convenient usage while cooking.", "short_answer": "lightweight", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_27", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Look, I don't have more than 10 bucks and I only trust Copper Chef and Ozeri. Find me a pan from one of those brands.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Ozeri\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Ozeri\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Copper Chef', 'Ozeri') AND price <= 10;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_62", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "What is the composition material of the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan?", "long_answer": "The pan is crafted from aluminized steel, which is known for its heavy gauge construction. This material choice ensures even heat distribution and contributes to the pan's durability, making it a sturdy option for baking.", "short_answer": "aluminized steel", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_28", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm looking for a pan, either copper or green, that can handle high temperatures. Which one can withstand the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"green\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"green\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('copper', 'green') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_63", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the Cuisinart French Classic Pan dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart French Classic Pan is technically dishwasher safe, but to extend the life of the non-stick coating and the pan itself, hand washing with a mild detergent is recommended.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_29", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm doing a lot of big batch cooking these days and I need a big pan that can handle high oven heat. What's the best pan you have that's at least 12 inches and can withstand the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_30", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm tired of those usual silver pans. Find me the biggest pan you have, just make sure it's not silver.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color <> 'silver' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_31", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm only interested in Matfer Bourgeat or Ozeri brand pans. Can you find me the cheapest one from these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"Ozeri\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"Ozeri\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"Ozeri\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Matfer Bourgeat', 'Ozeri') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_64", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Can the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set accommodate servings for two individuals?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is specifically tailored for individual or two-person servings, making it an ideal choice for those who are preparing smaller portions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_32", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I've been cooking with Norpro pans for years now, but they're just not heat resistant enough sometimes. Can you tell me what's their highest temperature-safe pan you carry?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches` with asin: B0012BR1XU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Norpro\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Norpro\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Norpro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Norpro' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_33", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm tired of the usual black pans and I'm not a fan of Lodge's stuff. What's the first alternative you can offer?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray` with asin: B000069RBK", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND NOT brand = \"Lodge\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND NOT brand = \"Lodge\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'black' AND brand != 'Lodge' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_65", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Does the Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet come already seasoned?", "long_answer": "The Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet is pre-seasoned, allowing for immediate use upon purchase. While it is ready for cooking without additional preparation, some users may choose to season it once more before first use to further improve its non-stick qualities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_66", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is it necessary to cook with oil or butter when using the ZWILLING Spirit ceramic non-stick pan?", "long_answer": "The ZWILLING Spirit ceramic non-stick coating is designed to enable cooking with reduced quantities of oil, but adding a small amount of oil or butter is recommended to achieve optimal flavor and cooking performance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_34", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Look, I don't want to spend more than 30 dollars, and I need a pan that can handle heat above 600F. What's my cheapest option?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_67", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the pan suitable for preparing meals that serve more than two people?", "long_answer": "The pan is primarily designed for individual or two-person servings. However, it may be used to prepare up to four servings, with the actual number dependent on the type of food being cooked. Customer experiences have shown that while it is not the ideal size for larger meals, it has the capacity to serve more in certain cases.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_68", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is this pot of appropriate size for preparing pasta dishes for a small to medium-sized family?", "long_answer": "The pot is explicitly designed to accommodate pasta preparation, making it an ideal choice for small to medium-sized family meals, ensuring it is sufficient for most domestic cooking requirements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_69", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the T-fal fry pan dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The T-fal fry pan is designed to be dishwasher safe, allowing for convenient and easy cleaning without the need for manual washing.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_70", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is this fry pan compatible with an electric glass top stove?", "long_answer": "This fry pan is designed to be used on various types of stovetops, including gas, electric, and ceramic glass cooktops, making it suitable for use on an electric glass top stove.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_35", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm looking for a grey pan that can stand up to heat. Can you find me one that's above your average oven safe temperature, but keep it cheap?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'grey' AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_71", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "What is the country of origin for the final assembly of these pans with a GREBLON ceramic coating?", "long_answer": "The pans utilize a GREBLON ceramic coating that is made in Germany, but the final assembly of the pans is conducted in China.", "short_answer": "China", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_72", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the Thermo-Spot heat indicator on the pan reliably indicate when the pan is sufficiently pre-heated?", "long_answer": "The Thermo-Spot heat indicator on the pan is generally deemed reliable by the majority of users for signaling when the pan is adequately pre-heated and ready for cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_17", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Can this pan evenly cook my food, particularly during meat searing?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the pan's round design aids in consistent heat distribution, a feature that is especially advantageous for searing meats. This ensures your food cooks evenly, preventing the formation of hot spots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_73", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Can the frying pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?", "long_answer": "It is not recommended to clean the frying pan in a dishwasher because doing so could damage its seasoning. To properly maintain the pan, it should be hand washed using hot water, and if needed, scrubbed with a brush.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_36", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that can withstand the heat of at least 450F and doesn't cost me more than 20 dollars. What's the largest one you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND price <= 20 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_37", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm sticking to a tight budget but still want quality. Give me the biggest pan you have from ZWILLING J.A. Henckels or USA Pan under $10.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"USA Pan\") AND price < 10 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"USA Pan\") AND price < 10 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"USA Pan\") AND price < 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('ZWILLING J.A. Henckels', 'USA Pan')\n      AND price < 10\nORDER BY size DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_38", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I ain't got more than 10 dollars. And my oven works like a blast furnace. So, could you find me an all-purpose pan that can withstand a temperature of over 600F and costs 10 bucks or less?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 600;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_74", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the 1 1/2 quart saucepan large enough to accommodate larger canned items?", "long_answer": "The saucepan has a capacity of 1 1/2 quarts, which may not be adequate for larger canned items; it is primarily designed for smaller cooking needs, such as family size frozen vegetables.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_75", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Does the non-stick performance of the pan degrade after a month of use?", "long_answer": "The pan's non-stick performance may decrease over time, and some customers have noticed this after a month. Adhering to the manufacturer's care and usage guidelines is essential to preserve the pan's non-stick quality.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_76", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "What is the volume capacity, in quarts, of this saucepan?", "long_answer": "The saucepan has a volume capacity of 2 quarts, making it versatile enough to be used in diverse cooking activities.", "short_answer": "2 quarts", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_77", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan manufactured in the United States?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart saucepan is not produced in the United States; it is an imported product. Customers looking for products made in the USA should consider other options that clearly indicate the country of manufacture.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_78", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Would the Madeleine Pan be suitable as a gift for someone who enjoys baking?", "long_answer": "The Madeleine Pan is an excellent choice as a gift, particularly for those with an affinity for baking or for individuals who are interested in beginning to bake.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_79", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with the non-stick surface of this pan?", "long_answer": "Using metal utensils on the non-stick surface of this pan is advised against because they can cause damage to the coating, which may lead to the possibility of voiding the product's warranty.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_18", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "long_answer": "Our frying pans and skillets, crafted from aluminum or copper, boast superior heat conductivity that ensures even cooking. Nevertheless, should you use an induction stove, bear in mind that these materials lack inherent compatibility because they do not possess magnetic properties. Consequently, cooking performance may suffer unless you employ a ferrous plate to enable induction.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_39", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I'm a fan of Presto and Chicago Metallic. Point me to the first pan you have from either of these brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Chicago Metallic\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Chicago Metallic\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Presto', 'Chicago Metallic') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_80", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is the Copper Chef pan resistant to tarnishing and oxidation compared to traditional copper pans?", "long_answer": "The Copper Chef pan is constructed to resist tarnishing and oxidation, which are common issues with traditional copper cookware, thereby needing less maintenance and retaining its aesthetic appeal for a longer duration.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_40", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I always crank my oven up pretty high, like beyond 400F, and I want my pans in blue. Got anything that can handle all that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND color = \"blue\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND color = \"blue\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' AND oven_safe_temperature > 400;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_81", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "What is the duration of the warranty provided for the T-fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot comes with a Lifetime Limited Warranty that reflects the manufacturer's commitment to product quality and durability.", "short_answer": "Lifetime Limited Warranty", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_82", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Is the bottom of the frying pans designed to prevent oil from pooling at the sides?", "long_answer": "The frying pans are designed with a flat bottom to ensure even oil distribution and prevent pooling at the edges. However, factors such as individual cooking style and the evenness of the stove might lead to slight variations in how the oil is distributed during cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_41", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I don't need any blue pans and I'm cooking for a large group, so it needs to be bigger than 8 inches. What's the first thing you'd recommend?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND NOT color = \"blue\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND NOT color = \"blue\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND color != 'blue' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_83", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is the Stone Earth Pan compatible with induction stoves for cooking?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Pan is designed with a magnetized base to facilitate rapid heat transfer when used on induction stoves, which ensures that it performs well by providing even cooking on this type of cooktop.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_42", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Cooking at high temperatures is my game. Get me the cheapest pan that can take the heat over 500F.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_19", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I take pleasure in blackening fish; would this pan be suitable for such a cooking method?", "long_answer": "No, this pan is unsuitable for cooking techniques such as blackening fish that demand very high temperatures. Owing to its aluminum make-up, this pan lacks the high heat resistance of alternatives like cast iron or stainless steel, which are preferred for such methods.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's lack of high heat tolerance lack the capability to withstand searing and broiling applications that require maintaining structural integrity at very high temperatures, unlike cookware made of materials like stainless steel or cast iron.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_84", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is the cookware's handle designed to remain cool during cooking, and does it come with additional heat protection?", "long_answer": "The cookware's handle is constructed to resist high heat and remain cool to the touch during cooking. It is triple-riveted for enhanced stability, and it includes a removable silicone grip that provides extra heat protection and comfort while in use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_43", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm a loyal fan of Chicago Metallic, but I ain't paying more than 20 dollars. What's the cheapest pan you got from them?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND price < 20 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND price < 20 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Chicago Metallic' AND price <= 20 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_44", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Listen, I'm picky about colors. You got any pans in either grey or blue? Just show me the first one that fits the criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray` with asin: B000069RBK", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"blue\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"blue\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'blue') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_20", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for roasting a chicken?", "long_answer": "No, this pan is not suitable for \"dry cooking\" techniques like roasting as it includes a tempered glass lid. The design of such lids is meant to hold in moisture, which could disrupt the necessary dry heat for properly roasting a chicken.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids are not suitable for recipes requiring “dry cooking” methods such as roasting or baking without moisture, as the lids are designed to retain moisture within the pan.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_45", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I have a strict requirement for oven-safe temperature to be at least 450°F and anything but green. What's the first pan you can recommend?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND NOT color = \"green\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND NOT color = \"green\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND color != 'green' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_21", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is it safe to use my metal spatula with this pan without causing any damage?", "long_answer": "To preserve this pan's condition, it is recommended to refrain from using metal utensils. Constructed from anodized aluminum, the pan is quite resilient; however, it is susceptible to scratching from metal utensils. Such damage could impair the pan's non-reactive qualities and reduce its lifespan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with anodized aluminum are not suitable for use with metal utensils that can scratch the hardened surface, potentially compromising its non-reactive properties.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_46", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I ain't paying more than 10 dollars and I need a pan that's at least 12 inches. Can you find me a deal like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND size >= 12 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND size >= 12 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND size >= 12;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_47", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I don't want to pay more than the average price and I really like copper color. Seriously, show me the first pan you’ve got that meets my criteria.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND color = \"copper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND color = \"copper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND color = 'copper' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_48", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I do a lot of high temp cooking and only use Norpro gadgets. Do you have any pans that can take at least 500F? What's the ID of the product that can do this?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND brand = \"Norpro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND brand = \"Norpro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Norpro' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_49", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I am not a fan of green and my cooking usually requires high heat. Which pan can withstand an oven temperature over 600F but isn't green?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT color = \"green\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT color = \"green\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'green' AND oven_safe_temperature > 600;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_50", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I'm after a pan that's either grey or copper, and I'm not interested in breaking the bank. Can you find me the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'copper') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_51", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I need a new pan, but I want it to be bigger than 12 inches and either green or blue. What's the cheapest one you got in those specifications?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") AND size > 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") AND size > 12 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") AND size > 12 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND (color = 'green' OR color = 'blue') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_52", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I ain't gonna throw over 30 dollars for a pan. Find me the biggest heckin' one in the budget.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_53", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm after a Matfer Bourgeat pan but don't have more than 50 bucks to drop. Get me the highest oven-safe one within my budget.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Matfer Bourgeat' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_54", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I plan on using my pan in the oven at pretty high temp, over 600 degrees, and I have a thing for copper or silver. What's the product that matches these preferences?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND color IN (\"copper\", \"silver\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND color IN (\"copper\", \"silver\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('copper', 'silver') AND oven_safe_temperature > 600;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_85", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is the saucepan available for purchase within a cookware set offered by Anolon?", "long_answer": "Anolon provides the option to purchase cookware sets which may include saucepans, although this particular listing is for a single saucepan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_22", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is this pan capable of retaining moisture while cooking vegetables to prevent them from becoming dry?", "long_answer": "Certainly, when preparing vegetables, the stainless steel lid of this pan will prove useful. Its ability to form a tight seal effectively traps moisture, preventing the vegetables from becoming dry and preserving their authentic flavor and texture.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a stainless steel lid are known for providing an effective seal to lock in heat and moisture, enhancing cooking methods like simmering and braising.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "stainless steel lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_55", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I need a reliable All-Clad pan that can withstand over 400F in the oven. What's the first one you've got that can take the heat?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black` with asin: B0170TFNXM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'All-Clad' AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_56", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm a big fan of \"Copper Chef\", and I'm looking for a pan that's bigger than average size. Also, I need it to handle high temperatures in the oven. Got anything like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Copper Chef' AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans);"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_86", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is prior seasoning required for this non-stick ceramic coated pan before its initial use?", "long_answer": "Seasoning the pan is not required before its initial use since it comes with a non-stick ceramic coating that is ready for cooking straight from the packaging.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_57", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm a big fan of Bialetti, and I'm currently looking for the largest pan they've got. Which one is it?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal` with asin: B000S6I4ZE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Bialetti\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Bialetti\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Bialetti\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Bialetti' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_87", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is it advisable to use cooking sprays on the nonstick surface of the pan?", "long_answer": "The manufacturer's recommendation for this nonstick pan is to avoid using cooking sprays. To achieve the best culinary results and maintain the integrity of the surface, it's suggested to use a modest amount of oil or butter.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_58", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm a big fan of Norpro, but I'm looking specifically for a pan that can stand a temperature above 450F in the oven. Can you find that for me?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Norpro\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Norpro\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Norpro' AND oven_safe_temperature > 450;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_59", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I like my pans to handle some heat in the oven, at least 400F, and they gotta be bigger than 8 inches. What's the most affordable one you got that meets these requirements?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size > 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size > 8 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size > 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND size > 8 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_60", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Look, I'm after a really good pan but it's gotta be either blue or copper, just not Bialetti. Got anything that can handle the highest temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") AND NOT brand = \"Bialetti\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") AND NOT brand = \"Bialetti\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") AND NOT brand = \"Bialetti\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('blue', 'copper') \nAND brand != 'Bialetti' \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_23", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is this pan suitable for recipes requiring prolonged high heat, like stir-frying?", "long_answer": "It is advisable not to use this aluminum pan for recipes requiring continuous high heat, such as stir-frying. Aluminum's limited high heat tolerance suggests it won't perform as effectively as cookware crafted from more heat-resistant materials, such as cast iron or stainless steel, that can reliably withstand the high temperatures necessary for stir-frying.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's lack of high heat tolerance lack the capability to withstand searing and broiling applications that require maintaining structural integrity at very high temperatures, unlike cookware made of materials like stainless steel or cast iron.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_24", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Do I require specialized cleaning agents for the pan to maintain its like-new appearance?", "long_answer": "Although not mandatory, pans featuring stainless steel lids necessitate some maintenance to maintain their aesthetic, including periodic polishing and prompt drying. Should minimizing additional upkeep be important to you, opting for pans with alternative lid materials may be advisable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a stainless steel lid fail to meet the requirements for maintenance-free aesthetics over time, as they may require polishing if the shine is to be maintained and are susceptible to water spots if not dried promptly.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "stainless steel lid", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_88", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Does using cast iron cookware provide health benefits over nonstick pans due to its lack of synthetic coatings and iron contribution to food?", "long_answer": "Cast iron cookware is favored by many because it does not have synthetic coatings that could potentially release harmful chemicals. Additionally, cooking with cast iron has a health advantage as it can impart a small but significant amount of iron to the food prepared in it.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_89", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Does the pan's design include a raised center that could lead to uneven cooking?", "long_answer": "The design of the pan may feature a slightly raised center according to some customer observations, which has the potential to affect evenness in cooking. However, this can be mitigated by using an adequate amount of oil to create a more even cooking surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_61", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I'm not a fan of Ozeri at all. Which pan from any other brand can withstand the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Ozeri' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_62", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm looking for a silver Presto pan, but I don't want to break the bank. What's the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND brand = \"Presto\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND brand = \"Presto\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND brand = \"Presto\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Presto' AND color = 'silver' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_90", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this pan without damaging its surface?", "long_answer": "While metal utensils may be used with this pan, it is recommended to opt for gentle tools in order to protect and maintain the integrity of the pan's surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_91", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Should I use high heat while cooking with stainless steel cookware to avoid damaging the pan?", "long_answer": "Cooking with stainless steel cookware typically requires medium heat to prevent food from sticking and to protect the pan's surface. It's crucial to consult the manufacturer's instructions for optimal cooking temperatures and methods for the specific cookware.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_25", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I like to blacken fish; will this pan suffice for such cooking?", "long_answer": "No, this pan is unsuitable for cooking methods such as blackening fish that demand the ability to endure extremely high temperatures. As it is made of aluminum, it lacks the high heat resistance inherent to materials like cast iron or stainless steel that are more appropriate for such techniques.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's lack of high heat tolerance lack the capability to withstand searing and broiling applications that require maintaining structural integrity at very high temperatures, unlike cookware made of materials like stainless steel or cast iron.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_63", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm pretty particular about the brands I use in my kitchen. Get me the first product you have from either Anolon or All-Clad.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black` with asin: B0170TFNXM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"All-Clad\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"All-Clad\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Anolon', 'All-Clad') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_64", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I don't want to splurge but I'm a fan of All-Clad. Could you suggest a pan that doesn't cost more than 50 dollars from All-Clad?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND price <= 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND price <= 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND brand = 'All-Clad';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_65", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I like to bake in high temperatures, and I need something sizable. What's the biggest pan you have that can withstand more than 600F in the oven?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_92", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is the pan designed for Madeleines suitable for baking other similar-sized desserts?", "long_answer": "The pan is specifically crafted for Madeleines; however, thanks to its non-stick surface, it can be also used to bake other desserts that are comparable in size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_66", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I'm only interested in Tramontina and All-Clad pans. Find me the cheapest one from these brands, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch` with asin: B009HBKQR0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"All-Clad\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"All-Clad\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"All-Clad\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Tramontina', 'All-Clad') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_93", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is this saucepan dishwasher-safe?", "long_answer": "The saucepan should be hand-washed for optimal care since it is not suitable for cleaning in a dishwasher because of its nonstick coating.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_67", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm in the market for a new pan and I'm considering either All-Clad or Matfer Bourgeat, but only in either a copper or black color. Give me the first pan you find that matches those requirements.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") AND color IN (\"copper\", \"black\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") AND color IN (\"copper\", \"black\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (brand = 'All-Clad' OR brand = 'Matfer Bourgeat') AND (color = 'copper' OR color = 'black') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_68", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I'm in need of a pan that can handle some serious heat, over 450F, and I only do black or silver in my kitchen. What's the best you got for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND color IN (\"black\", \"silver\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND color IN (\"black\", \"silver\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('black', 'silver') AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_94", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Are the legs of this wok stand sturdy and durable for normal home use despite some users reporting issues over time?", "long_answer": "Despite reports from some users about wobbly or breaking legs after extensive use or over a long period, the wok stand appears to be sturdy and durable for most customers during regular home use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_95", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is it recommended to cook acidic foods in this pan before a good patina has been established?", "long_answer": "It is not recommended to cook highly acidic foods in the pan until a very good patina has been established, as doing so may strip the seasoning off the pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_69", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I need a pan from the brand Chicago Metallic, but I don't wanna burn more than 10 dollars for this. Can you find any for me?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Chicago Metallic' AND price <= 10;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_96", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is the pan dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The pan should not be placed in a dishwasher as this could damage its seasoning and reduce its lifespan. Hand washing without soap is the best method for cleaning to preserve the pan's quality.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_70", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm after a cheap pan that can handle some serious heat, at least 500 degrees. Find me something solid for under 30 dollars, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND price <= 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND price <= 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_97", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the electric wok designed with rounded sides identical to traditional woks?", "long_answer": "The electric wok bears resemblance to traditional woks with rounded sides; however, it is engineered with a flat bottom to support the electric heating element, providing a slightly altered cooking experience when compared to authentic round-bottomed woks.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_98", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the heavy-gauge aluminum pan capable of distributing heat evenly?", "long_answer": "The pan is constructed with heavy-gauge aluminum, a material that is engineered to facilitate fast and even heat distribution, thereby ensuring a uniform cooking experience.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_99", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the riveted silicone handle on this cookware maintain a cool temperature during use?", "long_answer": "The design of the riveted silicone handle is specifically intended to remain cool when touched, and user feedback generally supports this claim, affirming that it provides a comfortable and safe grip while cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_100", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the pot feature a non-stick surface on both the interior and exterior?", "long_answer": "The pot is designed with a non-stick surface on both the inside and the outside, which facilitates ease of cleaning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_101", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is it safe to use the pan on high heat without damaging the non-stick surface?", "long_answer": "The pan should be used on low to medium heat in accordance with the manufacturer's guidelines in order to preserve the non-stick surface. Using the pan on high heat could potentially damage the surface and may also void the warranty.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_102", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is it recommended to store food in the refrigerator using these non-stick pans?", "long_answer": "Storing food in non-stick cookware inside the refrigerator is generally discouraged, as the acidic content of food and presence of moisture could potentially degrade the non-stick surface over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_103", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is it advisable to frequently cook acidic foods such as tomato sauce in this pan?", "long_answer": "Cooking acidic foods like tomato sauce in this pan is generally not advised, as they can damage the seasoned layer on the pan's surface. If the seasoning is lost, it requires reapplication to restore the pan's non-stick properties.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_26", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this non-stick pan?", "long_answer": "It is recommended to avoid using metal utensils on this pan because it is constructed from ceramic material that is prone to scratching or chipping when exposed to such implements. Doing so could impair its non-stick properties and reduce the pan's longevity.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with ceramic material lack the capability to endure the use of metal utensils, as such tools can scratch or chip the non-stick surface and diminish the pan's lifespan.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "ceramic", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_71", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I need a pan of at least 8 inches that can take more heat than your average pan. What's the first one you got that suits this?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_72", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I can't spend tons on cookware, and I need a pan that withstands at least the average oven safe temperature, but costs under 20 dollars. Can you find one for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND price < 20 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND price < 20 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_73", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Listen, I only have 20 bucks to spend on a pan and I only trust Anolon or ZWILLING J.A. Henckels. So what's the best option you got for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND (brand = 'Anolon' OR brand = 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels') ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_27", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Is it safe to wash this pan in the dishwasher without concern for gradual damage?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this pan is crafted to endure the elevated heat and potent detergents typical of dishwashers, maintaining its integrity and appearance over successive washing cycles without succumbing to warping, corrosion, or deterioration.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute feature resistance to both the high temperatures and strong chemicals typical in dishwashers, which ensures they do not warp, rust, or degrade quickly when exposed to such conditions regularly.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_28", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Should I follow any particular precautions when cleaning this pan to preserve its surface?", "long_answer": "To preserve the surface integrity of this pan, steer clear of abrasive cleaning agents or scrubbing pads that might scratch the anodized aluminum. It's advisable to clean gently with a soft sponge or cloth to maintain the pan's non-reactive and non-stick characteristics.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with anodized aluminum are not suitable for use with metal utensils that can scratch the hardened surface, potentially compromising its non-reactive properties.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_104", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is there a lifetime warranty on the Cuisinart Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan?", "long_answer": "Cuisinart provides a lifetime warranty for the Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan, ensuring long-term satisfaction and protection for the purchaser.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_74", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm only interested in black or silver pans and I need it to withstand a pretty high oven temperature. Can you find me the baking pan that fits this criteria?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"silver\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"silver\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"silver\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('black', 'silver') AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_75", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Look, I need a pan that won't break the bank, and it's gotta be bigger than your average size. Also, I need it to survive some serious oven time. Show me the one that ticks all these boxes.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) \nAND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) \nAND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans);"}}
{"id": "search_qa_76", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I'm trying to save a few bucks here and I need a pan that can stand heat up to 400F. Can you fetch me the cheapest option you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 \nORDER BY price \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_105", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set constructed using nonstick materials?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is constructed from stainless steel, which is not a nonstick material. To reduce the likelihood of food sticking to the pan, it is recommended to spray the pan with cooking oil before use.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_29", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?", "long_answer": "Round-shaped pans are not the most space-efficient for storage in tight kitchens, which may be a disadvantage if maximizing every inch is essential. Square or angular pans might fit better if you need to tuck them into a small cupboard or shelf.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_106", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is cooking spray suitable for use with a Tramontina nonstick pan, or is cooking oil the better option?", "long_answer": "For Tramontina nonstick pans, using a small amount of cooking oil is recommended over cooking spray. The chemical additives in cooking spray can accumulate on the nonstick surface, potentially diminishing the pan's performance and durability over time.", "short_answer": "cooking oil", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_107", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is greasing the pan necessary when using a pan with a high-quality non-stick coating for baking?", "long_answer": "Greasing the pan is generally not required when using a high-quality non-stick coated pan, as the coating is designed to prevent sticking. Light greasing might still be preferred depending on the specific recipe or for added assurance of easy release of the baked item.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_30", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I understand that certain pans require particular attention following use. Could you elaborate on the care needed for this specific pan?", "long_answer": "This specific pan requires special attention, as it is not safe for dishwasher cleaning. Post-cooking, it must be hand-washed using proper methods and promptly dried to avoid damage. Should you prefer not to dedicate time to such maintenance routinely, consider opting for a dishwasher-safe pan instead.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are not recommended for use by consumers who may not be willing or able to invest the time and effort into the careful maintenance these pans require, which includes correct hand-washing techniques and immediate drying to prevent damage.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_77", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm not made of money, I need a pan for my cluttered kitchen without breaking the bank. Can you show me the largest one you got for 20 dollars or less?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_78", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I've got a beef with T-fal, so omit them. Show me the cheapest pan you got under 50 bucks.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"T-fal\" AND price < 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"T-fal\" AND price < 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'T-fal' AND price < 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_108", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Does the stainless-steel cooking surface of this pan impart a metallic taste to food?", "long_answer": "The stainless-steel cooking surface of the pan is non-reactive, ensuring that it does not alter the flavors of the food by imparting a metallic taste during cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_79", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm no Rockefeller - I can't shell out more than 30 bucks. However, I need a pan that can stand up to high oven temperatures over 400F. Gimme the biggest one you got that fits that criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_80", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I don't want any pans from USA Pan and it's gotta be bigger than 8 inches. Just show me one that fits the criteria, okay?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'USA Pan' AND size > 8 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_31", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "While simmering, I frequently face the challenge of adding water regularly to prevent burning. Can this pan assist in addressing that problem?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this pan will significantly aid in preventing the contents from scorching while simmering. Its robust cast-iron lid is both substantial and hefty, forging a secure seal that retains moisture and diminishes the necessity of frequent water additions. This characteristic will ensure a more seamless simmering experience for you.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a cast iron lid feature a tight seal due to the weight of the lid, which helps in locking in moisture and flavor—a crucial aspect for many cooking methods such as simmering or braising.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "cast iron lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_109", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Does baking bread goods in a heavy pan affect the evenness of heat distribution?", "long_answer": "Baking bread goods in a heavy pan is beneficial as it allows for more even heat distribution, resulting in consistently well-baked products, which is appreciated by many customers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_110", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Does the saucepan's nonstick coating contain the harmful chemical PFOA?", "long_answer": "The saucepan utilizes Dupont's Autograph nonstick coating that is professional in quality, both inside and out, and is specifically designed to be free from PFOA, ensuring its safety for use in cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_111", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Does this wok provide an effective traditional stir-fry cooking experience?", "long_answer": "The wok is found to be effective for traditional stir-frying by the majority of users. However, due to the heating element being concentrated at the bottom, it requires continuous movement of ingredients to achieve even cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_81", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm in need of a big pan that can take some serious heat in the oven. Pull up the first pan you got that's over 10 inches and can handle temperatures above 400 F.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_32", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Do I need to purchase any extra cleaning supplies when I buy this pan?", "long_answer": "Since this pan is not suitable for the dishwasher, you might want to acquire cleaning tools appropriate for manual washing, like a gentle sponge and a light dish detergent. It's also important to have a towel on hand for quick drying to prevent water marks or the possibility of rust, depending on what the pan is made of.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are not recommended for use by consumers who may not be willing or able to invest the time and effort into the careful maintenance these pans require, which includes correct hand-washing techniques and immediate drying to prevent damage.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_112", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set compatible with the size of a standard toaster oven?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is specifically designed to be small enough to fit within the confines of a standard toaster oven, therefore making it a suitable choice for those looking to prepare individual or small servings for two people.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_113", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is the pan considered convenient for storage?", "long_answer": "The pan is regarded as convenient for storage by numerous customers due to its lightweight design which facilitates easy handling and storing.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_114", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the T-fal pot contain any harmful toxins in its materials or non-stick coating?", "long_answer": "T-fal is a well-regarded brand that complies with established safety standards. The materials used in their pots, including the non-stick coating, are manufactured without harmful toxins, ensuring the safety of the cookware for food preparation.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_82", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm looking for a grey or black pan that can withstand a high heat in the oven - up to 600F. Can you find one for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'black') AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_115", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Do customers consider the Spirit Fry Pan's weight to be easily manageable?", "long_answer": "Customers generally regard the Spirit Fry Pan as having a weight that strikes a balance between being lightweight enough to handle comfortably and having a sturdy construction.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_83", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I don't have a ton of cash to splash and I'm not a fan of Tramontina. So, which is the largest pan you have under 50 dollars from a different brand?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND brand != 'Tramontina' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_84", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm fixed on brands like Copper Chef and Norpro and I would prefer a silver or copper colored pan. Which product do you have that matches these specifications?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Norpro\") AND color IN (\"silver\", \"copper\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Norpro\") AND color IN (\"silver\", \"copper\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Copper Chef', 'Norpro') AND color IN ('silver', 'copper');"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_33", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is it simple to recycle this cookware when it needs replacing?", "long_answer": "Certainly, recycling this cookware when it's time for an upgrade is simple. Given that these pans are crafted from aluminum, they're ideal for recycling efforts and can be reprocessed numerous times, consuming less energy.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's environmental considerations are not recommended for those who prefer to minimize their environmental footprint through recyclable and sustainable cookware options, highlighting aluminum's advantage as it can be recycled effectively.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_116", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are these pans dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The pans should preferably be washed by hand using a soft sponge and mild detergent in order to preserve the non-stick surface's quality, rather than being cleaned in a dishwasher.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_85", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm not dropping more than 50 bucks on a pan, got it? Now show me the Utopia Kitchen or Copper Chef one that can withstand the highest temperature.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Copper Chef\") AND price <= 50 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Copper Chef\") AND price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Copper Chef\") AND price <= 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Utopia Kitchen', 'Copper Chef') \nAND price <= 50 \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_117", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Can the Copper Chef pan be used on an induction cooktop?", "long_answer": "The Copper Chef pan is equipped with a stainless steel induction plate, making it compatible with various types of stovetops, such as gas, electric, ceramic, and specifically induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_86", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "No offense, but I don't want any of those Matfer Bourgeat pans. Can you find me the largest pan you have from any other brand?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Matfer Bourgeat' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_87", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Look, I only got a tenner to spend and I'm looking for a pan in either copper or grey color. What options do I have?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"grey\") AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"grey\") AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND (color = 'copper' OR color = 'grey');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_118", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is it possible for the wok to reach the necessary temperatures to sear meats effectively?", "long_answer": "The wok is capable of achieving the high temperatures required for searing meats, provided that it is adequately preheated and the temperature is managed appropriately throughout the cooking process.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_119", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is it necessary to grease a non-stick Madeleine pan prior to baking?", "long_answer": "While the pan has a non-stick coating aimed at easy removal of cakes, it is recommended by some bakers to lightly grease the pan for a guaranteed effortless release of the Madeleines.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_88", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm a bit of an amateur chef and I only trust USA Pan and Lodge pans. Which one of their products can stand the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Lodge\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Lodge\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Lodge\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('USA Pan', 'Lodge') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_120", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Can the Stone Earth Pan safely be used in an oven?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Pan is specifically designed for stovetop use, and there is a lack of information on its oven-safety, thus it is recommended not to use it in an oven to avoid potential damage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_121", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "How does the nonstick performance of All-Clad pans compare to that of other brands in terms of food release and ease of cleaning?", "long_answer": "All-Clad pans are reported by many users to have superior nonstick performance compared to other brands they have owned, specifically in the areas of food release and ease of cleaning.", "short_answer": "better", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_122", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan cannot be used on induction cooktops because its construction material is aluminum, and aluminum is not a magnetic metal required to work with induction stoves.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_123", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "How user-friendly is the maintenance of the mirror polish on the pan?", "long_answer": "The maintenance of the mirror polish on the pan is generally user-friendly, as reported by a majority of users who find it easy to maintain the pan's exterior. Scratches on the mirror polish can be effectively polished out, helping to preserve the pan's visual appeal over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_124", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Can these pans be used on an induction cooktop without issues?", "long_answer": "These pans are specifically designed to be compatible with induction cooktops, ensuring that they will function efficiently when used on such cooking surfaces.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_34", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is this pan designed to be presentable for table service?", "long_answer": "This saucepan is perfectly designed for cooking, but it wasn't made with table presentation in mind. If you're looking for an appealing table setting, consider looking for pans or dishes that are specifically designed to be aesthetically pleasing when serving.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan are not recommended for serving food directly due to their construction, as they are primarily designed for cooking rather than table presentation.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_125", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the T-fal Professional fry pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods without exceeding its temperature limit?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Professional fry pan is designed to withstand various cooking methods, including high-heat techniques, as long as the temperature does not surpass the recommended maximum oven-safe threshold of 400 degrees Fahrenheit.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_89", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I ain't got tons of cash to splash and I need my pan to handle a hot oven. Show me the cheapest pan you got that can take 400F and still costs less than 10 dollars.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price < 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_126", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the saucepan designed for easy hand cleaning?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed to be easy to clean by hand, as reflected in customer reports indicating that it typically requires just a quick rinse and wipe down.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_90", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm not about to ruin a good pan in a hot oven and my wallet can't take a hit over 30 dollars. Show me your cheapest heat-resistant pan, safe for at least 500 degrees.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_91", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I need a sturdy pan that can take the heat above 400F and comes in either silver or blue. What's the largest one you've got in stock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND color IN (\"silver\", \"blue\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND color IN (\"silver\", \"blue\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND color IN (\"silver\", \"blue\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND color IN ('silver', 'blue') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_92", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm whipping up dishes that require some serious heat, above 450F. What's the largest pan you got that can handle that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_93", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I got a big family to feed, need a pan at least 8 inches. Can you find me one that can handle the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_127", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils on this fry pan's nonstick interior?", "long_answer": "The fry pan is equipped with a ProMetal nonstick interior that is designed to be safe for use with metal utensils, but for increased longevity of the nonstick coating, the use of non-metal utensils is recommended.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_94", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I need a pan that's at least 12 inches, but I didn't have a good experience with Tramontina. Show me the one with the highest oven-safe temperature you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND brand <> 'Tramontina' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_95", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm cooking for a lot of guests. I need a big pan, atleast 12 inches. Also, the color should be either blue or copper. Can you help me find one?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND (color = 'blue' OR color = 'copper');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_128", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the Bialetti 6168 Fry Pan compatible with a ceramic glass stovetop without causing scratches?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti 6168 Fry Pan is specifically designed to be compatible with all types of conventional stovetops, including ceramic and glass. It will not cause scratches on the stovetop surface, assuming that it is used correctly and with care.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_96", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I ain't looking to spend a fortune, but I need a pan that can withstand a 600F oven and doesn't cost more than 20 dollars. What's the biggest one you got that fits the bill?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND price <= 20 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND price <= 20 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND price <= 20 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND price <= 20 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_97", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I want a blue pan but nothing from Matfer Bourgeat. Gimme what you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' AND brand != 'Matfer Bourgeat'"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_129", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Does the Presto 5900 Electric Wok perform comparably to a gas burner for stir-frying?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 Electric Wok is designed specifically for stir-frying on electric cooktops. While there may be minor distinctions in performance when compared with gas burners, it is generally considered to meet the cooking needs effectively for many customers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_35", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Are there particular considerations for what I should refrain from cooking in this pan?", "long_answer": "While cooking with a cast iron skillet, it's best to limit the duration of cooking acidic foods. Acids may interact with the cast iron, eroding the essential seasoning layer that provides flavor and non-stick capabilities, and potentially giving your food a metallic flavor. Conversely, non-acidic foods can be prepared in the skillet without any issues.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being made from cast iron cannot be used for acidic foods like tomato sauce for extended periods, as the acid can strip the seasoning and cause the food to take on a metallic taste.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "cast iron", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_98", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm looking for a high-quality pan. It needs to be oven safe up to at least 400F and bigger than 12 inches. What's the best option you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND size > 12 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND size > 12 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND size > 12\nORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_130", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are the non-stick ceramic coated pans dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "While the non-stick ceramic coated pans are advertised as easy to clean, it is advised to hand wash them in order to prolong the life of the non-stick coating and maintain their condition over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_99", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm looking to do some high heat cooking, so I need a pan that can take at least 500F. And no green ones, please. What's the best you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND NOT color = \"green\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND NOT color = \"green\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND color != 'green' ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_100", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Look, I'm a fan of Lodge and frequently cook at high temperatures. Show me a pan from Lodge that can withstand more than 600F in the oven.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Lodge\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Lodge\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Lodge' AND oven_safe_temperature > 600;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_131", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the T-fal Specialty Nonstick pot available for purchase as a standalone item rather than as a component of a larger set?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Specialty Nonstick pot is indeed available for purchase individually, catering to customers who require a replacement for an existing pot or prefer not to invest in a full cookware set.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_101", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm looking for the largest pan either from Utopia Kitchen or Lodge, but nothing copper. Brass tacks - what's my best option?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch` with asin: B00X4WQMAS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Lodge\") AND NOT color = \"copper\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Lodge\") AND NOT color = \"copper\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Lodge\") AND NOT color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Utopia Kitchen', 'Lodge') \nAND color != 'copper'\nORDER BY size DESC\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_132", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "How does the quality of the USA Pan compare to pans from high-end baking stores?", "long_answer": "The quality of the USA Pan is considered to parallel that of pans from other high-end baking stores, offering a professional-grade level of performance for baking tasks.", "short_answer": "comparable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_36", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it's subjected to regular dishwashing cycles?", "long_answer": "No, frequent dishwashing will not diminish the finish. The pans are crafted from sturdy metals with durable coatings or are anodized, designed to withstand the rigors of dishwashing and preserve their quality appearance.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_133", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does this pan have a safe non-stick coating that prevents chemical exposure?", "long_answer": "The non-stick coating applied to this pan is intended to be safe for culinary purposes, provided it is used in accordance with the manufacturer's guidelines. This includes not overheating the pan when empty and refraining from the use of sharp objects that could potentially scratch and damage the coating surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_134", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "What is the shape of the base of the wok, and is it appropriate for use on an electric heating element?", "long_answer": "The wok comes with a flat base, designed specifically to be compatible with electric stovetops, ensuring that the heat is distributed evenly during cooking.", "short_answer": "flat, yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_37", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for dishes requiring frequent temperature adjustments?", "long_answer": "If your cooking often necessitates swift and frequent changes in temperature, a cast iron pan might not serve you well. Owing to its sluggish heat conduction, cast iron struggles to respond promptly to shifts in temperature, which complicates the handling of recipes demanding those precise adjustments.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being made from cast iron are not recommended for rapid cooking or recipes requiring quick temperature changes, due to their slow heat conductivity and weight.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "cast iron", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_135", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Is the All-Clad E785S264 frying pan set compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The All-Clad E785S264 frying pan set is designed to be compatible with induction cooktops, though it is advised to use the pan on a burner that matches the pan's size to achieve the best cooking performance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_136", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is it safe to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat settings?", "long_answer": "It is not recommended to use the Anolon saucepan on high heat as doing so can damage the nonstick coating and consequently diminish the saucepan's longevity. The saucepan is durable but to maintain its nonstick properties and overall integrity, it's best to avoid high-temperature cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_102", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I don't need any small pans. Give me a big one, at least 8 inches, and it better be a USA Pan or Cuisinart. What's the first product you find?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Cuisinart\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Cuisinart\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('USA Pan', 'Cuisinart') AND size >= 8 ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_103", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I've got a pretty picky kitchen color scheme here, and I need a blue pan that can handle at least 400F in the oven. Got anything like that in your store?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_137", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the pan's design conducive to balanced weight distribution for easy tossing and flipping?", "long_answer": "The pan's design targets balanced weight distribution, which facilitates the process of tossing and sliding food, making it well-suited for tasks like crepe making and other cooking techniques that require such actions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_104", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm doing some heavy cooking and need an All-Clad pan that can handle more than 500°F. Which one would you suggest?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND brand = \"All-Clad\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND brand = \"All-Clad\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'All-Clad' AND oven_safe_temperature > 500;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_105", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I do a lot of heavy-duty cooking and need a pan that's at least 10 inches and can stand a temperature of over 500F. What's the best one you have got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 \nORDER BY price DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_106", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "No more than 50 bucks and I want something bigger than 8 inches. Find me the pan that can take the most heat.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND size > 8 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND size > 8 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND size > 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND size > 8 \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_107", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm specifically looking for a bigger pan, over 8 inches, from ZWILLING J.A Henckels. Give me the cheapest option you have.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' AND size > 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_138", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Are the cookware handles resistant to high temperatures during stovetop use?", "long_answer": "The handles of the cookware are designed to resist heat, allowing for regular stovetop use; however, exposing them to extremely high temperatures for extended timeframes could potentially cause damage. Adhering to the provided usage instructions is recommended to ensure safe handling and longevity of the cookware.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_108", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm in need of a pan that's at least 12 inches, but not a fan of the color blue. Gimme the first option you have that matches my criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND NOT color = \"blue\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND NOT color = \"blue\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND color != 'blue' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_139", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Does the pan's non-stick surface work as advertised?", "long_answer": "Customers generally report that the non-stick surface of the pan functions effectively, particularly when the pan is properly preheated and a minor amount of oil or butter is used to facilitate food release.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_140", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this nonstick pan?", "long_answer": "It is not recommended to use metal utensils with this nonstick pan as they can damage the nonstick surface. Instead, it is advised to use utensils made of nylon, silicone, or wood to maintain the integrity of the pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_141", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is the GREBLON ceramic coating on cookware safe from releasing toxic chemicals when used at high temperatures?", "long_answer": "The GREBLON ceramic coating is specifically engineered to be non-toxic and is safe as it does not emit harmful fumes when exposed to high temperatures, unlike some traditional non-stick coatings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_38", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is it acceptable to use a steel wool scrubber to eliminate persistent food remnants from this pan?", "long_answer": "It is not advisable to use a steel wool scrubber on this pan. Since the pan is constructed from aluminum and might feature a non-stick coating or be anodized, abrasive cleaning pads such as steel wool could harm the finish and impair its non-stick capabilities.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's specific maintenance needs fail to meet the requirements for indiscriminate cleaning methods such as harsh scouring pads or certain dishwasher detergents, especially if they have a non-stick layer or are anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_109", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that's either black or grey and from either Utopia Kitchen or Chicago Metallic. Just show me one.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"grey\") AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Chicago Metallic\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"grey\") AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Chicago Metallic\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (color = 'black' OR color = 'grey') AND (brand = 'Utopia Kitchen' OR brand = 'Chicago Metallic') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_142", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the French Classic Tri-Ply product line manufactured in France?", "long_answer": "The French Classic Tri-Ply product line is indeed manufactured in France, which ensures high-quality construction and materials for this particular line of products.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_143", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is it safe to cook with high heat using this nonstick pan?", "long_answer": "To ensure optimal performance and extend the life of the nonstick coating, it is recommended to cook using low to medium heat with this pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_144", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Are T-fal Professional fry pans compatible with metal utensils without losing their nonstick properties?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Professional fry pan is equipped with a Prometal Pro nonstick interior that is designed to be scratch-resistant and durable, which allows for safe usage with metal utensils. The customer feedback generally confirms the pan's nonstick performance, with reports of cooking that requires minimal fat or oil. To maintain the nonstick quality, it is recommended to adhere to the provided care instructions, including cooking on low to medium heat and avoiding abrasive cleaning materials.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_110", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm a Presto fan, but I'm not made of money. What's the cheapest pan you've got from them?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Presto\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Presto\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Presto\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Presto' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_39", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is it safe to routinely wash this pan in my dishwasher without causing any harm to it?", "long_answer": "Certainly, you may confidently wash this pan in your dishwasher. Our pans are crafted using robust materials such as stainless steel and aluminum, ensuring they can endure the intense conditions of a dishwasher without compromise.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_111", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Look, I've got 30 dollars to drop on a pan. I want a decent size though, no mini pans or anything. Find me the cheapest pan that's at least the average size out there.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_145", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the pan suitable for high-heat cooking methods, like searing?", "long_answer": "The pan is regarded as suitable for high-heat cooking methods, such as searing, provided that it is adequately preheated, as confirmed by the majority of customers who have experienced its even heat distribution.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_112", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I don't want to drop more than 50 dollars and I'm only interested in Anolon. What's the cheapest pan you got from them?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND brand = \"Anolon\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND brand = \"Anolon\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND brand = 'Anolon' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_113", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm over the basic black, and I need a pan that's larger than 12 inches. What's the first colorful one you can find for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND NOT color = \"black\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND NOT color = \"black\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color NOT IN ('black') AND size > 12 ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_114", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm not the biggest fan of silver pans. Can you find me a pan that's either from Cuisinart or Anolon but absolutely not silver?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray` with asin: B000069RBK", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Anolon\") AND NOT color = \"silver\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Anolon\") AND NOT color = \"silver\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Cuisinart', 'Anolon') AND color != 'silver';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_146", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set manufactured using authentic stainless steel?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is indeed made from stainless steel, which provides durability and longevity for the cookware.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_147", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Is it advisable to wash these nonstick pans in a dishwasher?", "long_answer": "Although the pans are marketed as being dishwasher safe, it is encouraged that they be hand washed to maintain the integrity of the non-stick coating and to extend their usable life.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_115", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I often crank up my oven to 400 degrees, and I only trust Utopia Kitchen and Ozeri. What's the first pan that can handle that heat from these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Ozeri\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Ozeri\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Utopia Kitchen', 'Ozeri') AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_116", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I've had enough of Presto, no more of their pans. I need a pan that can take the heat up to 500F in the oven. What's the cheapest option you got that isn't Presto?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Presto' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_40", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Should I wish to bake an assortment of dishes often, would you suggest this particular pan?", "long_answer": "Considering your requirements for adaptable bakeware suited to daily use, I would advise against choosing this pan; its novelty shapes are intended primarily for special events and not for versatile cooking and baking tasks.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with novelty shapes are not suitable for consumers looking for multipurpose bakeware; these pans are designed more for specific occasions rather than everyday use.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "novelty shapes", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_148", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Does the pan's handle come with a loop designed for hanging storage?", "long_answer": "The pan features a handle that is designed with a loop, specifically to enable the pan to be hung for storage purposes, providing a convenient option to save space in the kitchen.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_117", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I ain't looking to break the bank here. What's the cheapest pan you have that's priced 20 dollars or less?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_118", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Look, I'm after a bargain. Find me a pan from either Cuisinart or Norpro that's less than 10 bucks, you got anything like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Norpro\") AND price < 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Norpro\") AND price < 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Cuisinart', 'Norpro') AND price < 10;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_149", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this cast iron skillet?", "long_answer": "Using metal utensils with this cast iron skillet is safe, although to maintain the integrity of the skillet's seasoning, it is advisable to opt for wooden or silicone utensils when feasible.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_119", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I don't want any of those Matfer Bourgeat's stuff. Listen, I need a pan that can handle at least 600 degrees in the oven. Find me the biggest one for that.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Matfer Bourgeat' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_120", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Listen, I'm not one to splurge and I need a pan under 20 bucks that can handle above average oven temperatures. What's your best shot?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND price <= 20 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND price <= 20 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND oven_safe_temperature > 350 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC, price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_121", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm trying to save some cash and need a pan that won't cost more than 20 bucks. It's got to be tough enough to handle oven temps above 400F. What’s the most affordable one you got that can do that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_150", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Does this pan provide even heat distribution during cooking?", "long_answer": "The heavy-gauge die-cast aluminum body of the pan ensures that heat is distributed evenly across its surface, resulting in a high level of customer satisfaction regarding its cooking performance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_151", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the non-stick functionality of the pan remain effective over time with proper care according to customer feedback?", "long_answer": "Customer feedback indicates that with proper maintenance and care, the non-stick functionality of the pan generally remains effective over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_122", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm looking to switch things up; no more Utopia Kitchen pans for me. Point me to the cheapest pan from a different brand, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Utopia Kitchen' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_123", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm looking for a big pan, preferably larger than 8 inches. But hey, it's got to be in either blue or green. What's the first one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"green\") AND size > 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"green\") AND size > 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND (color = 'blue' OR color = 'green') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_152", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "How durable is the non-stick coating on the T-fal saucepan according to customer feedback?", "long_answer": "The non-stick coating on the T-fal saucepan is generally seen as durable, providing easy cooking and cleanup experiences. However, it should be noted that customer reviews suggest that with extensive use and if improper cleaning methods are applied, the durability of the non-stick coating could be compromised.", "short_answer": "generally durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_153", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is it safe to use non-stick spray on nonstick cookware without affecting its performance?", "long_answer": "Using non-stick sprays on nonstick surfaces is discouraged as these sprays can cause the deterioration of the nonstick coating, ultimately reducing the cookware's performance. Instead, it is more advisable to use a moderate amount of oil or butter to maintain the integrity and non-stick qualities of the cookware.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_154", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "How durable is the All-Clad nonstick coating when used with proper utensils and care?", "long_answer": "The All-Clad cookware comes with a triple-layer nonstick coating which is specifically engineered to be scratch-resistant and long-lasting. When users adhere to proper maintenance guidelines, including the use of recommended utensils, the nonstick coating is expected to retain its integrity for an extended period without wearing off.", "short_answer": "durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_155", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Can the bread pan accommodate the baking of larger loaves for family gatherings?", "long_answer": "The bread pan is designed to be suitable for baking larger loaves, which is ideal when preparing bread for family gatherings or events where a larger bread size is desired.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_41", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the lid of this pan designed to be easily handled by someone with arthritis?", "long_answer": "Considering that pans with stainless steel lids tend to have some heft, they might not be the ideal choice for individuals with arthritis or those with limited hand strength. The weight of the lid can pose challenges for people with these conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a stainless steel lid are not recommended for lightweight applications where ease of handling is crucial, such as in settings that cater to individuals with limited strength or mobility as the moderate weight of the lids could pose a challenge.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "stainless steel lid", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_124", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I love to cook with pans in the oven and often crank it up to 500F. Plus, I need a pan that's larger than 8 inches. What's the cheapest one you got that can handle all that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size > 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size > 8 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size > 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_125", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm after a blue pan, just not from Anolon. Got anything like that in stock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND NOT brand = \"Anolon\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND NOT brand = \"Anolon\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color='blue' AND brand!='Anolon';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_156", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is seasoning required for ceramic non-stick pans before their initial use?", "long_answer": "Seasoning ceramic non-stick pans is not necessary before their first use; however, a minor number of users suggest that lightly oiling the pans before storing them can help maintain their non-stick quality for a more extended period.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_157", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Can the heating element of the wok be detached for cleaning purposes?", "long_answer": "The wok is designed with a detachable heating element, allowing it to be removed and enabling safe and thorough cleaning of the appliance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_158", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Would the Bialetti pan be an appropriate gift for an individual who enjoys cooking and is willing to follow its care instructions?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti pan could indeed be a suitable gift for a cooking enthusiast who is mindful and ready to adhere to the specific care instructions that come with the pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_159", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is there a warranty provided with the Stone Earth Pan?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Pan is sold with a satisfaction guarantee, and customers are advised to reach out to customer service to inquire about specific warranty details and obtain any necessary assistance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_126", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Listen, I don't want to dish out a lot of dough on a pan. Just find me a cheap one but it's gotta be safe in the oven up to at least 400 degrees, alright?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price <= 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price <= 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_127", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm in need of a larger pan, nothing less than 8 inches will do. Go dig up the cheapest one you can find that measures up!", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_160", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the pan designed to be dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The pan is created with the capability to be washed in a dishwasher, providing convenience for those who prefer this method. However, a number of customers choose to hand wash the pan in order to preserve its aesthetic and ensure the longevity of its non-stick features.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_42", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for roasting a chicken?", "long_answer": "No, this pan is not suitable for \"dry cooking\" techniques like roasting, due to its tempered glass lid, which is meant to retain moisture and could disrupt the creation of the required dry heat to roast a chicken effectively.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids are not suitable for recipes requiring “dry cooking” methods such as roasting or baking without moisture, as the lids are designed to retain moisture within the pan.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_161", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "What is the exact weight of the pan?", "long_answer": "The pan possesses a net weight of 2.6 pounds, allowing most users to use and handle it without discomfort due to its manageable heftiness.", "short_answer": "2.6 pounds", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_162", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the wok designed to enable cooking with lower quantities of oil?", "long_answer": "The wok is specifically designed for healthy stir-frying practices that typically necessitate the use of reduced amounts of oil, with its stainless-steel surface aiding in the searing of ingredients effectively without a substantial requirement for oil.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_163", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "What is the highest temperature the T-fal Professional fry pan can tolerate when used in an oven?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Professional fry pan is designed to withstand oven temperatures of up to 400 degrees Fahrenheit without sustaining damage.", "short_answer": "400 degrees Fahrenheit", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_164", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "What are the dimensions of the Copper Chef pan and how is its size suitable for serving family meals?", "long_answer": "The Copper Chef pan measures 9.5 inches square, offering up to 25% more cooking space than traditional round pans, thereby making it adequately suitable for preparing meals that can serve an entire family.", "short_answer": "9.5 inches square, very suitable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_128", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm only interested in T-fal and Presto brands, give me a pan from either of them.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Presto\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Presto\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('T-fal', 'Presto') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_129", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm looking to match my kitchen decor and only want either a black or copper pan. Can you show me one of your products in those colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"copper\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"copper\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('black', 'copper') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_165", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the pan's handle designed to remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "long_answer": "The pan incorporates stay-cool stainless handles that are specifically designed to remain cool to the touch when used for cooking on a stovetop, ensuring safer handling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_43", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Does this pan ensure uniform cooking on a conventional round burner?", "long_answer": "No, this specific pan may not yield even cooking on a standard round burner, given that its design doesn't support uniform heat distribution—a feature more readily accomplished by round pans on such burners.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with square shapes do not have a function of evenly distributing heat in rounded stovetop equipment or accommodating natural stirring motions as effortlessly as round pans.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "square", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_130", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I don't have a lot to spend but I love 'USA Pan'. What's their cheapest pan under 10 dollars?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND brand = \"USA Pan\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND brand = \"USA Pan\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'USA Pan' AND price < 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_166", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set suitable for cooking methods other than broiling?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Pan Set is designed to be versatile, allowing it to be used for a range of cooking tasks beyond just broiling, which includes roasting and reheating food items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_167", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Do the riveted handles on kitchenware create challenges when cleaning around them?", "long_answer": "Riveted handles on kitchenware are not generally considered to create significant challenges during cleaning, though a minority of users might have a preference for a smooth interior for easier maintenance.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_168", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is the pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "long_answer": "The pan includes a stainless steel induction plate, specifically designed to ensure compatibility with induction stovetops as well as facilitate even heat distribution.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_44", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "My cupboard space is quite limited; is this pan designed for convenient storage when it's not in use?", "long_answer": "Round pans may not be the most space-efficient for storage in cramped kitchens, presenting a disadvantage if optimizing every square inch is essential for you. Square or more angular pans could be more suitable if you need to fit them into a tight cupboard or shelf.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_169", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the All-Clad pan considered a good investment by customers in terms of durability and performance?", "long_answer": "Customers generally regard the All-Clad pan as a good investment because of its long-lasting durability and high-quality performance, which justify its cost over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_170", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is seasoning the pan necessary before using it for the first time?", "long_answer": "Seasoning the pan prior to its initial use is advised to enhance its non-stick properties. The suggested method is to follow the provided instructions, usually involving oil, salt, and potatoes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_131", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Look, I want nothing to do with Norpro or any green pans. What's the first product that fits that criteria?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Norpro\" AND NOT color = \"green\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Norpro\" AND NOT color = \"green\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Norpro' AND color != 'green' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_171", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the temperature on this electric wok adjustable, and are users satisfied with its performance across different heat settings?", "long_answer": "The electric wok comes equipped with adjustable temperature settings, which allows users to tailor the heat to their cooking preferences. Customer feedback indicates that it performs well at various settings, though some users mention that it tends to run hot and may require adjustments during cooking to achieve the desired results.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_132", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Look, I'm not breaking the bank here. I need a pan from either Ozeri or Copper Chef that's not gonna cost me more than 20 dollars. What you got?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND brand IN (\"Ozeri\", \"Copper Chef\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND brand IN (\"Ozeri\", \"Copper Chef\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Ozeri', 'Copper Chef') AND price <= 20;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_172", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is a cover included with the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan does not come with a cover when you purchase it.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_173", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Does the pan ensure even heat distribution to prevent hot spots during cooking?", "long_answer": "The pan is specifically designed to distribute heat evenly, facilitating uniform cooking and excellent browning, which helps to avoid the formation of hot spots that can lead to unevenly cooked food.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_45", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I recently acquired a new cooktop and intend to purchase a pan that's compatible. Are there specific features I should consider?", "long_answer": "When looking for a new pan, opt for one with a round shape since it offers greater compatibility with different cooktops, such as the latest induction units. Make sure, though, that the pan is constructed from a magnetic material if you're using an induction cooktop to guarantee seamless performance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_46", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is it possible to use this pan immediately on an induction cooktop without any prior preparation?", "long_answer": "If you're contemplating purchasing one of our aluminum or copper frying pans or skillets, be aware that they are not compatible with magnetic induction, a requirement for induction cooktops. To utilize them on these types of stoves, you would need an extra ferrous disc to facilitate the required magnetic reaction for the heating process.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_174", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Does the control panel allow for precise temperature adjustments and user-friendly interaction?", "long_answer": "Customers report that the control panel receives positive feedback, particularly highlighting the thermostat's sensitivity that provides precise temperature control. The panel also features an indicator light to show when the heating element is active. However, users should exercise some caution to prevent surpassing their preferred temperatures because of the responsive nature of the controls.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_175", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is sticking a common issue with this wok when cooking food?", "long_answer": "Sticking can occur with this wok, as reported by some users; however, it can usually be prevented by heating the wok adequately before adding oil and food, and by maintaining the appropriate temperature during cooking according to the manufacturer's instructions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_176", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is it possible to handle the cast iron skillet comfortably with just one hand?", "long_answer": "The cast iron skillet is relatively heavy, which may make it challenging for some individuals to handle comfortably with one hand. However, it is equipped with a secondary handle to aid in lifting.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_133", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm a big fan of Utopia Kitchen and Bialetti. Find me the largest pan from these two brands, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch` with asin: B00X4WQMAS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Bialetti\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Bialetti\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Bialetti\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Utopia Kitchen', 'Bialetti') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_134", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Look, I'm not trying to empty my wallet on a pan, got a 50 dollar limit here. Hook me up with the largest one I can get for that price.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_135", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm looking for a big pan, something over 10 inches. Oh, and it's gotta be grey or copper. What's the first product that comes to mind?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND (color = 'grey' OR color = 'copper') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_47", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for stir-frying, which demands rapid and uniform heat distribution?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this pan is superb for stir-fry recipes. Its round-bottomed shape is ideal for swiftly flipping ingredients, and when utilized atop a gas flame, it garners the intense and uniform temperature essential for genuine stir-frying.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with a traditional round-bottomed wok are ideally used for gas stoves that can accommodate the shape and allow for the high-heat cooking method common in Asian cuisine.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "wok", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_177", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Should oven temperature be reduced to avoid over-browning when using dark non-stick pans for baking?", "long_answer": "When using dark non-stick pans for baking, it is advisable to lower the oven temperature slightly to mitigate the risk of over-browning, according to both common practice and customer recommendations.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_178", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is this pot suitable for outdoor camping use, and what precautions should be taken during its use?", "long_answer": "This pot is suitable for outdoor and camping use. However, it is important to verify that the handle is securely attached and to ensure the pot is situated on a stable surface when cooking over open flames or an outdoor stove to avoid accidents.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_179", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the non-stick coating of this pan durable enough to withstand frequent cooking of acidic foods without damage?", "long_answer": "The non-stick coating on this pan is designed with durability in mind. However, to extend the lifespan of the non-stick surface, it is recommended to avoid frequent cooking of highly acidic foods.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_180", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Can you prevent having to manually clean the tiny holes in the pan?", "long_answer": "Users recommend lining the pan with aluminum foil, which streamlines the cleanup process and eliminates the need to clean the tiny holes by hand after each use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_136", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm not looking to spend more than 30 dollars and I want a pan that's black or grey. What's the cheapest one you got that fits what I'm looking for?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND color IN (\"black\", \"grey\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND color IN (\"black\", \"grey\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND color IN ('black', 'grey') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_137", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm not interested in All-Clad at all, so do me a favor and list the biggest pan from other brands you have available.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"All-Clad\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"All-Clad\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"All-Clad\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'All-Clad' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_181", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Can the flat-bottomed pan be used on a ceramic stovetop without issues?", "long_answer": "The saucepan has a perfectly flat bottom, which makes it compatible with ceramic stovetops and should work without any problems.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_138", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm looking to add a bit of flair to my kitchen, either with a green or silver pan. Which is the most affordable one you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"silver\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"silver\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"silver\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (color = 'green' OR color = 'silver') ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_139", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm trying to find a reliable pan from either All-Clad or Lodge that can withstand oven temperatures above 450 degrees. Show me the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black` with asin: B0170TFNXM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"Lodge\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"Lodge\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"Lodge\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('All-Clad', 'Lodge') AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_140", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I'm looking for a big black pan, like, the biggest one you got. Can you find that for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'black' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_182", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "How durable is the non-stick coating on the Green Earth Pan Set with regular use?", "long_answer": "The non-stick quality of the Green Earth Pan Set is designed to be durable, but it may degrade over time with regular use. Adhering to the care instructions and using lower heat settings can help maintain the non-stick performance for a longer period.", "short_answer": "diminishes over time", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_141", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I'm doing up my kitchen in a grey and blue theme so find me the largest pan you got in these colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"blue\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"blue\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"blue\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'blue') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_183", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the pot designed to be lightweight or does it have a heavier construction for stability?", "long_answer": "The pot strikes a balance between being lightweight for effortless handling and possessing sufficient weight to ensure stability while cooking. This is based on the general consensus among users, reflecting a mix of opinions on its heft.", "short_answer": "balanced weight", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_142", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I'm not looking to splurge, just need a pan under 20 dollars. It's gotta be either copper or blue though, can you find me one?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND color IN (\"copper\", \"blue\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND color IN (\"copper\", \"blue\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND (color = 'copper' OR color = 'blue');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_184", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Does the fry pan's stainless-steel handle remain cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "long_answer": "The fry pan's contoured stainless-steel handle is crafted to stay cooler when touched during stovetop use; however, it may still become hot under certain conditions, such as prolonged use over high heat or when placed in the oven.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_48", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Can this pan be used to roast a chicken?", "long_answer": "No, because this pan includes a tempered glass lid, it isn't suitable for \"dry cooking\" methods like roasting. These lids are intended to hold in moisture, potentially disrupting the necessary dry heat required for properly roasting a chicken.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids are not suitable for recipes requiring “dry cooking” methods such as roasting or baking without moisture, as the lids are designed to retain moisture within the pan.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_185", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is this pot designed to be compatible with a small burner?", "long_answer": "This pot is specifically designed for versatility, allowing it to be used effectively on a small burner without any issues.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_186", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does the handle of this cookware retain heat during use, making it hot to the touch?", "long_answer": "Users have reported instances where the handle becomes hot after being used for extended periods. To ensure safety and comfort, it is recommended to utilize a silicon handle cover or wear heat-resistant gloves while handling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_143", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I can't stand anything from Chicago Metallic and I don't have more than 20 dollars to spare. Can you find me the largest pan from any other brand within my budget?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND price < 20 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND price < 20 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND price < 20 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND brand != 'Chicago Metallic' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_187", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does purchasing this saucepan on Amazon.com come with a discount coupon?", "long_answer": "When buying this saucepan from Amazon.com, there is metadata indicating the availability of a 5% discount coupon. Nonetheless, it's important for potential buyers to verify the latest information on the product page since promotional offers can change periodically.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_144", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm torn between ZWILLING J.A. Henckels and All-Clad for my pan purchase. Tell me the cheapest one from these brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"All-Clad\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"All-Clad\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"All-Clad\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('ZWILLING J.A. Henckels', 'All-Clad') ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_49", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Are there any health risks linked to the materials utilized in this pan?", "long_answer": "Certainly, when considering a grill pan featuring a non-stick surface, there are potential health risks tied to the components involved. Non-stick coatings may have substances that raise health concerns if they leach into the food, especially under high temperatures or when the pan's coating is damaged.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with non-stick coatings fail to meet the requirements for environmentally conscious consumers who are concerned about the potential for chemical components entering their food or the environment.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "grill pan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_188", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is it necessary to season the cast iron skillet before its initial use?", "long_answer": "Even though the cast iron skillet arrives pre-seasoned, it is advisable to season it yourself before using it for the first time to guarantee a non-stick surface. Regular maintenance through seasoning after each use is also recommended to preserve the non-stick quality.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_145", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I ain't throwing money around and I need to be able to slam this thing in a 400F oven. What's the cheapest pan you got that can handle that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 \nORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_189", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Can the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan be used on induction cooktops or in the oven?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti 12-inch saute pan is designed to be compatible with various types of conventional stove tops, such as electric, gas, ceramic, and glass. Nevertheless, it should be noted that this cookware is not compatible with induction cooktops and is not designed for oven use.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_146", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm a fan of T-fal and I do a lot of high-heat cooking. Can you track down a pan from them that can withstand at least 600 degrees in the oven?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'T-fal' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_50", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is this pan suitable for direct placement on charcoal during a barbecue?", "long_answer": "Using this saucepan directly on charcoal or any similar high-heat source is not recommended, as it is not designed to withstand the temperatures of open flames, and doing so could result in damage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan lack the capability to be used on open fires or grills without risking damage to their handles or materials that are not designed to withstand such direct, intense heat.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_190", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen cast iron skillet compatible with all types of stovetops?", "long_answer": "The Utopia Kitchen cast iron skillet is designed to be versatile and can be utilized on a range of heat sources. It works on induction, ceramic, electric, and gas stovetops, and is additionally safe to use in the oven.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_147", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm a big fan of ZWILLING J.A. Henckels products. Show me the biggest pan they make.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_191", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Does food cook evenly in the pans from this cookware set?", "long_answer": "The pans in this cookware set are reported by customers to provide even heating and perform well on different heat sources, resulting in meals that are cooked evenly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_192", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro broiler pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "long_answer": "Customers have reported successful use of the Norpro broil/roast pan set on induction stovetops, particularly when making gravy, indicating its compatibility with this type of cooking surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_148", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm in the mood for some fancy French cookware, but only if it's gray. Give me the biggest pan you've got from Matfer Bourgeat.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND color = \"grey\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND color = \"grey\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND color = \"grey\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Matfer Bourgeat' AND color = 'grey' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_193", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the Cuisinart French Classic Pan available for purchase within a cookware set?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart French Classic Tri-Ply series offers cookware sets which may contain various types of pans, including a crepe pan and others that might align with your culinary needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_149", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm a big fan of Copper Chef, but money isn't growing on trees. Find me their most affordable pan, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Copper Chef\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Copper Chef\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Copper Chef' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_194", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is it possible to fry an egg in this pan without it sticking?", "long_answer": "Eggs and other foods can be fried in the pan without sticking, as long as the pan is preheated properly and the care instructions are adhered to during use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_150", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I need a pan that can handle a high heat, over 400 degrees, and I only want it in black or silver. Show me the biggest one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"silver\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"silver\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"silver\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND (color = 'black' OR color = 'silver') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_195", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this non-stick saucepan?", "long_answer": "It is not advisable to use metal utensils with this non-stick saucepan as doing so could damage the non-stick surface. To ensure the longevity of the pot, it is best to use wooden, plastic, or silicone utensils.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_196", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the 12-inch pan designed to accommodate the cooking needs of singles and smaller families?", "long_answer": "The 12-inch pan is versatile and provides sufficient space for cooking a range of dishes, making it an appropriate choice for individuals, couples, or small families looking for everyday convenience in their kitchenware.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_151", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I do a lot of cooking, and I need a big pan that can handle some serious heat. Give me your biggest heat-resistant pan that's over 10 inches.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC, size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_197", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch pan oven-safe?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti 12-inch pan is not intended for oven use because the materials and design of the handle make it unsuitable for such conditions. It is explicitly created for use on the stovetop.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_198", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is it safe to clean this pan with metal scouring pads?", "long_answer": "Metal scouring pads should not be used on this pan as they can damage the non-stick surface, which is why cleaning with a soft sponge or cloth is recommended to maintain the pan's condition.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_51", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Will the finish on this pan deteriorate if it goes through frequent dishwashing cycles?", "long_answer": "No, frequent dishwashing won't diminish the finish. The pans are crafted from durable, coated, or anodized metals designed to withstand the rigors of dishwashing and retain their high-quality finish.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_199", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is there a warranty included with the purchase of this saucepan?", "long_answer": "The saucepan includes a lifetime warranty that covers any defects, ensuring the product's longevity and customer satisfaction.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_200", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is the saucepan suitable for high-temperature cooking on the stovetop without damaging its nonstick coating?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is capable of being used on a stovetop and is designed to distribute heat evenly. However, in order to preserve the integrity of the nonstick coating, it is advised to refrain from using extremely high heat during cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_201", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is a 10-inch pan appropriate for cooking meals for a single individual?", "long_answer": "A 10-inch pan is indeed suitable for cooking meals for one person, as it provides an ample cooking surface for dishes such as crepes and pancakes, thereby making it a flexible cooking utensil for individual meal preparation.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_152", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I want a decent sized pan but I'm steering clear of Utopia Kitchen's stuff. Give me your best pan that's over 10 inches.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND NOT brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND NOT brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND brand <> 'Utopia Kitchen' ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_153", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I ain't dropping more than 20 dollars, and I only trust All-Clad or USA Pan brands. Give me the pan that can take the highest oven heat within my budget and preferred brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"USA Pan\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"USA Pan\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"USA Pan\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND (brand = 'All-Clad' OR brand = 'USA Pan') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_52", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Can the pan's lid retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "long_answer": "Over time, the tempered glass lid of the pan might lose its non-toxic properties. Should the coating on the handle or the rim of the lid begin to deteriorate, it could lead to undesirable interactions with your food, potentially affecting the non-toxic quality of the cooking space.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids fail to meet the requirements for completely non-reactive cooking conditions, especially if any sort of coating on the lid's handle or edges were to degrade and interact with the food.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_202", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is this fry pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "long_answer": "This fry pan is specifically designed to be compatible with gas, electric, and ceramic glass cooktops as indicated by the product details. However, there is no explicit mention of compatibility with induction cooktops in the product metadata, suggesting that the fry pan may not be suitable for that type of cooktop.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_154", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm hunting for a pan, either blue or copper colored, but it's got to be from Norpro or Tramontina. Give me one option that checks these boxes.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") AND brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"Tramontina\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") AND brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"Tramontina\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('blue', 'copper') AND brand IN ('Norpro', 'Tramontina') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_203", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "What is the maximum number of people you can prepare a meal for using this electric wok?", "long_answer": "Based on customer feedback, the electric wok can be used to cook meals that serve approximately 6 to 7 people, though the actual number may vary depending on individual portion sizes.", "short_answer": "6-7", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_204", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the pot come with a lid that seals tightly during cooking?", "long_answer": "The pot includes a lid that is designed to fit well and seal during cooking. However, there have been reports from some customers about the lid not sealing completely. In such cases, customers are advised to contact customer service for a replacement or additional support.", "short_answer": "generally yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_205", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "How much does the Lodge Skillet weigh, and does it require two hands to handle it safely?", "long_answer": "The Lodge Skillet, being made of cast iron, is heavier compared to other materials used for cookware. It is designed with two handles to aid in lifting. Handling the skillet, particularly when it is hot, typically necessitates using both hands, as well as pot holders for safety and to manage its substantial weight.", "short_answer": "two hands", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_206", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "What specific material is the included spatula with the wok made of?", "long_answer": "The spatula included with the wok is made of wood and features a long handle, making it particularly suitable for use with the wok.", "short_answer": "wooden", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_207", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is it necessary to use oil or butter to prevent food from sticking on this nonstick cookware?", "long_answer": "The nonstick surface of the cookware is engineered to allow food to release easily without sticking. However, adding a small amount of oil or non-stick spray might enhance cooking results and help maintain the cookware's nonstick qualities over time, as the nonstick effectiveness may diminish with usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_208", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan compatible with induction stovetops?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti 12-inch saute pan is designed to be used on various types of stovetops including electric, gas, ceramic, and glass. However, it is not compatible with induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_53", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Might the pan's shape render it difficult to stow in a drawer alongside other kitchen tools?", "long_answer": "The circular design of the pan may not fit seamlessly within the confines of rectangular drawers, which could make it more challenging to store with other kitchen tools. Opting for a pan with a shape that matches the dimensions of your storage will likely aid in conserving space and maintaining order.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_155", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Look, I got a max of 50 dollars and I need a pan that can survive in an oven temperature of at least 400F. Now, can you show me the best match for that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY price DESC, oven_safe_temperature ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_156", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm not a fan of ZWILLING J.A. Henckels and I don't want to dish out more than 50 dollars. What's the largest pan you have that matches my criteria?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND price <= 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND price <= 50 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND price <= 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_157", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I’m looking for a big pan, something larger than 10 inches. It has be a Bialetti though. See if you can find one for me.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal` with asin: B000S6I4ZE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND brand = \"Bialetti\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND brand = \"Bialetti\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND brand = 'Bialetti';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_158", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I cook a lot in the oven and I need a pan that can handle at least 500F. And by the way, I'm not planning on spending more than the average price. So what's my best option here?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_54", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Can the lid of this pan retain its non-toxic properties over time?", "long_answer": "Over time, the pan's tempered glass lid might not retain its non-toxic properties. Should the coating on the handle or along the edges begin to deteriorate, this could lead to undesirable reactions with your food, potentially affecting the non-toxicity of your cooking space.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids fail to meet the requirements for completely non-reactive cooking conditions, especially if any sort of coating on the lid's handle or edges were to degrade and interact with the food.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_159", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I ain't paying more than 10 bucks for a pan. Dig up the cheapest black or blue one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('black', 'blue') AND price <= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_209", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is the pan safe to use at high oven temperatures up to 450F / 232C?", "long_answer": "The pan is indeed oven safe and is designed to withstand temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit or 232 degrees Celsius. However, it is important to note that the pan should not be used under a broiler, as this is beyond its intended use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_160", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm eyeing both Anolon and Ozeri but my wallet's crying out for mercy - it can just stretch out to 20 bucks. Give me the cheapest pan from these brands.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Ozeri\") AND price < 20 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Ozeri\") AND price < 20 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Anolon', 'Ozeri') AND price <= 20 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_161", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I want a pan that can take some real heat and looks fancy too. Got any in green or copper that can handle more than 450°F? Show me the best option.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"copper\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"copper\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('green', 'copper') AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_210", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan appropriate for baking gluten-free bread?", "long_answer": "The USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan is explicitly designed to accommodate gluten-free bread recipes. It features a non-stick surface, which facilitates the easy release of bread after baking. However, it is important to note that adjustments to the recipe might be required, as gluten-free dough can have different properties compared to traditional wheat dough.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_211", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the pan effective for cooking with low-fat methods without causing food to stick?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to handle low-fat cooking effectively; however, it is advisable to use a minimal amount of fat to prevent sticking and achieve the desired culinary results.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_212", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is the saucepan dishwasher safe according to the manufacturer's recommendations?", "long_answer": "The manufacturer advises against using a dishwasher to clean this saucepan, recommending hand-washing instead in order to preserve its quality and its nonstick characteristics.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_213", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the saucepan suitable for preparing delicate sauces and reductions?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed with heat distribution properties and a solid construction that make it suitable for cooking techniques requiring precise temperature control such as slow simmers, rolling boils, and reductions, thus making it ideal for delicate sauces.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_162", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Look mate, I don't want anything from Chicago Metallic and I need the pan to handle at least 500 F. Show me the biggest pan you got that meets these needs.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Chicago Metallic' \nAND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 \nORDER BY size DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_214", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Do customers find that the finished Madeleines have well-defined shell shapes?", "long_answer": "The overall customer satisfaction is high with regard to the definition of the shell shapes on the finished Madeleines, with some customers noting that applying adequate greasing can enhance the clarity of the shell pattern imprints.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_215", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the pan dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The pan is designated as dishwasher safe; however, to maximize the longevity of the nonstick surface and achieve the best results, it is advisable to hand wash the pan using non-abrasive cleansers and liquid dishwashing soap.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_216", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is the pan considered to have a good weight and balance for handling and maneuverability?", "long_answer": "The pan is crafted with a thick aluminum core that facilitates even distribution of heat. It is considered to be nicely weighted, offering a sense of quality and ease of handling and maneuverability, as indicated by customer feedback.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_55", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is this pan compatible with various stove types?", "long_answer": "Sauté pans constructed from materials such as copper require a magnetic layer to ensure universal compatibility with all heat sources, including gas and electric stoves, as well as induction cooktops. Lacking this characteristic, their usage would be restricted to specific kinds of heat sources.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with certain materials like copper are not suitable for induction cooktops unless they have been specially designed with a magnetic layer, which might limit their universality across different heat sources.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saute pan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_163", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm only interested in silver pans from either Copper Chef or Cuisinart. What's the first one you got in stock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Cuisinart\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Cuisinart\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'silver' AND (brand = 'Copper Chef' OR brand = 'Cuisinart') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_217", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is the Stone Earth Pan lighter than traditional cast iron pans?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Pan is designed to offer a substantial feel akin to heavy-gauge cookware, yet it is significantly lighter than traditional cast iron pans, facilitating easier handling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_164", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I got a thing about Matfer Bourgeat, don't ask. What other pan brands do you have? Show me any one of them.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Matfer Bourgeat' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_165", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm after a grey pan that can resist temperatures above 500F. Which is the largest one you got in stock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'grey' AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_218", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Are the riveted silicone handles of the cookware designed to maintain a cool temperature during cooking for a secure grip?", "long_answer": "The riveted silicone handles on the cookware are specifically designed to remain cool to the touch, which ensures a secure and comfortable grip while cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_166", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Listen, I've got around 30 dollars to shell out for a pan. Find me the one that can survive the highest oven temperature for that price.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_219", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is the lid of the skillet designed to create a tight seal when placed on top?", "long_answer": "The lid of the skillet is specifically designed to fit tightly onto the skillet, incorporating tips on its underside that serve to improve basting and the even distribution of moisture throughout the cooking process.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_167", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm a big fan of Anolon and Matfer Bourgeat pans. Can you tell me which one of their products can withstand the highest oven temperatures?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Anolon', 'Matfer Bourgeat') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_168", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I need a pan that can handle extreme heat, over 600°F, and don't show me anything from Cuisinart. What's the first thing you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT brand = \"Cuisinart\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT brand = \"Cuisinart\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND brand != 'Cuisinart' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_169", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm after a big pan, in grey or silver should do fine. Can you pull up the biggest one in those colors for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"silver\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"silver\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"silver\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'silver') \nORDER BY size DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_56", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm in search of cookware that can aid in quicker meal preparation. Do pans featuring glass lids contribute to a faster cooking experience?", "long_answer": "Pans featuring tempered glass lids provide the benefit of allowing you to monitor your food during cooking, yet they might not be the optimal choice for speedier meal preparation. Owing to possibly less efficient heat retention, these pans can marginally increase the cooking duration when compared to pans equipped with solid, weightier lids that better conserve heat.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids are not recommended for users looking for the most energy-efficient cookware, as they might not insulate heat as well as some heavier, more solid lid options, potentially leading to slightly increased energy use over time.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_57", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I am in search of a multifunctional pan capable of both simmering soups and handling frying tasks. Would this be an appropriate choice for my needs?", "long_answer": "A saucepan, with its tall sides and design optimized for liquid cooking, is ideal for simmering soups and sauces. However, it is not the best choice for frying. For frying purposes, a pan with lower sides that can withstand direct, intense heat is preferable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan cannot be used for high-heat searing or frying due to their high sides and design focusing more on liquid-based cooking methods.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_220", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Can this skillet be used for both frying and baking?", "long_answer": "The skillet is designed to be versatile, allowing it to be used effectively for frying, as well as for baking. This versatility means the skillet is suitable for various cooking methods, including sautéing, among others.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_170", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I'm a big fan of Copper Chef and USA Pan. Get me the cheapest pan from either of these brands, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"USA Pan\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"USA Pan\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"USA Pan\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Copper Chef', 'USA Pan') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_221", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Should the pan be expected to emit odors the first time it is used?", "long_answer": "It is not uncommon for the pan to emit odors during the inaugural uses. This typically results from residues left over from the manufacturing process. The odors are expected to subside after the pan is used a few times and washed properly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_222", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does the heavy-gauge aluminum bottom construction of this pan provide even heating?", "long_answer": "The pan is constructed with a heavy-gauge aluminum bottom, which according to reports from the majority of customers, facilitates quick and even heating, leading to a satisfactory cooking experience.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_223", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set made of durable material?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is constructed from stainless steel, which is known for its durability. Nevertheless, some users have provided feedback indicating that the pan set is lighter in weight and does not meet their expectations in terms of sturdiness.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_171", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm so over silver pans. Find me the cheapest one you've got that's any color but that.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color <> 'silver' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_172", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm in the market for a new pan - either blue or black. What's the cheapest option you got in those colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"black\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"black\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"black\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('blue', 'black') ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_224", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Does the 10 1/4\" Lodge cast iron skillet effectively reduce oil splatter when frying chicken?", "long_answer": "The 10 1/4\" Lodge cast iron skillet, with its deeper walls, is designed to help reduce oil splatter when frying chicken, as noted by customers who experience less spatter compared to other pans.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_225", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Can the Presto 5900 wok be recommended for professional or commercial kitchen environments?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 wok is primarily designed and optimized for home use, meaning it's well-suited for residential kitchens. It may not possess the necessary features or the durability that is typically demanded in professional or commercial kitchen settings, where usage is more intense and frequent.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_226", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is this pot suitable for cooking rice with minimal steam release?", "long_answer": "The pot is capable of cooking rice, but it has a vented lid that releases more steam than pots with tighter lids typically used for specialized rice cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_227", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is the ZWILLING Spirit 8\" Thermolon Fry Pan compatible with an induction cooktop?", "long_answer": "The ZWILLING Spirit 8\" Thermolon Fry Pan is designed to be used on various types of cooktops, including induction. This makes it a versatile cookware choice for different cooking methods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_58", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Will this pan allow my food to cook evenly on all types of stoves?", "long_answer": "Our frying pans and skillets, crafted from aluminum or copper, are renowned for their superior heat conductivity, ensuring uniform cooking. But be aware when using an induction stove: these materials lack inherent magnetic properties, making them unsuitable by default. Your cooking efficiency could be reduced without a ferrous plate to enable induction compatibility.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_173", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I've got this thing for blue, so I need a blue pan. But I ain't a millionaire, so show me your cheapest option.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_59", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Could the pan rust if it's not maintained correctly?", "long_answer": "Indeed, lacking dishwasher-safe features, these pans may be susceptible to rust unless they are properly maintained with consistent seasoning, which aids in guarding against corrosion and preserving the pan's integrity.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" do not have a function of self-maintenance and will need regular seasoning (for cast iron or carbon steel) or polishing (for aesthetic reasons) to maintain their best condition.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_60", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "If I don't conscientiously maintain this pan, will its appearance alter as time goes by?", "long_answer": "Indeed, because the pan is not dishwasher safe, it might need polishing to maintain its appearance. Furthermore, routine upkeep such as seasoning, based on the pan's material, is necessary to prevent its aesthetic degradation.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" do not have a function of self-maintenance and will need regular seasoning (for cast iron or carbon steel) or polishing (for aesthetic reasons) to maintain their best condition.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_174", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I'm not breaking the bank for a pan but I don't want to skimp on quality either. What's your cheapest pan that can handle more heat than the average?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_175", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I got enough grey kitchenware as it is, and I need something bigger than 8 inches. What's the first non-grey pan bigger than 8 inches you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"grey\" AND size > 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"grey\" AND size > 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color <> 'grey' AND size > 8 ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_176", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm into big pans and only trust brands like USA Pan and Matfer Bourgeat. Give me the biggest pan you've got from either of those brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('USA Pan', 'Matfer Bourgeat') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_228", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "How can the saucepan be maintained to look like new after multiple uses?", "long_answer": "Proper care, including the use of stove top polish, as mentioned by customers, can help in maintaining the saucepan's like-new appearance even after multiple uses.", "short_answer": "stove top polish", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_61", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is this pan capable of withstanding high-temperature cooking such as searing a steak?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this aluminum pan is not ideal for high-temperature cooking like searing steak. It does not possess the required heat resilience for these tasks and might not retain its form under extreme temperatures that stainless steel or cast iron pans can tolerate.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's lack of high heat tolerance lack the capability to withstand searing and broiling applications that require maintaining structural integrity at very high temperatures, unlike cookware made of materials like stainless steel or cast iron.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_229", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the interior of this saucepan designed to be non-stick?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is equipped with a high-quality non-stick interior which facilitates effortless cooking and simplifies the cleaning process.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_230", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered fry pan designed for high-heat cooking and suitable for searing meats?", "long_answer": "The All-Clad Stainless 41106 10-inch covered frying pan is specifically designed to withstand high-heat cooking, which is optimal for searing meats to produce a deep rich flavor and color.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_231", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it possible to cook in the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan without using oil, and will the food not stick to the pan?", "long_answer": "The Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan comes equipped with a non-stick ceramic coating which allows cooking with little to no oil, and when the pan is used as per the provided instructions, food is unlikely to stick to its surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_177", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm looking for a decent sized pan from either Anolon or Chicago Metallic that can handle some serious heat. What's the product with the highest oven safe temperature you've got in stock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Chicago Metallic\") AND size >= 8 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Chicago Metallic\") AND size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Chicago Metallic\") AND size >= 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Anolon', 'Chicago Metallic') \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_178", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm not really a fan of silver cookware, give me a pan of any other color. What's your top pick?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'silver' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_232", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is a Lifetime Limited Warranty included with the purchase of the pot?", "long_answer": "The pot includes a Lifetime Limited Warranty, as stated in the product description, ensuring protection against potential manufacturing defects over the product's lifetime.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_62", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I sometimes favor cooking with a grill. Would this pan be suitable for such a cooking technique?", "long_answer": "As the pan in question is a saucepan, it is advisable not to use it on a grill. The direct and intense heat of a grill may damage areas of the pan that are not designed to tolerate such extreme temperatures.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan lack the capability to be used on open fires or grills without risking damage to their handles or materials that are not designed to withstand such direct, intense heat.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_63", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for evenly searing meat?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the sauté pan is engineered to offer excellent heat distribution and retention, essential for delivering uniform cooking outcomes. This is particularly important for activities such as searing meat, where consistent heat is key to obtaining the ideal crust.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a purely aesthetic design fail to meet the requirements for professional culinary tasks if they do not possess the necessary heat distribution and retention characteristics essential for consistent cooking results.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saute pan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_233", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the pot considered lightweight by customers?", "long_answer": "Customers have reported that the pot has a heavier weight than they expected, suggesting it might not meet the definition of lightweight for all users, potentially affecting its convenience when it comes to carrying or maneuvering.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_234", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it safe to leave the Copper Chef pan on high heat for an extended period without causing damage?", "long_answer": "The Copper Chef non-stick pan is not designed to withstand very high heat for long durations. Extended exposure to high heat can damage the pan's non-stick surface. Medium heat is recommended for most cooking tasks to preserve the non-stick coating.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_235", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the pot come with a pouring spout and built-in strainer in the lid?", "long_answer": "The pot is designed with a pouring spout, also referred to as a pouring lip, to facilitate convenient pouring. Additionally, the lid of the pot incorporates a built-in strainer feature, which customers have found to be a practical and useful aspect of the pot.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_236", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is the saucepan compatible with glass cooktops without causing any damage?", "long_answer": "This saucepan is confirmed to work well on glass cooktops by customer reports and will not cause damage when it is used according to the manufacturer's guidelines.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_179", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm gonna be using this pan in a pretty damn hot oven - needs to withstand at least 450F. Dig out the cheapest one you've got from ZWILLING J.A. Henckels for me.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' and oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_180", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I don't have time to browse, just tell me the first pan you have from either Lodge or Matfer Bourgeat.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Lodge', 'Matfer Bourgeat') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_181", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm all about saving money and adding a little style to my kitchen, so find me the largest copper or green pan you got for under 10 dollars.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND color IN (\"copper\", \"green\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND color IN (\"copper\", \"green\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND color IN (\"copper\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('copper', 'green') AND price < 10 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_237", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Can the crepe pan effectively sear meats, achieving caramelization?", "long_answer": "Users have reported that the crepe pan is indeed capable of conducting heat efficiently enough to achieve excellent caramelization and searing on meats, attesting to its ability to deliver a good sear.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_238", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Does the Green Earth Frying Pan set maintain its non-stick functionality as intended?", "long_answer": "The Green Earth Frying Pan set features a unique honeycomb textured cooking surface intended to provide non-stick cooking performance. The vast majority of customers report effective non-stick results and ease of cleaning. However, there have been instances where customers notice a decline in the non-stick quality after extended use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_182", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I ain't trying to spend above 50 dollars and I want a silver pan. What's the cheapest one you have that fits my requirements?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND color = \"silver\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND color = \"silver\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND color = 'silver' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_183", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I need a decent sized pan from either Presto or Ozeri that can handle some heat, but don't show me the tiny ones. What's the one with the highest oven-safe temperature you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Ozeri\") AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Ozeri\") AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Ozeri\") AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Presto', 'Ozeri') \nAND size > 10 \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_184", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm doing some heavy cooking and need a large pan that can take heat over 500°F. Can you find me the one that fits this description?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND size > 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND size > 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_185", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm a fan of copper pans, but I've had lousy experiences with Norpro. Get me a different brand, would ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND NOT brand = \"Norpro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND NOT brand = \"Norpro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' AND brand != 'Norpro';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_64", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is this pan compatible with my induction cooktop?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the pan is compatible with an induction stovetop, provided it is constructed of a magnetic material. Its round shape enhances its suitability for various types of stovetops, induction ones included.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_239", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Does the non-stick quality of the pan remain effective over time with proper maintenance?", "long_answer": "The non-stick feature of the pan can remain durable over time if the pan is cared for correctly. This includes hand washing, avoiding abrasive utensils, and periodically seasoning the pan to preserve its non-stick properties.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_65", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Can this pan retain its new look over time without requiring much effort from me?", "long_answer": "Regrettably, copper pans won't retain their fresh appearance without a bit of effort from you. Regular polishing is necessary, and they need to be cleaned gently to avoid tarnishing, thereby maintaining their beauty and practicality.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with copper material do not have the function of being low-maintenance; they require regular polishing and gentle cleaning to prevent tarnishing and maintain their appearance and performance.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "copper", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_240", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Does the pan's design result in a reduced usable surface area compared to the total pan size?", "long_answer": "The design with a wide brim and slanted sides results in a usable surface area that is smaller than what the total pan size might suggest.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_241", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is the Copper Chef pan compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The Copper Chef pan features a stainless steel induction plate, which ensures its compatibility with various stove types, including gas, electric, ceramic, and specifically induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_242", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is there a pour spout on this model of skillet?", "long_answer": "This specific model of skillet does not come equipped with a pour spout. Individuals in search of this feature should explore alternative models by Lodge that offer pour spouts.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_243", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is there a warranty included with the purchase of the Cuisinart crepe pan?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart crepe pan includes a lifetime warranty, which guarantees the pan's durability and reliable performance over its lifespan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_186", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I don't have money to burn, but I trust Utopia Kitchen and Norpro when it comes to pans. Can you find me the cheapest one they offer?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch` with asin: B00X4WQMAS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Norpro\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Norpro\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Norpro\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Utopia Kitchen', 'Norpro') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_187", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I’ve got a thing for silver or blue pans from either Norpro or Utopia Kitchen. Do you have one in stock?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"blue\") AND brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"blue\") AND brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (color = 'silver' OR color = 'blue') AND (brand = 'Norpro' OR brand = 'Utopia Kitchen');"}}
{"id": "search_qa_188", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "The pans I use go in the oven a lot, and I need something that can handle at least 600F, just no grey ones, okay? And I'm not made of money so hit me with the cheapest option please.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT color = \"grey\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT color = \"grey\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT color = \"grey\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND color != 'grey' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_189", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm looking for a green pan and I don't want to shell out more than 50 bucks for it. Show me the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND color = \"green\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND color = \"green\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'green' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_190", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Avoid showing me anything from Utopia Kitchen. I want the biggest pan you have that's at least 12 inches.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" AND size >= 12 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" AND size >= 12 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Utopia Kitchen' AND size >= 12 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_244", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is the pan suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be compatible with various types of cooktops, including gas, induction, ceran, halogen, and electric cooktops, allowing for versatile usage across different cooking surfaces.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_245", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Do the pans require seasoning before their first use for optimal performance?", "long_answer": "While seasoning the pans with oil is not an absolute necessity for every user, some customers report that doing so enhances the pans’ performance.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_191", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm all about size when it comes to my pans, and I'm a loyal Ozeri customer. Find me the biggest pan above 12 inches from Ozeri.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand = 'Ozeri' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_246", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Can the Stone Earth Pan by Ozeri be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Pan by Ozeri is designed to be dishwasher safe. However, to preserve its non-stick properties and extend its lifespan, hand-washing with mild detergent is advised, as recommended by most customers who also report that it's easy to clean manually.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_247", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is it required to season the pan prior to each use?", "long_answer": "There is no need to season the pan fully each time it is used. However, applying a light coat of oil after cleaning is beneficial in preserving its non-stick qualities.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_66", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is it safe to use metal spatulas or forks with this pan without causing any harm?", "long_answer": "Using metal utensils on pans with sensitive non-stick coatings can cause scratches and impair the surface. We advise opting for wooden, silicone, or plastic utensils when handling this specific frying pan to preserve its non-stick quality.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with delicate non-stick coatings cannot be used for cooking methods that involve metal utensils or very high heat, to avoid damaging the surface.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_248", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is a ceramic non-stick pan suitable for searing meat?", "long_answer": "This type of pan is not recommended for searing meat, as there are better options available, such as carbon steel, cast iron, or stainless steel cookware, which are more suited for high-temperature cooking required for searing.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_192", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I need a pan, but it has to be able to withstand high oven temperatures of at least 600F and has to cost me no more than 10 dollars. Can you find me one?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND price <= 10;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_193", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm a big fan of Utopia Kitchen and I've got a thing for big pans. What's your biggest pan from them? Must be at least a 10-incher.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch` with asin: B00X4WQMAS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" AND size >= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" AND size >= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Utopia Kitchen' AND size >= 10 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_194", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm not a fan of green and I need a pan that's bigger than 10 inches. What's the first option you've got that matches that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND size > 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND size > 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND color != 'green' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_249", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Can the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set accommodate cooking for a larger family?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is designed primarily for individual servings or meals that serve two people, implying that it is not suitable for cooking larger family-sized meals.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_250", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Should I expect the ceramic coating on cookware to chip and wear over time?", "long_answer": "Normal use of ceramic-coated cookware may lead to some chipping and wearing, but this can be mitigated by using lower heat settings and avoiding metal utensils and abrasive cleaning materials to prolong the coating's life.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_251", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are these pans safe to use for baking in the oven?", "long_answer": "Unless the manufacturer confirms oven compatibility, the pans should only be used on the stovetop to ensure their longevity, as the description does not explicitly state that they are oven-safe.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_195", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I need a grey pan for my new kitchen theme that can hold up to high temps. Give me your highest oven-safe temperature pan, alright?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'grey' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_196", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Listen, I can't be burning money on pans. Get me the cheapest pan that can handle over 400 degrees in the oven, but don't cross the $30 limit.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND price < 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND price < 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND price <= 30 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_252", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the saucepan come with a tight-fitting lid that aids in cooking by sealing in moisture and nutrients?", "long_answer": "The saucepan includes a Flavor Lock Lid designed to create a tight seal, which helps to retain moisture and nutrients during the cooking process, thereby contributing to healthier and more flavorful food.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_197", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm cooking big meals these days and need a pan larger than 8 inches. Find me the one that can take the highest oven temperature.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_198", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm cooking up a storm in a hot oven, and I need a green pan that can withstand more than 500 F. Don't make me a broke man. Find me the most affordable one.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND color = \"green\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND color = \"green\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'green' AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_199", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I got a specific color preference. Either grey or blue will do for me. Now, could you get me the least expensive pan in these colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"blue\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"blue\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"blue\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'blue') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_253", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Should the pan be washed and seasoned before its initial use?", "long_answer": "Before using the pan for the first time, it should be washed. Additionally, to enhance its performance, it is advisable to season the pan following the provided instructions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_67", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is this pan suitable for recipes that begin on the stovetop and subsequently require oven baking?", "long_answer": "Certainly, a sauté pan's versatility accommodates dishes that need stovetop preparation followed by oven completion. Its straight sides and considerable depth offer sufficient space and help avoid spills while transferring and cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a sauté design are ideally used for cooking methods that involve liquids, such as simmering sauces or shallow frying, due to their straight sides that help contain the contents.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saute pan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_254", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the T-fal Professional line include different skillet sizes beyond this 10-inch model?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Professional line features a selection of skillets in multiple sizes, providing options that include both smaller and larger pans than the 10-inch model to accommodate various cooking requirements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_255", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is cast iron cookware compatible with induction stovetops?", "long_answer": "Cast iron cookware can be used on induction stovetops because of the material's ferrous nature, which responds well to the magnetic field created by induction burners.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_200", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I ain't looking to shell out more than 20 dollars and I only trust Copper Chef and Bialetti brands. Get me a pan from one of those brands that won't clear out my wallet.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Bialetti\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Bialetti\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Copper Chef', 'Bialetti') AND price <= 20;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_256", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is seasoning required before using the nonstick pan for the first time?", "long_answer": "Seasoning the pan according to the manufacturer's instructions before its initial use is advised to enhance the nonstick performance of the surface and to prolong the pan's lifespan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_257", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is the cast iron skillet susceptible to rusting after being washed with water?", "long_answer": "The cast iron skillet is prone to rusting if it is not dried promptly post-washing. It's crucial to dry the skillet thoroughly and then apply a light coating of oil to act as a protective layer against rust.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_258", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set large enough to cook meals for more than two people?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is specifically designed for one to two people, suggesting that its size is not sufficiently large to prepare meals for more than two individuals at a single time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_201", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I need a pan that can take the heat, specifically one that's good for 600°F or more. Just stick to 'Lodge' or 'T-fal' brands though, and you better find me the cheapest one.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"T-fal\") AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"T-fal\") AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"T-fal\") AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Lodge', 'T-fal') AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_202", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I like to crank up the heat when I'm cooking and I need a big pan. What's the cheapest pan you have that can withstand over 400F and is at least 12 inches?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size >= 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size >= 12 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size >= 12 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_68", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm fond of stir-frying frequently; is this pan suitable for that method of cooking?", "long_answer": "When stir-frying, which requires vigorous movement of ingredients, a round pan is more appropriate. Rectangular-shaped pans are not well-suited for high-heat techniques such as stir-frying, since they do not facilitate the same ease of tossing and shifting the food.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with rectangular shapes cannot be used for high-heat cooking methods such as stir-frying or sautéing typically performed in round pans where ingredients are tossed and moved around frequently.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "rectangular", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_259", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the pan's cooking surface prone to staining and marking with usage?", "long_answer": "The pan's cooking surface has been reported by some users to be susceptible to staining or showing marks after use, but these can generally be removed using a product specifically designed for cleaning stainless steel, such as Bar Keeper's Friend.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_260", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Does the Cuisinart crepe pan's non-stick surface meet food safety standards for direct food contact?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart crepe pan features a non-stick surface that adheres to safety standards for direct contact with food, in addition to facilitating easy release of the food from the pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_261", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "What is the composition material of the pan?", "long_answer": "The pan is constructed using tri-ply stainless steel, renowned for its heat control capabilities and long-lasting durability.", "short_answer": "tri-ply stainless steel", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_262", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is the skillet suitable for baking bread and pastries in addition to frying and stovetop cooking?", "long_answer": "The skillet is designed to be versatile, allowing not only for frying and stovetop cooking but also for baking. It excels at baking bread and pastries due to its superior heat distribution properties, which stem from the material it's made of, typically cast iron.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_263", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does the handle of the Matfer Bourgeat pan remain cool during cooking?", "long_answer": "The Matfer Bourgeat pan's handle, which is made of high-quality, extra-strong steel strip, is not heat-resistant and may become hot while the pan is used for cooking, necessitating the use of pot holders or a handle cover to prevent burns.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_203", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I've had enough of Copper Chef. Show me the cheapest pan not from them.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Copper Chef' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_204", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I don't want nothing to do with USA Pan. Just find me some other brand's pan that can take at least 400F without melting and doesn't cost an arm and a leg. Hell, make it the cheapest you got!", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'USA Pan' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 \nORDER BY price\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_264", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Does the 18/10 stainless steel surface of this pan react with acidic foods?", "long_answer": "The pan features an 18/10 stainless steel cooking surface that does not react with acidic ingredients, ensuring that the natural flavors of the food are preserved without being altered by the cookware.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_265", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Can the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set be cleaned in a dishwasher without causing damage?", "long_answer": "The manufacturer of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set suggests hand washing as the ideal method for cleaning to ensure the pan's longevity, although some users report that the pan can be cleaned in a dishwasher without issue.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_266", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is the Madeleine pan designed to allow easy release of the cakes?", "long_answer": "Customers generally have a successful experience with Madeleines releasing readily from the pan, and applying a light greasing can enhance this effect.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_205", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I need a blue pan to match my kitchen, but not more than 30 dollars. Show me the largest one you have that's within my budget.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND price <= 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND price <= 30 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND price <= 30 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' AND price <= 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_69", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is it possible to whip up a rapid stir-fry sauce in this pan without scorching it?", "long_answer": "Undoubtedly, a wok is ideal for this job due to its rounded bottom, which centralizes heat in the middle. This feature lets you slide the ingredients up the cooler sides of the pan, thus preventing the sauce from scorching as you maintain high heat at the core for continuous cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with a completely flat bottom do not have a function of concentrating heat in the same way a traditional wok does. The round bottom of a wok allows for a small area of heat concentration which can be used for efficient high-heat cooking.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "wok", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_206", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I am hunting for a deal, buddy. I only have 10 bucks in my pocket and I am crazy about Chicago Metallic and USA Pan. What's the highest oven safe temperature pan I can get?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand IN (\"Chicago Metallic\", \"USA Pan\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand IN (\"Chicago Metallic\", \"USA Pan\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand IN (\"Chicago Metallic\", \"USA Pan\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND (brand = 'Chicago Metallic' OR brand = 'USA Pan') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_267", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are these pans dishwasher safe or should they be hand washed?", "long_answer": "Although some customers report they have washed the pans in the dishwasher without any immediate issues, the recommended cleaning method is hand washing. The rationale behind hand washing is to preserve the integrity and extend the life of the pan's coating.", "short_answer": "hand washing", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_268", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is the Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri is designed with a magnetized base, making it suitable for use on induction cooktops as it allows for rapid heat transfer.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_70", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Will this pan evenly cook my food, particularly during meat searing?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the pan's round design is intended to promote uniform heat distribution, which is especially advantageous for searing meats. It ensures that your food cooks evenly, preventing the formation of hot spots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_207", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I need a blue pan that's at least 12 inches, but I don't want to cough up too much. Give me the cheapest one you have.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND color = \"blue\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND color = \"blue\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND color = \"blue\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' AND size >= 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_208", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm tired of those silver pans. Get me the one with the highest oven-safe temperature that isn't silver.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'silver' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_269", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does this pot feature a pouring spout to facilitate spill-free pouring of liquids?", "long_answer": "The pot is equipped with a pouring spout and additionally features a lip design that aids in the easy and spill-free pouring of liquids.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_270", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Can the handle of the pan be safely placed in the oven?", "long_answer": "The pan includes a cast stainless steel handle that is not only triple-riveted to ensure sturdiness but also comes with a removable silicone sleeve. This design means the handle can withstand oven temperatures, rendering it oven-safe.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_271", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is it safe to cook highly acidic foods in this nonstick pan without risking damage to the coating?", "long_answer": "Cooking acidic foods in a nonstick pan will not immediately damage its surface. However, the nonstick coating may degrade more quickly with prolonged exposure to highly acidic dishes, thus it is preferably avoided to ensure the longevity of the pan's coating.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_209", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Just checking, but do you have any Bialetti pans that can handle over 500F degrees in the oven? Show me your best one.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Bialetti\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Bialetti\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Bialetti' AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_272", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the Cuisinart Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan have a weight that is difficult to manage when handling?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan has been designed to have a balance between sturdiness and manageability, resulting in a weight that is not considered heavy for the user to handle.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_71", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I aim to find eco-friendly cookware. Does purchasing these pans align with that objective?", "long_answer": "Certainly, purchasing these pans aligns with your objective of acquiring sustainable cookware. The pans, made from aluminum, are extremely recyclable and contribute positively to environmental preservation, which is in harmony with the tenets of sustainability.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's environmental considerations are not recommended for those who prefer to minimize their environmental footprint through recyclable and sustainable cookware options, highlighting aluminum's advantage as it can be recycled effectively.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_210", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm after an All-Clad pan, but it needs to be bigger than the average size. Find me the cheapest one that fits those demands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black` with asin: B0170TFNXM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'All-Clad' AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_211", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I love to blast my oven, but I don't want my pan to melt away. Find me the cheapest one that can withstand temperatures over 400 degrees.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_273", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the T-fal saucepan durable for daily cooking use?", "long_answer": "Customer feedback suggests that the T-fal saucepan withstands daily use without problems. However, a few customers have expressed concerns about the thinness of the metal, but generally, the saucepan is seen as well-built and provides good value for its cost.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_274", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Can the handle of this cookware be safely used in the oven?", "long_answer": "The cookware comes with large, stay-cool loop handles, which are specifically designed to provide ease of use and control when handled with oven mitts. These handles are also constructed to be oven-safe.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_72", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Will this pan heat quickly on the stove?", "long_answer": "Cast iron pans generally require more time to warm up due to their slower heat conductivity when compared to materials such as aluminum or stainless steel. Therefore, it's necessary to allot additional time for your cast iron pan to attain the required temperature prior to beginning the cooking process.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being made from cast iron are not recommended for rapid cooking or recipes requiring quick temperature changes, due to their slow heat conductivity and weight.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "cast iron", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_212", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm tired of replacing pans that can't handle my oven's heat. Show me the first pan that can stand an average or above average oven safe temperature.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_275", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is this pot suitable for cooking various quantities of food, ranging from single servings to larger meals for multiple people?", "long_answer": "The pot's size and design are versatile, allowing for the preparation of different food quantities, suitable for cooking both small single servings and larger meals intended for numerous individuals.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_276", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Can the T-fal Professional fry pan be cleaned in a dishwasher without damaging it?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Professional fry pan is designed to be dishwasher safe, allowing for easy cleaning. However, to prolong the durability of the nonstick coating, it is recommended that the fry pan be handwashed.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_213", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm looking for a pan, specifically a Tramontina brand and only in silver or black. What's the cheapest option you got in those?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch` with asin: B009HBKQR0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") AND brand = \"Tramontina\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") AND brand = \"Tramontina\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") AND brand = \"Tramontina\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Tramontina' AND color IN ('silver', 'black') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_214", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm after a good-sized pan from either Utopia Kitchen or USA Pan - it has to be at least 8 inches. Oh, and it needs to handle high oven temperatures. Which one can take the most heat?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"USA Pan\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"USA Pan\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"USA Pan\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Utopia Kitchen', 'USA Pan') \nAND size >= 8 \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_277", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Can this pan be safely used in an oven according to the product metadata?", "long_answer": "The product metadata does not mention the oven safety of the pan. Therefore, without explicit confirmation from the manufacturer's instructions, it is recommended not to use the pan in the oven to ensure its longevity and proper care.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_215", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Churning out big meals requires sizeable pans but my budget is tight. What's the largest pan you've got under 30 dollars?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND size > 12 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND size > 12 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_278", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is this bread pan suitable for baking gluten-free recipes?", "long_answer": "This bread pan is fully compatible with gluten-free recipes and can produce baking results of the same high quality as with traditional recipes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_216", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm looking for a green pan that can withstand at least 450 degrees. Don't try to rob me though, give me the most affordable option you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND color = \"green\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND color = \"green\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'green' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_217", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm after a pan from either Ozeri or Copper Chef that can handle some serious heat. Which one of their pans can withstand the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Ozeri\", \"Copper Chef\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Ozeri\", \"Copper Chef\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Ozeri\", \"Copper Chef\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Ozeri', 'Copper Chef') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_218", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm looking for a budget friendly pan from either Presto or Anolon, but it needs to be able to handle some heat in the oven. What's the best option you guys have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Anolon\") AND price <= 50 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Anolon\") AND price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Anolon\") AND price <= 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Presto', 'Anolon') AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_279", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is it necessary to use oil or butter on the pan's nonstick surface for cooking?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed with a nonstick surface that enables cooking with minimal or no addition of fat or oil, which encourages healthier cooking practices and ensures that food can be easily removed from the pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_280", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "How would you describe the weight of the saucepan?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed with a moderate weight that strikes a balance, ensuring it is neither too heavy nor too lightweight, giving it a sturdy feel while still being easy to handle.", "short_answer": "moderate weight", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_219", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm whipping up some high heat dishes and need a pan that can withstand at least 600 Fahrenheit and I'm into grey and blue stuff. Do you have one like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"blue\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"blue\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND (color = 'grey' OR color = 'blue');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_281", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does this pan have a second handle to assist with lifting?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed with only one handle; therefore, it does not include a second handle to facilitate easier lifting. Individuals requiring a pan with two handles for more manageable weight handling should consider different models that offer this feature.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_282", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is this pan dishwasher safe for cleaning?", "long_answer": "This pan is not suitable for cleaning in a dishwasher. The recommended cleaning method is to use hot water and subsequently re-grease it lightly following each use to maintain its condition.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_283", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Should food adhere to the surface of a well-seasoned cast iron skillet?", "long_answer": "A properly seasoned cast iron skillet is expected to exhibit nonstick properties, meaning food should not adhere to its surface during cooking. However, if food is sticking, the skillet might require further seasoning. In the meantime, using additional oil or fat can help to reduce sticking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_220", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm staying away from Ozeri. But show me your most affordable pan that's at least average in size.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Ozeri' AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_73", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Can this pan comfortably fit in my compact kitchen that has limited storage space?", "long_answer": "Considering that round pans may not make the best use of space in a smaller kitchen, particularly when attempting to fit them into square or unconventional nooks, it's crucial to think about the pan's storage efficiency. If conserving space is a priority, looking into alternative pan shapes that better fit your kitchen's storage configuration could prove advantageous.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_221", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm trying to save some dough here, but I still want quality. Plus, I'm only looking for green or black pans. What's the highest oven-safe temperature pan you've got that is not more costly than an average pan?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND color IN (\"green\", \"black\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND color IN (\"green\", \"black\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND color IN (\"green\", \"black\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('green', 'black') AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_284", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the cookware distribute heat evenly during cooking?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed with an aluminum encapsulated base that rapidly heats up and diffuses heat uniformly, thereby preventing any hot spots and enhancing the overall cooking experience.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_285", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is the skillet suitable for outdoor cooking, such as on a campfire?", "long_answer": "The skillet is designed with durability in mind and can withstand high temperatures, making it perfectly suited for the tough conditions of outdoor cooking, including use over a campfire.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_286", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is the lid provided with the saucepan designed for straining pasta?", "long_answer": "The saucepan comes with a lid that has steam holes on two sides, which allows it to effectively drain pasta and perform similar tasks, making it versatile in its use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_287", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is it possible to cook fish or chicken in the pan without them sticking?", "long_answer": "Cooking fish or chicken in the pan is feasible, and to mitigate sticking, the use of a cooking spray like PAM is recommended which also facilitates easier cleaning post-use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_288", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Does the pan possess a non-stick surface that allows for easy food release?", "long_answer": "According to customer feedback, the pan has a non-stick surface that facilitates easy food release, thereby making it particularly good for cooking crepes and various other meals without the issue of sticking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_222", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I need a cheap All-Clad pan for my cooking, ideally not more than $10. What's the maximum oven safe temperature I can use it at?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND price <= 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND price <= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND price <= 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'All-Clad' AND price <= 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_289", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Does the skillet handle become hot when cooking?", "long_answer": "The entire skillet, handle included, will become hot when it is used for cooking, necessitating the use of oven mitts or a protective handle cover to prevent burns to the hands.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_74", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is it sufficient to wash this pan with soap and water, or does it have specific cleaning needs?", "long_answer": "Stainless steel pans require more than just soap and water for cleaning since they can become discolored over time. To maintain their appearance, regular polishing should be incorporated into your standard cleaning regimen, an important factor to think about if you prefer low-maintenance cookware.", "short_answer": "specific cleaning needed", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with stainless steel material are not suitable for those seeking the easiest maintenance, as they can develop discoloration and require regular polishing to keep their appearance pristine.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "stainless steel", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_223", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm not shelling out more than 30 dollars. Get me the cheapest black pan you have in stock.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND color = \"black\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND color = \"black\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND color = 'black' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_290", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "What is the weight characteristic of the frying pan as perceived by customers?", "long_answer": "Customers perceive the frying pan to have a significant weight, which they associate with its quality construction, implying that the pan is not lightweight but rather built to convey sturdiness and durability.", "short_answer": "substantial weight", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_224", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I cook a lot in the oven, with temperatures soaring above 400F. What's the cheapest pan you got that can stand this heat?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_291", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the silicone handle of the fry pan remain cool during stovetop cooking?", "long_answer": "The fry pan is equipped with riveted silicone handles specifically manufactured to remain cool to the touch, providing a secure and comfortable grip when cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_292", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the entire interior of the pan designed to be magnetic for induction cooking?", "long_answer": "Not the entire interior of the pan is magnetic; there is a magnetic disk at the bottom that enables compatibility with induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_225", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I've got an eye only for Bialetti and Cuisinart, and it's gotta be silver. Dig up the cheapest pan for me from one of those brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Cuisinart\") AND color = \"silver\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Cuisinart\") AND color = \"silver\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Cuisinart\") AND color = \"silver\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'silver' AND (brand = 'Bialetti' OR brand = 'Cuisinart') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_75", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is it safe to use my metal spatula with this pan without causing any damage?", "long_answer": "It is advisable to refrain from using metal utensils with this pan. Constructed of anodized aluminum, the pan is robust yet susceptible to scratching when metal utensils are used. Such scratches can undermine the pan's non-reactive characteristics and diminish its durability.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with anodized aluminum are not suitable for use with metal utensils that can scratch the hardened surface, potentially compromising its non-reactive properties.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_293", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Does the wok come with a lid that allows visibility of the contents during cooking?", "long_answer": "The wok includes a tempered-glass cover that enables you to see the contents while cooking, providing the convenience of monitoring your food without the need to remove the lid.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_226", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Look, I ain't shelling out more than 30 dollars here. So, find me an affordable pan either from Bialetti or Copper Chef, please.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal` with asin: B000S6I4ZE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Copper Chef\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Copper Chef\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (brand = 'Bialetti' OR brand = 'Copper Chef') AND price <= 30;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_227", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm after a pan that's either green or blue. What's the cheapest one you got in these colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('green', 'blue') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_228", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I do a lot of high-heat cooking and only trust Tramontina for my kitchen stuff. Hook me up with a pan that can withstand at least 450F.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch` with asin: B009HBKQR0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND brand = \"Tramontina\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND brand = \"Tramontina\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Tramontina' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_294", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is this pan designed to be used for broiling chicken?", "long_answer": "The pan is crafted to withstand the high temperatures required for broiling and is effective for cooking chicken under such conditions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_295", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does this pan naturally have a non-stick surface, or is seasoning required to achieve it?", "long_answer": "To achieve a non-stick surface on this pan, seasoning is necessary. The process might require some effort, but success in creating and maintaining the non-stick quality tends to improve with repeated use and adherence to the proper seasoning instructions provided.", "short_answer": "Seasoning required", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_229", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Not gonna settle for any mini pan that can't handle high temperatures. Get me the cheapest pan that's bigger than the average size and can withstand at least 450F in the oven.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_296", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it necessary to use oil when cooking with the Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan?", "long_answer": "The Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan is engineered with a non-stick ceramic coating that enables cooking with little or no oil. Reviews from customers corroborate that food items, including eggs, bacon, and omelets, can be cooked without sticking, attesting to the pan's proficiency in oil-free cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_297", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Can this pan accommodate making large, 2-pound loaves of artisan bread?", "long_answer": "Yes, the pan has been designed with dimensions that cater specifically to large bread loaves. It is capable of holding up to 6 cups or 2 pounds of bread dough, which is suitable for making family-sized artisan bread.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_298", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the saucepan's rim specifically designed to facilitate drip-free pouring?", "long_answer": "The rim of the saucepan is purposely tapered to enable drip-free pouring, making it easier to transfer liquids without spillage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_299", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Are the nonstick pans dishwasher-safe?", "long_answer": "The nonstick pans are indeed dishwasher-safe, but handwashing is recommended to better maintain the quality and longevity of the nonstick surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_300", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is the weight of a cast iron skillet typically heavy?", "long_answer": "Cast iron skillets are inherently heavy due to the material and design used in their construction, which is a characteristic that contributes to their ability to retain heat effectively.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_301", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the rim of the saucepan designed to allow drip-free pouring?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed with a tapered rim to facilitate drip-free pouring.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_302", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is it possible for the pan to rust when left soaked in water overnight?", "long_answer": "If a pan is left soaked in water overnight and is not dried properly afterward, it can potentially rust. To avoid rusting, it is recommended to wash and then swiftly and thoroughly dry the pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_230", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I need a big pan, something over 12 inches, but I've had enough of Chicago Metallic brand. What's the most affordable one you got that fits my needs?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand != 'Chicago Metallic' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_303", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is the glass lid designed to form a tight seal on the pan?", "long_answer": "Yes, the glass lid is specifically engineered to fit tightly on the pan, ensuring that heat and moisture are effectively retained, which leads to quicker and more uniform cooking results.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_231", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm not looking to blow a ton of money on fancy pans. What's the largest pan you have that's less than 10 dollars?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_304", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the pot stable on a burner despite being lightweight?", "long_answer": "Although the pot has been manufactured with a focus on being lightweight for convenience, it does not compromise on stability when placed on a burner, ensuring it remains well-balanced.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_305", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "What is the duration of the warranty for the fry pan?", "long_answer": "The fry pan is backed by a lifetime warranty, which covers any defects in craftsmanship and material, provided that it has been used and cared for in a manner that is considered normal.", "short_answer": "lifetime", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_232", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I like to crank the heat up in the kitchen, so I need a pan that can handle an oven temperature above 600F. But I'm not made of money, so find me a pan that's cheaper than your average pan price, okay?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans);"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_306", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Does this pan cause Madeleines to brown unevenly, particularly at the edges?", "long_answer": "Customers have reported that Madeleines tend to brown more on the edges when using this pan, indicating that adjustments in oven temperature or baking time could be required to achieve even browning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_307", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "What is the feedback from customers regarding the durability of this wok?", "long_answer": "The majority of users report that the wok is sturdy and endures well over time, although a minority of users indicate that extensive use at maximum settings may cause wear, especially affecting the thermostat component.", "short_answer": "sturdy and durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_308", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is it necessary to cook with oil or butter to prevent food from sticking to the Stone Earth Pan?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Pan is designed with non-stick properties that significantly reduce the need for oil or butter while cooking. Customers often report that food does not stick to the pan, and therefore, use of oil or butter can be minimal to prevent sticking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_309", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the Presto 5900 electric wok equipped with a non-stick coating?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 electric wok is constructed with a durable stainless-steel body and does not include a non-stick coating, catering to individuals who opt not to use non-stick surfaces in their cooking equipment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_76", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I enjoy creating confections; can this pan assist with tasks such as melting chocolate without scorching it?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the copper material's responsive nature in the pan enables gentle and even heat distribution, which is perfect for melting chocolate without causing it to scorch.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with copper material are ideally used for cooking processes requiring precise temperature control, such as simmering delicate sauces or melting chocolate due to their responsive nature to temperature changes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "copper", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_233", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Look, I need a pan but I can't afford to shell out more than 30 dollars. Also, I've had a bad experience with Matfer Bourgeat before and I am not eager to repeat it. Find me the most affordable option from any other brand, ASAP.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND brand != 'Matfer Bourgeat' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_234", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I tend to cook at high temperatures and I am a big fan of Chicago Metallic products. Tell me, do you have a pan that can withstand at least 450F?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Chicago Metallic' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_235", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm only interested in the brands Utopia Kitchen and Ozeri for my kitchenware. Can you find me the most affordable pan from these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch` with asin: B00X4WQMAS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Ozeri\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Ozeri\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Ozeri\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Utopia Kitchen', 'Ozeri') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_236", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm cranking up the heat, man. Can you find me a Norpro pan that can handle over 400F in the oven?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND brand = \"Norpro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND brand = \"Norpro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Norpro' AND oven_safe_temperature > 400;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_310", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is it necessary to use specialized cleaning products for this broiler pan set?", "long_answer": "Standard cleaning methods and products are generally adequate for cleaning this broiler pan set, but for optimal results, some users recommend using a cleaning product known as Barkeeper's Friend.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_311", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Does the pan maintain its non-stick properties when used according to the manufacturer's instructions?", "long_answer": "When the pan is used and maintained as per the manufacturer's instructions, most users report that it retains its non-stick qualities effectively.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_312", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is the Chicago Metallic brand pan suitable for use in professional baking environments?", "long_answer": "The Chicago Metallic brand pan is held in high regard for its professional-grade durability, making it a well-suited option for use in professional baking settings.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_313", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Can the Copper Chef frying pan be used on an induction stovetop?", "long_answer": "Yes, the Copper Chef frying pan is designed to work with induction stovetops. It features a stainless steel induction plate built into the base of the pan for even heat distribution, making it also suitable for gas, electric, and ceramic cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_314", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is food sticking a common issue when cooking with this cast iron skillet?", "long_answer": "Properly seasoning and pre-heating the cast iron skillet usually provides a natural non-stick surface, with users reporting minimal food sticking when the skillet is used correctly.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_315", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Does the pan's nonstick coating contain PFOA?", "long_answer": "The nonstick coating on the pan has a reinforced design, and it is specifically made without PFOA to ensure safety and health-conscious cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_316", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the pan well-balanced and easy to handle while cooking?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be well-balanced and easy to handle during the cooking process, as described by the product specifications and echoed in user testimonials. Yet, it should be noted that those with diminished strength or manual dexterity may perceive the pan as somewhat heavy, potentially affecting its ease of use for this subset of users.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_317", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is the saucepan effective and safe to use on ceramic stovetops?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is known to perform effectively on ceramic stovetops, providing even heating across the surface while maintaining a non-heating handle to ensure safe handling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_237", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm after a decent sized pan over 12 inches. Can you tell me the cheapest one you have from either Matfer Bourgeat or USA Pan?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"USA Pan\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"USA Pan\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"USA Pan\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size>12 AND brand IN ('Matfer Bourgeat', 'USA Pan') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_318", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "What is the maximum oven temperature the Madeleine Pan can withstand before it becomes unsafe to use?", "long_answer": "The Madeleine Pan is safe for use in the oven at temperatures reaching up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit or 232 degrees Celsius. However, it should not be used under a broiler, as it is not designed to endure the intense heat of that setting.", "short_answer": "450F / 232C", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_238", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "No silver pans or anything from Ozeri, got it? Show me your pan that can handle the highest oven temperature within these conditions.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" AND NOT color = \"silver\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" AND NOT color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" AND NOT color = \"silver\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'silver' AND brand != 'Ozeri' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_77", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is it safe to use metal spatulas or forks with this pan without causing harm?", "long_answer": "Avoid using metal utensils with pans that have fragile non-stick coatings, such as this one, as they can cause scratches and damage to the surface. We advise opting for wooden, silicone, or plastic utensils when using this specific frying pan to maintain its non-stick quality.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with delicate non-stick coatings cannot be used for cooking methods that involve metal utensils or very high heat, to avoid damaging the surface.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_78", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is this pan suitable for those who often prepare meals rich in spices and herbs?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this is a wonderful choice for those types of dishes. The ceramic composition of the pan is non-reactive with even the most pungent spices or herbs, guaranteeing that the tastes of your dishes stay true and unchanged.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with ceramic material typically mean they are advantageous for cooking acidic foods because the non-reactive nature ensures that the food taste is not altered.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "ceramic", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_239", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm not picky on colors, but it's got to be either black or copper, and it needs to handle a good amount of heat. What's your highest temperature tolerant pan in those colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"copper\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"copper\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"copper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('black', 'copper') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_319", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the 18/10 stainless steel cooking surface of the pan non-reactive and capable of preserving the natural flavors of food without imparting a metallic taste?", "long_answer": "The pan is manufactured with an 18/10 stainless steel cooking surface, which is intentionally designed to be non-reactive. As a result, it doesn't alter the flavor profile of your food or contribute any metallic taste, ensuring that the food's natural flavors are preserved during the cooking process.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_79", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "What kind of maintenance will be needed for this pan as time goes by?", "long_answer": "As time progresses, maintaining this pan will demand more effort compared to other alternatives because it is not dishwasher safe. To ensure it continues to function optimally and retains its appearance, manual washing and adherence to specific care procedures, such as periodic re-seasoning, are necessary.", "short_answer": "handwash", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" fail to meet the requirements for easy maintenance and may involve extra steps like re-seasoning or careful hand-polishing to uphold their performance and appearance standards.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_80", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "long_answer": "Our frying pans and skillets, crafted from aluminum or copper, are renowned for their superior heat conductivity, ensuring even cooking. Nonetheless, should you use an induction stove, bear in mind that these materials inherently lack magnetic properties, rendering them incompatible and potentially affecting cooking performance, unless you employ a ferrous plate to enable induction.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_320", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Does the frying pan have a non-stick cooking surface?", "long_answer": "The frying pan features a stick-resistant cooking surface which can be utilized efficiently by preheating the pan, using an adequate amount of oil or butter, and being careful not to overheat the pan, which helps prevent food from sticking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_240", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm trying to cook up a storm here and need a big pan, at least 10 inches or more. Give me your most affordable option.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_241", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm no fancy chef, but I need a pan that can withstand at least 600 F in the oven. What's the least expensive one you got that can handle that heat?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_321", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the T-fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot feature a built-in temperature gauge?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot is not equipped with a built-in temperature gauge.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_242", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I often crank my oven up beyond 450F and I like the Anolon brand. What's the first pan you'd recommend that can handle the heat?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND brand = \"Anolon\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND brand = \"Anolon\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Anolon' AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_243", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I often bake stuff at around 400F and looking for a decent sized pan that doesn't cost an arm and a leg. Can you suggest the biggest one that can handle the heat and won't wipe out my account?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price < 100 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_322", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with a cast iron skillet without damaging it?", "long_answer": "Although it is possible to use metal utensils on a cast iron skillet, it is advisable to opt for wooden or silicone utensils to preserve the skillet's seasoning and prevent the surface from scratches, thereby prolonging the lifespan and quality of the cookware.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_81", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is it safe to use a steel wool scrubber for cleaning this pan to get rid of the tough food remnants?", "long_answer": "It is advised not to use a steel wool scrubber on this pan. Since the pan is constructed from aluminum and could possess a non-stick coating or an anodized finish, abrasive scouring pads, such as steel wool, have the potential to harm the surface and impair its non-stick capabilities.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's specific maintenance needs fail to meet the requirements for indiscriminate cleaning methods such as harsh scouring pads or certain dishwasher detergents, especially if they have a non-stick layer or are anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_323", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Do the pan handles remain cool due to being coated with a heat-resistant material?", "long_answer": "The pan handles are coated with heat-resistant silicone, which is designed to keep the handles cool and provide a comfortable grip during cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_244", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm after a pan that's at least 10 inches wide but not in that copper colour. Find me the cheapest one you've got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND NOT color = \"copper\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND NOT color = \"copper\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND NOT color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND color != 'copper' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_324", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is this skillet non-stick immediately upon first use?", "long_answer": "The skillet is pre-seasoned, which is intended to offer some non-stick properties, but initially, some foods may still stick. It is expected that with regular use and maintenance, including additional seasoning, the non-stick performance will enhance progressively.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_82", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I need a pan suitable for use over my fireplace during power outages. Is this model appropriate and safe for that situation?", "long_answer": "Since this pan is a saucepan, it is advisable not to use it over a fireplace. Direct heat from a fireplace may harm the pan's handle and other parts that are not designed to withstand such high temperatures.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan lack the capability to be used on open fires or grills without risking damage to their handles or materials that are not designed to withstand such direct, intense heat.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_83", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is it simple to clean this pan in the dishwasher after preparing a steak?", "long_answer": "It is advised against cleaning this pan in the dishwasher because of its distinctive material composition, which is intended for traditional or specific culinary techniques that necessitate superior heat retention, like preparing a steak. To preserve its quality and functionality, hand washing is the preferred method.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are ideally used for traditional or specialized cooking methods that take advantage of their unique material properties, such as the heat retention of cast iron.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_325", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Does the handle of the cast iron skillet remain cool to the touch during cooking?", "long_answer": "The handle of the skillet is constructed from cast iron, the same material as the skillet itself, meaning it will become hot when the skillet is used for cooking; therefore, it is essential to use a pot holder or handle cover to prevent burns and ensure safe handling.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_326", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is preheating required before cooking with this wok?", "long_answer": "It is recommended to preheat the wok to the desired temperature before adding ingredients in order to achieve the best cooking results, as is the case with most cooking appliances.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_327", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is it necessary to use oil when cooking with the All-Clad fry pan?", "long_answer": "Although the design of the All-Clad fry pan allows for cooking with reduced amounts of oil, it is generally advisable to use at least some oil to avoid sticking, depending on the food being prepared.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_245", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm keen on Tramontina. Which product of theirs do you have in your pan collection?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch` with asin: B009HBKQR0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Tramontina\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Tramontina\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Tramontina';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_328", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is this pan safe for cleaning in a dishwasher?", "long_answer": "The pan is labeled as dishwasher-safe; however, to maintain the integrity of the nonstick coating, user experiences suggest that hand washing is preferable. Hand washing is recommended to help preserve the pan's quality over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_329", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is a lid included with the Cuisinart 719-16 Saucepan?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart 719-16 Saucepan comes with a Flavor Lock Lid, which is designed to seal in moisture and nutrients, thereby contributing to healthier and more flavorful cooking outcomes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_330", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the product likely to stain or discolor over time with usage or after being washed in a dishwasher?", "long_answer": "The product, made from stainless steel, is generally resistant to high heat and is not prone to discoloring. However, some customers have reported that it may not appear perfectly clean after dishwasher use and could tarnish over time, particularly if exposed to high broiler heat.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_246", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I need a decent-sized, copper pan that can take serious heat. Find me one that's 10 inches or larger and can handle the highest oven temperature.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND color = \"copper\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND color = \"copper\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND color = 'copper' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_247", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I've had enough of Cuisinart! Get me the cheapest pan you got from any other brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Cuisinart\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Cuisinart\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Cuisinart\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Cuisinart' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_248", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I got a thing for copper colored pans and I trust \"Matfer Bourgeat\" and \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\". Can ya find me the first product from these brands in that shade?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' AND (brand = 'Matfer Bourgeat' OR brand = 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_249", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I'm not really a Wednesday Adams, but I do need me a grey pan that could withstand oven temps of more than 600 F. Now, I'm not rolling in cash so find me the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND color = \"grey\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND color = \"grey\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND color = \"grey\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'grey' AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_84", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is this pan's lid capable of retaining its non-toxic qualities over time?", "long_answer": "Over time, the pan's tempered glass lid might not retain its non-toxic characteristics. Should the coating on the handle or the rim of the lid begin to deteriorate, it could lead to undesirable reactions with your food, potentially jeopardizing the non-toxic quality of the cooking space.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids fail to meet the requirements for completely non-reactive cooking conditions, especially if any sort of coating on the lid's handle or edges were to degrade and interact with the food.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_85", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is it possible for me to regularly use this pan for preparing various types of cuisines without concerning myself with its durability?", "long_answer": "In the majority of culinary styles, the pan should be durable. Nonetheless, if you regularly cook with acidic or alkaline components, it's advisable to choose a treated or anodized pan to prevent metallic taste transfer and discoloration, which can affect the pan's longevity when regularly subjected to these substances.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with reactivity to acidic and alkaline foods feature a potential for metallic taste transfer and discoloration, rendering them less suitable for long-term cooking of tomato sauces or citrus-based dishes unless they're treated or anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_331", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Can this pan serve as an effective substitute for non-stick Teflon pans when it comes to non-stick properties?", "long_answer": "Yes, when this pan is properly seasoned, it becomes an excellent substitute for non-stick Teflon pans, as it can withstand high temperatures and rougher utensils without the risk of peeling. Additionally, the pan is capable of developing a durable non-stick surface over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_86", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Could the pan rust if it isn't properly maintained?", "long_answer": "Indeed, lacking dishwasher-safe capabilities, these pans may be susceptible to rust if not properly maintained with consistent seasoning. This preventative measure aids in safeguarding against corrosion and preserving the pan's integrity.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" do not have a function of self-maintenance and will need regular seasoning (for cast iron or carbon steel) or polishing (for aesthetic reasons) to maintain their best condition.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_87", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I enjoy preparing omelets; would this pan be appropriate for that task?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the pan's circular form ensures heat is spread uniformly over its surface, which is perfect for preparing sensitive dishes such as omelets, guaranteeing they are cooked evenly and softly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_332", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is this pot dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The pot is designed to be dishwasher safe, but to maintain the condition of the non-stick coating, some users suggest hand washing as a preferred cleaning method.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_250", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I can't stand the color silver and I've only got 50 bucks to spare. Give me the biggest non-silver pan you have within that price range.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" AND price < 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" AND price < 50 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" AND price < 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color <> 'silver' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_88", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I recently purchased a new cooktop and need to ensure I acquire a suitable pan. Are there particular features I should be on the lookout for?", "long_answer": "When looking for a new pan, opt for one with a round shape to ensure better compatibility with different types of cooktops, especially the latest induction ones. Make sure the pan is constructed from a magnetic material if you're using an induction cooktop, for seamless functionality.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_333", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the pot's construction allow for quick and even heat distribution?", "long_answer": "The pot is made of durable aluminum, which is engineered to achieve quick and even heat distribution, facilitating efficient cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_334", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Do the molds allow for the creation of traditional shell-shaped madeleines with distinctive ridges?", "long_answer": "The molds are crafted specifically to produce the traditional shell-shaped madeleines complete with the distinctive ridges, staying true to the classic form of these French pastries.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_335", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is there a warranty included with the purchase of the saucepan?", "long_answer": "The saucepan includes a lifetime warranty that guarantees the product's quality and durability over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_251", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I like All-Clad, but I’m bored of silver. Give me the cheapest non-silver pan from All-Clad you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black` with asin: B0170TFNXM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND NOT color = \"silver\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND NOT color = \"silver\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND NOT color = \"silver\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'All-Clad' AND color != 'silver' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_336", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Does the customer feedback suggest that the broiler pan is worth its cost?", "long_answer": "Customer feedback indicates that the quality of the broiler pan is considered impressive by multiple purchasers relative to its price, suggesting that the pan provides good value for its cost.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_337", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Does the All-Clad D3 Fry Pan come with a warranty? ", "long_answer": "The All-Clad D3 Fry Pan is backed by a limited lifetime warranty, which assures consumers coverage for specific defects and issues for the lifetime of the product under certain conditions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_252", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I need a non-silver pan that can withstand at least 400F in the oven. Point me to one, would you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'silver' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_253", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm trying to upgrade my kitchen arsenal and especially love Tramontina pans. Can you find me the cheapest one that's still bigger than the average size?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch` with asin: B009HBKQR0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND brand = \"Tramontina\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND brand = \"Tramontina\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND brand = \"Tramontina\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Tramontina' AND price = (SELECT price FROM all_pans WHERE brand = 'Tramontina' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1) AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans)"}}
{"id": "search_qa_254", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I am looking for a pan that's either black or green and larger than 8 inches. What's the first one that comes to mind?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") AND size > 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") AND size > 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('black', 'green') AND size > 8 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_338", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "What is the material composition of the T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot?", "long_answer": "The T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot is constructed from durable aluminum, which is known for its ability to provide long-lasting performance and promote even heat distribution during cooking.", "short_answer": "aluminum", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_339", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Should these pans be preheated at low temperature before adding food?", "long_answer": "These pans are designed to be preheated before adding food, as per the manufacturer's instructions; however, it's advised to avoid overheating and to preheat at a lower temperature to ensure proper cooking and to preserve the integrity of the pans.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_89", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I am in search of cookware that can assist me in cooking more efficiently. Do pans equipped with glass lids contribute to a faster cooking time?", "long_answer": "Pans featuring tempered glass lids provide the convenience of monitoring your food during cooking, yet they may not be the optimal choice for faster cooking times. The less efficient heat insulation of glass lids might slightly prolong the cooking process compared to pans with solid, heavier lids that offer superior heat retention.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids are not recommended for users looking for the most energy-efficient cookware, as they might not insulate heat as well as some heavier, more solid lid options, potentially leading to slightly increased energy use over time.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_340", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the saucepan suitable for boiling water, melting butter, and cooking soups?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed to be versatile and effective for tasks such as boiling water, melting butter, and preparing soups, indicating its capability to handle these common cooking activities efficiently.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_341", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Can the crepe pan be cleaned in a dishwasher without damaging it?", "long_answer": "The product information does not state whether the crepe pan is dishwasher safe. To ensure the pan's durability, it is generally advised to wash it manually using a mild detergent and warm water.", "short_answer": "Not specified", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_342", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the T-fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot is designed to be dishwasher safe, enabling easy cleaning. Additionally, its non-stick interior also makes hand washing simple, according to customer feedback.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_255", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm a big fan of T-fal and ZWILLING J.A. Henckels. Got any pans from those brands? Show me the first one you find.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('T-fal', 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_256", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Listen, I need a pan that can go in the oven at 600°F but I'm not looking for anything fancy. Just a regular black or grey one will do. Can you find me a product that matches that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"grey\") AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"grey\") AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND (color = 'black' OR color = 'grey');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_343", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does the glass lid come with a pour spout that is efficient for straining purposes?", "long_answer": "The glass lid features a Cook `n Pour design, which includes a pour spout that is specifically aimed at facilitating the straining process for items such as vegetables and pasta, and it has been found to be convenient by many users.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_344", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is this pan manufactured using any harmful chemicals such as PTFE or PFOA?", "long_answer": "The pan is manufactured without the use of PTFE and PFOA, which are considered harmful chemicals, ensuring that its production is free from these substances.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_90", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Can this pan withstand frequent cleaning in the dishwasher if I tend to wash my kitchenware that way often?", "long_answer": "Certainly. This pan is designed specifically for regular use. It is built to withstand the high temperatures and harsh chemical detergents commonly found in dishwashers, ensuring that it does not readily warp, rust, or deteriorate, even with daily machine washing.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute feature resistance to both the high temperatures and strong chemicals typical in dishwashers, which ensures they do not warp, rust, or degrade quickly when exposed to such conditions regularly.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_345", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the lighter-weight pan able to distribute heat as evenly as cast iron pans?", "long_answer": "Despite its lighter weight, the pan features a heavy-gauge bottom that ensures quick and even heat conduction, thereby offering consistent cooking results similar to those of cast iron pans.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_346", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "How long does it take for the wok to heat up for use?", "long_answer": "The wok is designed to heat up swiftly, enabling customers to cook meals in a reduced time frame, as reported by numerous users who appreciate the convenience of the rapid heat-up feature.", "short_answer": "quickly", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_257", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I ain't parting with more than 50 dollars, so show me the cheapest pan you have in stock.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_258", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I do a lot of cooking and my pans need to handle the heat. So which pan can withstand the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_91", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is there a chance of encountering hot spots when I sauté vegetables using this pan?", "long_answer": "No, you should not encounter hot spots when sautéing vegetables, since the pan's rounded design is recognized for its even heat distribution, which is essential to properly cook vegetables during the sautéing process.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_259", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I don't need anything fancy or pricey, just give me a pan that's oven safe at high temperatures but won't bust my wallet. What's your best option in terms of the average price or less?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_260", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I ain't throwing around much cash at 30 bucks max and I have a thing for copper. What's the biggest copper-colored pan you got within that limit?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND color = \"copper\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND color = \"copper\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND color = 'copper' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_347", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the nonstick coating on this product prone to chipping?", "long_answer": "The nonstick surface of this product may be susceptible to chipping after prolonged use. Customers have reported instances of chipping. To minimize the risk of damage to the coating, it is advisable to avoid overheating and to employ gentle cleaning techniques.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_348", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the stainless steel pan likely to develop rust after being washed?", "long_answer": "With appropriate maintenance and care, the stainless steel pan typically does not become rusty, as indicated by customer feedback, which suggests the pan remains rust-free and maintains its usability over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_349", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Can this pan be used for searing meats and is it safe to transfer directly from stovetop to oven?", "long_answer": "This pan is capable of searing meats effectively and is designed to be oven safe, allowing for a direct transfer from the stovetop to the oven, as reported by customers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_261", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm not a fan of Presto's pans, but I need a really large one for my next cooking experiment. What's the largest pan you have that's not from Presto?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size = (SELECT size FROM all_pans WHERE brand != 'Presto' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1) AND brand != 'Presto';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_350", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is it possible to season the pan with different oils and techniques?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the pan can be seasoned using various methods, provided they adhere to the fundamental principles of seasoning. Experimentation with different oils and techniques is encouraged to discover the most effective personal method.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_351", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is the Lodge Skillet suitable for baking bread and delivering a crusty loaf?", "long_answer": "The Lodge Skillet is indeed appropriate for baking bread; its significant depth and even heat distribution contribute to the creation of a perfectly crusty loaf.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_352", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "How resistant to scratches is the non-stick coating on the Stone Earth Pan when used with proper utensils?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Pan features a hardened, scratch-resistant coating that is highly durable, particularly when used with plastic or silicone utensils and cared for properly.", "short_answer": "highly resistant", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_353", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is the ceramic coating on the fry pan prone to chipping?", "long_answer": "While there are customer reports indicating instances of the ceramic coating chipping, it is essential to follow the manufacturer's instructions for use and care of the fry pan to minimize the risk of such damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_92", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I frequently encounter issues with pans that fail to heat evenly on my stovetop. Is this design engineered to promote uniform heating?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the circular design of the pan contributes to a more uniform heat distribution across the surface, enhancing its compatibility and heating efficiency on a variety of stovetops, such as conventional and contemporary induction ranges, provided it is made from suitable magnetic materials.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_262", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm not a fan of copper color and I often do some serious high-heat cooking. Bring me the pan with the highest oven-safe temperature that doesn't have a copper finish.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'copper' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_263", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I've been hearing a lot about this Utopia Kitchen brand. Can you point me to one of their pans?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch` with asin: B00X4WQMAS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Utopia Kitchen' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_354", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Are there any reports of color changes or staining on the pot after usage?", "long_answer": "One customer reported a caramel-colored film appearing after cooking tomato stew in the pot, but such occurrences are not widely reported among other users, implying that staining is not a common issue.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_355", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the Presto 5900 wok susceptible to peeling or flaking due to any non-stick coatings?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 wok is constructed from stainless steel and does not have any non-stick coatings applied to its surface. As a result, the wok does not experience peeling or flaking issues that can occur with non-stick surfaces over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_264", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I won't buy any pans from Mattfer Bourgeat. Period. Now, can you tell me which is the cheapest pan from all other brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price = (SELECT price FROM all_pans WHERE brand <> 'Matfer Bourgeat' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1);"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_356", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Will the stainless steel surface of this saucepan discolor or react with food, altering flavors?", "long_answer": "The saucepan's stainless steel surface is constructed to resist discoloration and to avoid reacting with food, thus ensuring that it does not alter the taste of the food cooked in it, leading to professional cooking outcomes.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_265", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm looking for something in green or copper that's bigger than your average pan. Got anything that fits that description?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"copper\") AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"copper\") AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('green', 'copper') AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans);"}}
{"id": "search_qa_266", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I am only interested in ZWILLING J.A. Henckels pans that are larger than 12 inches. Can you find it for me?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' AND size > 12;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_267", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm doing a lot of high-heat cooking and need a tough pan. What's the product ID of the Norpro brand pan that can withstand a temperature of at least 600°F?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND brand = \"Norpro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND brand = \"Norpro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Norpro' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_93", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Do I need to carry out any specific cleaning or maintenance duties for these pans?", "long_answer": "Indeed, as these pans are unsuitable for the dishwasher, they will need routine seasoning if they're made of cast iron or carbon steel, or occasional polishing to preserve their look and functionality.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" do not have a function of self-maintenance and will need regular seasoning (for cast iron or carbon steel) or polishing (for aesthetic reasons) to maintain their best condition.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_357", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Can this pan be used to make both bread loaves and sandwich buns?", "long_answer": "The pan is versatile and well-suited for baking a variety of items, including both bread loaves and homemade sandwich buns or rolls, making it an excellent tool for home bakers aiming for professional-grade results.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_358", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the broiler pan suitable for roasting vegetables?", "long_answer": "Yes, the broiler pan is a versatile cooking tool that is not just for broiling meats and fish but is also suitable for roasting vegetables.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_359", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Does the non-stick feature of this cookware maintain its effectiveness over time with proper care?", "long_answer": "The durability of the non-stick feature is dependent on proper care and usage; it tends to hold up well when exposed to low to medium heat settings and when proper cleaning methods are applied. However, some customers have reported a decrease in non-stick performance after prolonged use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_268", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm not a fan of Presto and I do a lot of high heat cooking. Point me to the pan from any other brand that can withstand the highest oven temperature.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Presto' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_360", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is the non-stick surface of this pan effective enough to cook with little or no oil?", "long_answer": "The pan boasts a high-quality non-stick surface that allows customers to cook using less oil than they would with traditional pans, and some customers report that they can cook without using any oil at all.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_361", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the non-stick coating on this pot exhibit long-term durability with proper care?", "long_answer": "The non-stick coating on the pot is of high quality and is known to be durable when maintained correctly, which includes recommendations from users to avoid using metal utensils and to handle the coating with care to ensure its longevity.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_269", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm in the need of a big pan, more than 12 inches at least. Specifically, I'm looking for one from USA Pan. Got anything like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand = \"USA Pan\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand = \"USA Pan\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand = 'USA Pan';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_94", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is it safe to use high heat to sear meats with this pan?", "long_answer": "No, this pan should not be used for cooking techniques that require extremely high temperatures, such as searing meats, as the sensitive non-stick surface may become compromised. For cooking at high temperatures, you should opt for pans without non-stick surfaces, such as those made from cast iron or stainless steel.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with delicate non-stick coatings cannot be used for cooking methods that involve metal utensils or very high heat, to avoid damaging the surface.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_362", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Does the Tramontina fry pan come with a warranty?", "long_answer": "The Tramontina fry pan comes with a Lifetime Warranty, indicating that the manufacturer covers the product for its lifetime, given that the user adheres to the proper use and care instructions provided.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_363", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the T-fal pot suitable for both frying and stir-frying?", "long_answer": "The T-fal pot is considered suitable for various cooking methods and is particularly good for frying and stir-frying as reported by customers who have used it for such purposes, including food items that involve stirring in sauces.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_364", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the T-fal E93897 Fry Pan allow cooking eggs without them sticking to the surface?", "long_answer": "Yes, the T-fal E93897 Fry Pan has been reported by numerous customers to be effective in cooking eggs without them sticking, making it possible to cook without the need for added oils.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_95", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is this pan compatible with my induction cooktop?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the pan will function effectively on an induction stovetop, provided it's constructed from a magnetic-grade material. Its circular design favors compatibility across various types of stovetops, encompassing those with induction technology.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_270", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I've had great experiences with both Presto and Bialetti, but I'm not looking to spend more than 20 bucks this time. Do you have any pans from those brands within my price range?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Bialetti\") AND price <= 20 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Presto\", \"Bialetti\") AND price <= 20 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (brand = 'Presto' OR brand = 'Bialetti') AND price <= 20;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_365", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the saucepan's base provide even heat distribution?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed with an aluminum encapsulated base which ensures quick heating and distributes the heat evenly across the surface, effectively eliminating the existence of hot spots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_271", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm a nut for T-fal and Chicago Metallic. Can you tell me the cheapest pan you got from either of those brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Chicago Metallic\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Chicago Metallic\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Chicago Metallic\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('T-fal', 'Chicago Metallic') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_272", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I need a blue pan, at least 8 inches in size. Do you got something like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND color = \"blue\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND color = \"blue\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND color = 'blue';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_366", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the handle of the crepe and pancake pan crafted to facilitate the easy flipping of food?", "long_answer": "The pan's handle is specifically designed with the intention of providing user comfort during the cooking process, especially for tasks like the easy tossing and flipping of delicate items such as crepes and pancakes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_96", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I enjoy preparing omelets; would this pan be appropriate for that?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the pan's circular design facilitates uniform heat distribution throughout its surface, which is perfect for preparing delicate dishes such as omelets, assuring they are cooked evenly and softly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_367", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Can stainless steel be used safely for broiling and other high-heat cooking methods?", "long_answer": "Stainless steel is suitable for use in high-heat cooking methods, including broiling, due to its resilience and ability to maintain food safety at elevated temperatures.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_368", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this pan due to its interior coating?", "long_answer": "The pan is coated with Prometal Pro nonstick material, which is highly durable and resistant to scratches. As a result, it is designed to be safely used with metal utensils.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_369", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "What type of warranty is included with the USA Pan Bakeware bread pan?", "long_answer": "The USA Pan Bakeware bread pan includes a limited lifetime warranty, indicating the company's commitment to the longevity and performance of their product.", "short_answer": "limited lifetime warranty", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_273", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I need a decent sized pan but it's gotta be either Tramontina or Chicago Metallic. What's the smallest one you've got that is at least average size?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Chicago Metallic\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Chicago Metallic\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand in ('Tramontina', 'Chicago Metallic') AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY size ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_274", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Look, I need an Anolon pan that's at least 10 inches. Can you tell me if you have one in stock?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand = \"Anolon\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand = \"Anolon\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Anolon' AND size >= 10;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_275", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I've only got $30, and I've had enough of these Ozeri pans. Give me the best pan you've got that fits my budget.. but it can't be an Ozeri!", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Ozeri' AND price <= 30 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_97", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Do I need to invest significant time in the care of this pan post-cooking?", "long_answer": "Stainless steel pans necessitate some effort for upkeep. Regular polishing is required to remedy any discoloration and preserve their luster, meaning a time investment is necessary after cooking to maintain them in top-notch condition.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with stainless steel material are not suitable for those seeking the easiest maintenance, as they can develop discoloration and require regular polishing to keep their appearance pristine.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "stainless steel", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_370", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Does the 17-inch measurement in the product details accurately reflect the cooking surface size?", "long_answer": "The 17 inches described in the product details refer to the overall size of the product, including the handles. This has led to confusion among some customers who anticipated the cooking surface itself to be 17 inches. It is important for potential buyers to carefully review the measurements to ensure it meets their specific requirements.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_371", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "What is the weight characteristic of the pan based on its construction material?", "long_answer": "The pan, constructed with heavy-gauge aluminum, tends to be on the heavier side compared to other pans. Its weight contributes to both fast, even heating and increased stability during cooking.", "short_answer": "heavy", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_276", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I ain't cooking with Anolon pans anymore. Can you get me the pan with the highest oven safe temperature that's not Anolon brand?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Anolon\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Anolon\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Anolon\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Anolon' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_277", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I need a pan that's at least 8 inches. It's gotta be a Cuisinart though. Show me the least expensive one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND brand = \"Cuisinart\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND brand = \"Cuisinart\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND brand = \"Cuisinart\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Cuisinart' AND size >= 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_278", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm tired of my small pans and need something bigger, like over 8 inches. But I'm only interested in those in silver or black. Dig up the cheapest pan that meets these requirements, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND (color = 'silver' OR color = 'black') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_372", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Are metal utensils likely to scratch the Bialetti pan's non-stick coating?", "long_answer": "Metal utensils are known to be harmful to non-stick surfaces and are not recommended for use with Bialetti pans. To maintain the integrity of the non-stick coating, it is better to use utensils made of nylon, silicone, or wood.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_279", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm trying to upgrade my kitchen and I only trust Lodge and Chicago Metallic for quality. Find me the cheapest pan bigger than 12 inches from these brands.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"Chicago Metallic\") AND size > 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"Chicago Metallic\") AND size > 12 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"Chicago Metallic\") AND size > 12 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Lodge', 'Chicago Metallic') AND size > 12 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_373", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is this Lodge cast iron skillet suitable for cooking over an open campfire?", "long_answer": "Yes, the Lodge cast iron skillet is suitable for use over an open campfire because its heavy-duty construction allows it to withstand high temperatures and adapt to the uneven surfaces typically encountered during outdoor cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_280", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm after a big pan, something larger than a foot. Do you have any from Norpro or Tramontina?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"Tramontina\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"Tramontina\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (brand = 'Norpro' OR brand = 'Tramontina') AND size > 12;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_281", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm a serious cooker and need a pan that can stand the heat, higher than the average, but I'm not made of money. What's the most affordable one you got with a higher than average oven safe temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_98", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is it safe to use high heat to sear meats with this pan?", "long_answer": "This pan is unsuitable for cooking techniques that require extremely high temperatures, like meat searing, as the sensitive non-stick surface may become compromised. For such high-temperature culinary applications, it would be advisable to opt for a pan bereft of non-stick layers, such as one made of cast iron or stainless steel.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with delicate non-stick coatings cannot be used for cooking methods that involve metal utensils or very high heat, to avoid damaging the surface.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_99", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is this pan suitable for use under a broiler?", "long_answer": "No, you should refrain from using this non-stick frying pan under a broiler as the extreme heat may damage the non-stick surface. It is advisable to opt for pans that are designed to be broiler-safe when you intend to broil your food.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with delicate non-stick coatings cannot be used for cooking methods that involve metal utensils or very high heat, to avoid damaging the surface.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_282", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I'm cooking up a storm in a large kitchen, so none of those puny pans for me. Also, I'm not a fan of copper color. Give me a pan that’s larger than average and is the cheapest you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND NOT color = \"copper\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND NOT color = \"copper\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND NOT color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'copper' AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_283", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm looking for a big pan but can't stand anything from ZWILLING J.A. Henckels. Show me the largest pan you got that isn't from that brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand NOT LIKE 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_100", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm usually in a hurry and prefer not to spend too much time on cleaning. Does this pan suit my lifestyle?", "long_answer": "Since the pan in question is not suitable for dishwasher cleaning, it necessitates delicate hand-washing and prompt drying after every use. Should you typically be short on time and favor swift clean-up procedures, you may wish to look into an alternative pan that is dishwasher-safe to align more closely with your daily routine.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are not recommended for use by consumers who may not be willing or able to invest the time and effort into the careful maintenance these pans require, which includes correct hand-washing techniques and immediate drying to prevent damage.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_374", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is this non-stick saucepan suitable for cooking acidic foods without damaging the coating?", "long_answer": "This saucepan features a non-stick interior that can handle acidic foods effectively, provided the coating is properly maintained and exposure to highly acidic substances is not prolonged.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_284", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm looking for a large pan, it's gotta be bigger than 12 inches. But please, no Ozeri brand. Gimme the first one that fits these conditions.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand != 'Ozeri' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_101", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I need a pan that's versatile enough for both simmering soups and frying. Would this type be suitable for my needs?", "long_answer": "A saucepan, with its tall sides and design optimal for liquid-based cooking, is perfect for simmering soups and sauces. However, when it comes to frying, it's less than ideal. A pan with shorter sides that can withstand direct, intense heat contact with food would serve better for frying purposes.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan cannot be used for high-heat searing or frying due to their high sides and design focusing more on liquid-based cooking methods.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_285", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm on the hunt for a Tramontina pan that won't break the bank - gotta keep it under 10 dollars. Can you pick out the one that can withstand the highest oven temperature for me?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand = \"Tramontina\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand = \"Tramontina\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand = \"Tramontina\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Tramontina' AND price < 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_375", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is the tempered glass lid prone to shattering when used in the oven or on the stove?", "long_answer": "While there have been isolated reports of the tempered glass lid shattering, it is important to adhere to the recommended temperature guidelines to minimize the risk of thermal shock and potential shattering.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_376", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Does the Stone Earth Pan require seasoning before its initial use?", "long_answer": "According to the instructions provided with the Stone Earth Pan, it is recommended to coat the pan lightly with oil before using it for the first time to enhance its non-stick performance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_377", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Does the design of this saucepan allow for efficient use of cupboard space?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed with a tall and narrow structure, and without an extra helper handle, which enables it to occupy a smaller footprint in the cupboard, potentially making it a space-efficient choice for storage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_378", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "What type of warranty is included with this Bialetti cookware pan?", "long_answer": "Although the warranty specifics are not provided in the given information, Bialetti cookware commonly includes a manufacturer's warranty. However, it is advised to consult the retailer or manufacturer directly to obtain the precise details of the warranty policy.", "short_answer": "manufacturer's warranty", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_379", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does cooking acidic foods like tomato sauce in this nonstick pan affect its nonstick surface?", "long_answer": "Cooking acidic foods such as tomato sauce in this nonstick pan is generally not reported to cause issues by the majority of users; however, it is advisable to limit prolonged exposure of the nonstick surface to highly acidic ingredients to maintain its integrity.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_286", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I don't want some fancy colored pans, just show me your cheapest silver or copper one.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"copper\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"copper\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"copper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('silver', 'copper') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_102", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Does regular use reduce the hygiene benefits of my pan?", "long_answer": "The inherent antimicrobial properties of copper-infused pans ensure that their hygiene benefits are not diminished through regular use. This is due to copper's natural capacity to diminish the presence of bacteria and other pathogens.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with copper material feature natural antimicrobial properties that can help reduce the presence of bacteria and other germs on the surface of the cookware.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "copper", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_287", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I do a lot of high-heat cooking and need a pan that can take the heat, it has to be bigger than 8 inches though. Find me your cheapest pan that meets these requirements.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND size >= 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND size >= 8 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND size >= 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 \nORDER BY price ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_380", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the saucepan considered comfortably lightweight for handling?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is regarded by customers as having a comfortable weight balancing lightness and sufficient heft, making it easy to handle.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_103", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Could using a dishwasher to clean the pan pose a risk of it warping?", "long_answer": "Using a dishwasher to clean this pan poses no substantial risk of warping. It is constructed from materials that are specifically selected for their resilience to the heat and water pressure experienced inside a dishwasher, ensuring the pan retains its shape.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_288", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm all about copper pans and the bigger the better. Get me the largest copper pan you guys sell.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_104", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is there a risk of hot spots when I sauté vegetables in this pan?", "long_answer": "No, experiencing hot spots when sautéing vegetables is unlikely because the pan's rounded design is celebrated for its even heat distribution, essential for perfectly cooked vegetables during the sauté process.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_105", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is this pan capable of withstanding high-temperature cooking, such as searing a steak?", "long_answer": "No, this pan is not the ideal choice for high-temperature cooking, like searing a steak. Constructed from aluminum, it doesn't possess the requisite tolerance for high heat needed for these methods, and it might not retain its shape when exposed to the extreme temperatures that are easily handled by stainless steel or cast iron pans.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's lack of high heat tolerance lack the capability to withstand searing and broiling applications that require maintaining structural integrity at very high temperatures, unlike cookware made of materials like stainless steel or cast iron.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_289", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I've got a big family dinner coming up and need a pan that can handle a high heat of over 400F in the oven, but make it something else than silver. What's the biggest one you got that will do the job?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND NOT color = \"silver\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND NOT color = \"silver\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND NOT color = \"silver\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND color != 'silver' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_106", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Will this pan ensure even cooking of my food on all types of stoves?", "long_answer": "Our aluminum and copper frying pans and skillets are renowned for their superior heat distribution, ensuring uniform cooking. Nevertheless, when using an induction stove, take into account that these materials lack inherent magnetic qualities, making them incompatible with induction heating. To avoid impaired cooking performance, you'll need a ferrous plate to enable proper induction.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_107", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Should I implement any specific precautions when cleaning this pan in a dishwasher?", "long_answer": "This pan doesn't require any special handling. It's designed to withstand the demanding conditions of a dishwasher, being safe for cleaning without suffering damage from heat or detergents.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute feature resistance to both the high temperatures and strong chemicals typical in dishwashers, which ensures they do not warp, rust, or degrade quickly when exposed to such conditions regularly.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_381", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Does the Copper Chef pan require frequent polishing to prevent oxidation or tarnishing?", "long_answer": "The Copper Chef pan is engineered to resist oxidization and tarnishing, thereby eliminating the need for regular polishing like some traditional copper cookware.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_290", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Look, I don't have more than 20 dollars to spend on a pan, but I need as big a size as I can get. Can you find me the biggest pan that meets that price?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_291", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I ain't got more than 50 dollars to throw at a pan, but I need one that can handle high heat, ya know, like over 600 degrees Fahrenheit. What's the biggest one you got that'll do the job?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_382", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Can the Madeleine Pan be cleaned in a dishwasher without damaging it?", "long_answer": "The Madeleine Pan is indeed dishwasher safe. However, to prolong its lifespan and preserve the non-stick coating, hand-washing the pan is favored.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_383", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set suitable for use in both regular and toaster ovens?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is designed to be versatile, suitable for use in both traditional ovens and toaster ovens. This compatibility allows users to employ the set for various cooking methods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_108", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Can this pan withstand frequent cycles if I consistently clean my kitchenware in the dishwasher?", "long_answer": "Certainly. This pan is designed to withstand frequent use. It is built to resist the high temperatures and harsh chemical detergents commonly found in dishwashers, ensuring it won't warp, rust, or deteriorate quickly, even with daily machine washing.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute feature resistance to both the high temperatures and strong chemicals typical in dishwashers, which ensures they do not warp, rust, or degrade quickly when exposed to such conditions regularly.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_109", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Is there any specialized equipment required to utilize this pan on various stove types?", "long_answer": "If you are transitioning between various kinds of stovetops, our aluminum and copper frying pans are suitable for use on gas, electric, and glass-ceramic ranges. However, for induction cooktops, you must use an additional ferrous plate to facilitate interaction with the induction system, as these substances are not magnetically responsive.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_384", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is it advisable to use cooking sprays on these non-stick pans?", "long_answer": "It is not advisable to use cooking sprays on these non-stick pans, as they can cause a build-up that may deteriorate the pan's non-stick performance over time. It is recommended to use a small amount of oil or butter to maintain the quality of the pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_385", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is the cast iron skillet designed to be used over an open flame, such as while grilling or camping?", "long_answer": "The cast iron skillet is indeed designed to withstand the heat from an open flame, and because of its durability and heat tolerance, it is an excellent choice for outdoor cooking during activities like grilling or camping.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_386", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "How well does the pan handle sticky foods such as eggs or pancakes?", "long_answer": "According to customer feedback, the pan is highly effective in handling foods that are prone to sticking, allowing sticky foods like eggs and pancakes to be removed with ease.", "short_answer": "very well", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_387", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does the pan's handle remain cool to the touch, or is a pot holder required during use?", "long_answer": "The pan's handle is constructed of an extra-strong steel strip, which can become heated with use, necessitating the use of a pot holder or towel to handle the pan comfortably and safely.", "short_answer": "pot holder required", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_388", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils when cooking with this cast iron skillet?", "long_answer": "Metal utensils can be used with cast iron skillets, yet it's recommended to employ them cautiously to prevent damaging the protective seasoning layer. Opting for wooden or silicone utensils may be a better choice to avoid scratching.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_389", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Does the Stone Earth Pan come with any warranty or satisfaction guarantee?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Pan comes with a satisfaction guarantee according to the product description, which suggests the company is confident in its product. The details of a warranty, if any, would need to be confirmed by contacting the manufacturer directly.", "short_answer": "satisfaction guarantee", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_292", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm a die-hard fan of Bialetti and Copper Chef. Which is the largest pan available from these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal` with asin: B000S6I4ZE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Copper Chef\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Copper Chef\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Copper Chef\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Bialetti', 'Copper Chef') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_293", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm no regular cook but I sometimes go hard. I need a pan that can stand 600 degrees or more in the oven. And it's gotta be either green or silver. What do you recommend?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND color IN (\"green\", \"silver\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND color IN (\"green\", \"silver\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND (color = 'green' OR color = 'silver');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_390", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the saucepan's Flavor Lock Lid create an effective seal to retain moisture and nutrients during cooking?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is equipped with a Flavor Lock Lid, which is specifically designed to provide a tight seal. This functionality is instrumental in sealing in moisture and nutrients, which contributes to healthier and more flavorful cooking outcomes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_294", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm a big fan of Presto, got any pans from them? Just need one for now.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Presto\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Presto\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Presto' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_295", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I'm picky about my pans and only want stuff from Bialetti or USA Pan. On top of that, it has to be black. So pull up the first product that fits these demands, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"USA Pan\") AND color = \"black\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"USA Pan\") AND color = \"black\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Bialetti', 'USA Pan') AND color = 'black' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_391", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is there a discount available for the Presto 5900 Electric Wok on Amazon.com?", "long_answer": "As of the latest information, Amazon.com is running a promotion that provides a 5% discount on the purchase of the Presto 5900 Electric Wok. Customers can access this discount through the \"Clip this coupon\" section on the product's page, although certain terms and conditions may apply.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_392", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Are the handles of this pot designed to resist high temperatures without becoming loose?", "long_answer": "The pot features ergonomically designed handles to provide comfort and safety; however, feedback from some customers indicates that the handles may become loose over time, especially if exposed to very high temperatures for long durations. Thus, caution is recommended when handling the pot under such conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_296", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Green is definitely not my color. Could you find me the largest pan you have that's not green?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'green' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_110", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Can I safely place this pan in the dishwasher with my other dishes, or is it better to wash it on its own?", "long_answer": "Hand washing this pan is recommended since some dishwasher detergents may be overly abrasive for aluminum pans, especially if they have non-stick surfaces or are anodized, potentially impacting their durability and functionality.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's specific maintenance needs fail to meet the requirements for indiscriminate cleaning methods such as harsh scouring pads or certain dishwasher detergents, especially if they have a non-stick layer or are anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_297", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I can't stand copper stuff. Find me a Norpro pan that comes in a different color.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches` with asin: B0012BR1XU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" AND brand = \"Norpro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" AND brand = \"Norpro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Norpro' AND color != 'copper';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_111", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Can this pan easily fit within the constraints of my small kitchen that has limited storage options?", "long_answer": "Considering that round-shaped pans may not maximize the use of space in a compact kitchen when trying to accommodate them in square or irregularly-shaped areas, it's crucial to evaluate the pan's storage efficiency. If space constraints are a significant issue, it could be advantageous to seek out pans of different shapes that better conform to the available storage in your kitchen.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_298", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm not looking to blow a lot of cash, just need a pan that can handle the heat better than most. What's the cheapest pan you got that can withstand an above average oven safe temperature and doesn't cost more than 20 dollars?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND price <= 20 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND price <= 20 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_393", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Do customers find the interior measurement markings on this cookware to be accurate and useful for cooking?", "long_answer": "The interior measurement markings on the cookware have received positive feedback from customers, who report that they are both accurate and useful for achieving precision in their cooking endeavors and following recipes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_394", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Can the Matfer Bourgeat pan be safely used in an oven?", "long_answer": "The Matfer Bourgeat pan is designed to be oven-safe, as confirmed by users who have transitioned the pan from stovetop to oven without any issues.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_299", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I don't have time for complicated new brands, just give me a product id for a T-fal pan.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'T-fal' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_395", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is the pan effective at cooking eggs without them sticking to the surface?", "long_answer": "Assuming the pan is seasoned appropriately, customers commonly indicate that it performs well in cooking eggs with little to no sticking on the surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_396", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Do the metal handles of the pan become hot when cooking for extended periods?", "long_answer": "During prolonged cooking sessions, the metal handles of the pan are prone to heating up, necessitating caution and the use of pot holders to handle them safely.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_397", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is this skillet suitable for deep frying due to its capacity and depth?", "long_answer": "The skillet is indeed suitable for deep frying, thanks to its 3 qt capacity and depth which provide sufficient space and volume for the oil and items being fried.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_300", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I've had it with Tramontina. Get me a different brand pan size bigger than 8 inches. And make it the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" AND size > 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" AND size > 8 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" AND size > 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Tramontina' AND size > 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_398", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the lid of the pot have built-in strainer features?", "long_answer": "The pot's lid includes two sets of holes designed to facilitate the straining of contents directly from the pot, which enhances convenience during various cooking tasks.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_301", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm after products from Chicago Metallic. Give me the ID of one of their pans, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Chicago Metallic' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_302", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I do a lot of high-heat cooking in large pans, oven-safe up to 500 degrees Fahrenheit. What's the most affordable pan you've got that's over 10 inches?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size > 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size > 10 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size > 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_399", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Can this pan be used on an induction cooktop?", "long_answer": "This pan is not designed to work with induction cooktops. It is explicitly made for traditional cooking surfaces like electric, gas, ceramic, and glass stovetops.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_303", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I'm only interested in Anolon and T-fal brands for pans, but they gotta handle more heat than the average pan. Got any like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"T-fal\") AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"T-fal\") AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Anolon', 'T-fal') AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans);"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_400", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is it safe to cook with high heat on this non-stick pan?", "long_answer": "It is not recommended to use high heat with most non-stick cookware, including this pan, as doing so may compromise the non-stick surface and could lead to warping or other forms of damage to the pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_401", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does the handle of the Bialetti fry pan remain cool to touch while cooking?", "long_answer": "The handle on the Bialetti fry pan is specifically crafted to resist heat and to stay cool, ensuring a comfortable grip throughout the cooking process due to its heat-resistant design coupled with an extra-long soft-touch.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_112", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is it sufficient to simply wash this pan with soap and water, or does it have specific cleaning instructions?", "long_answer": "Stainless steel pans require more than just soap and water for cleaning since they can become discolored over time. To maintain their appearance, it is necessary to polish them regularly in addition to your standard cleaning regimen, something to bear in mind if you prefer to avoid additional upkeep.", "short_answer": "specific cleaning needed", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with stainless steel material are not suitable for those seeking the easiest maintenance, as they can develop discoloration and require regular polishing to keep their appearance pristine.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "stainless steel", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_402", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Can the edges of this pan cause injury due to sharpness?", "long_answer": "The pan's edges have been reported by some customers to be somewhat sharp, suggesting that caution should be exercised when handling the pan to prevent possible injury.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_403", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the saucepan's rim prevent dripping while pouring?", "long_answer": "The saucepan features a specially tapered rim that is designed to ensure a drip-free pouring experience, thereby preventing messes and spills when transferring liquids.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_404", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Does the exterior of the stainless-steel wok heat up when cooking?", "long_answer": "The outside of the wok, being made of stainless steel, is subject to heating up when the wok is used for cooking. Therefore, caution is necessary when handling the wok, and it is recommended to use its loop handles to move it safely.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_405", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is a convex center normal in a Copper Chef pan?", "long_answer": "A Copper Chef pan is designed to have a flat bottom to enable even cooking. A convex center is indicative of a deformity, possibly from manufacturing, and is not considered normal.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_406", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Where is the Cuisinart French Classic cookware line manufactured?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart French Classic cookware line is manufactured in France, which is well-received by customers for its craftsmanship and quality.", "short_answer": "France", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_407", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Can the T-fal pan be safely used for searing and sautéing?", "long_answer": "The T-fal pan is designed to accommodate various cooking techniques, such as searing and sautéing. It is equipped with a Thermo-Spot heat indicator, which ensures that the pan is properly pre-heated for optimal cooking performance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_113", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm concerned about chemicals from the dishwasher potentially impacting the material of the pan. Is this a legitimate worry?", "long_answer": "You needn't concern yourself with the chemicals in dishwasher detergent impacting this pan. It is crafted from materials that can withstand the typical chemicals present in dishwasher cleaning agents, thus preserving its integrity through numerous wash cycles.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_408", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is this wok compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "This wok is specifically made as an electric appliance, meaning it operates independently by plugging into an electrical outlet and is not compatible with induction cooktops or any other type of stovetop.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_409", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Can this wok be used to prepare meals for multiple people?", "long_answer": "This wok boasts a large capacity that is affirmed by numerous customers to be appropriate for creating substantially sized meals designed to serve several individuals.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_410", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is this skillet suitable for baking bread and achieving a crispy crust?", "long_answer": "This skillet can be used for baking bread, and it is especially effective at yielding a golden, crispy crust because it retains and distributes heat excellently.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_411", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the nonstick coating on this pan a good balance of cost and durability?", "long_answer": "The majority of customers are satisfied that the pan provides a strong balance between price, quality, and performance. Ensuring the pan is cared for properly may contribute to a longer life, enhancing this balance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_114", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is this pan a good choice if I seek cookware that requires minimal upkeep?", "long_answer": "No, if you desire low-maintenance cookware, a pan with a cast iron lid may not be the most suitable option. Such a lid demands diligent upkeep to avoid rust, necessitating thorough drying and regular oiling after each use, which can be more laborious than the care needed for other materials.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a cast iron lid lack the capability to be washed in a dishwasher or left to soak without proper drying and oiling as this can lead to rust formation, requiring more hands-on maintenance compared to some other materials used for lids.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "cast iron lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_412", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is the pan suitable for evenly baking artisan bread and facilitating easy release?", "long_answer": "The pan is highly regarded for its proficiency in baking artisan bread, as it delivers even heat distribution and provides an easy release of the loaves, which are essential elements for artisan bread making.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_304", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm loyal to USA Pan and Chicago Metallic brands. Give me the first product you got from either of these brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Chicago Metallic\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Chicago Metallic\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('USA Pan', 'Chicago Metallic') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_115", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is this pan suitable for use under a broiler?", "long_answer": "No, it is not advisable to use this non-stick frying pan under a broiler as the high temperatures can damage the non-stick surface. It is preferable to opt for pans that are designated as broiler-safe when broiling is required.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with delicate non-stick coatings cannot be used for cooking methods that involve metal utensils or very high heat, to avoid damaging the surface.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_116", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I enjoy preparing omelets; would this pan be appropriate for that task?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the pan's circular design promotes a uniform heat distribution throughout its surface, which is optimal for preparing sensitive dishes such as omelets, guaranteeing a consistent and gentle cooking process.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_305", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm all about the environment, man. Give me the biggest green pan you've got, but it's gotta be at least 12 inches.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" AND size >= 12 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" AND size >= 12 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'green' AND size >= 12 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_306", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm trying to scoff up a pan larger than 12 inches, and I don't want it in green. Find me the cheapest one you have that meets these requirements.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND NOT color = \"green\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND NOT color = \"green\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND NOT color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND color <> 'green' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_117", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is there a risk of hot spots occurring when I sauté vegetables in this pan?", "long_answer": "No, you should not encounter hot spots when sautéing vegetables since the pan's round shape is designed to distribute heat uniformly, which is essential for obtaining evenly cooked vegetables during sautéing.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_413", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is it necessary to apply grease or baking paper when using this non-stick pan?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed with an efficient non-stick coating, which most customers find eliminates the need for greasing or using baking paper. However, certain users may choose to apply a light coating of butter or cooking spray for added assurance against sticking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_414", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the Bialetti saute pan designed to distribute heat evenly across its surface?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti saute pan features a heavy-gauge bottom which is specifically designed to ensure that heat is distributed evenly, providing a uniform cooking experience.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_415", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "What is the maximum number of Madeleines that can be baked simultaneously with this Madeleine pan?", "long_answer": "This Madeleine pan is designed with 12 shell-shaped cups, allowing a baker to prepare up to 12 Madeleines in a single baking session.", "short_answer": "12", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_118", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is this cookware readily recyclable when it comes time for replacement?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this cookware is readily recyclable upon the need for replacement. Constructed from aluminum, these pans are ideal for recycling efforts and can be reprocessed numerous times, consuming less energy.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's environmental considerations are not recommended for those who prefer to minimize their environmental footprint through recyclable and sustainable cookware options, highlighting aluminum's advantage as it can be recycled effectively.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_416", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the Cuisinart saucepan equipped with a nonstick coating?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart saucepan is constructed from stainless steel and lacks a nonstick coating, making it more suitable for traditional cooking methods that may be better suited to stainless steel than nonstick surfaces.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_307", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm trying to get my hands on a Matfer Bourgeat pan without breaking the bank. Got anything under 50 bucks?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Matfer Bourgeat' AND price < 50;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_417", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is the reinforced nonstick coating on the product prone to flaking with correct usage and maintenance?", "long_answer": "The product's reinforced nonstick coating is engineered for durability and is not prone to flaking under proper use and care. Ensuring the use of appropriate utensils and cleaning techniques will mitigate the risk of the nonstick coating flaking off.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_418", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the pan dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be dishwasher safe, which allows for easy and convenient cleaning after use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_419", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the All-Clad frying pan resistant to warping?", "long_answer": "The All-Clad frying pan is designed with a 3-ply construction, which gives it resistance to warping. Nonetheless, to maintain this warp-resistant quality, it's advisable not to subject the pan to sudden temperature changes or heat it when it's empty.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_420", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is it safe to use an adapter with the Presto 5900 electric wok?", "long_answer": "The manufacturer does not recommend using the Presto 5900 electric wok with an adapter since it's designed specifically for 120 volts, 60 Hz electrical systems. Using an adapter could not only damage the wok but also present potential safety risks.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_421", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is the pan's handle capable of withstanding high oven temperatures?", "long_answer": "The pan is equipped with a high-quality, extra-strong steel strip handle designed specifically to endure high temperatures, ensuring the handle's durability and safety both on the stovetop and inside an oven.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_422", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Can this wok be used to cook stir-fry meals that contain sauces without burning or sticking?", "long_answer": "The wok is capable of cooking a wide range of stir-fry dishes, including those with sauces. For optimal cooking performance and to prevent burning or sticking of foods, it is recommended to control the heat appropriately and apply a small amount of oil.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_308", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I need a new pan but I only have 20 dollars and I really want it in blue. Can you find a match for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND color = \"blue\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND color = \"blue\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND color = 'blue';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_423", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Can using this pan on high heat cause it to warp?", "long_answer": "Using the pan on high heat has led to warping according to reports from some users; therefore, it is recommended to cook with moderate heat to prevent such damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_309", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm looking for a big copper pan that can endure at least 400 degree oven heat. What's the largest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_119", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Should I buy this pan, will it maintain its surface integrity without the need for extra treatments?", "long_answer": "No, pans containing copper can undergo changes in their surface quality over time due to tarnishing without further treatments like polishing and re-tinning.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with copper material are not recommended for long-term durability without proper maintenance since copper can tarnish and may require re-tinning of interior linings over time to preserve their functional qualities.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "copper", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_424", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is this pot safe for oven use, and if so, what is the maximum temperature it can withstand?", "long_answer": "This pot is designed to be oven-safe, allowing for stovetop to oven transitions, with a maximum temperature tolerance of up to 350 degrees Fahrenheit.", "short_answer": "yes, 350°F", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_310", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I'm trying to upgrade my kitchen gear, alright? Get me the highest temperature resistant pan y'all got, provided it's green or copper-tone and bigger than your 'average' size.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND color IN (\"green\", \"copper\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND color IN (\"green\", \"copper\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND color IN (\"green\", \"copper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('green', 'copper') \nAND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_311", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I've narrowed my choices down to Norpro and USA Pan. Can you tell me which one of their pans is the least expensive?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches` with asin: B0012BR1XU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"USA Pan\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"USA Pan\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"USA Pan\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Norpro', 'USA Pan') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_312", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I cook a lot and I need a pan that can take the heat. This thing has to be at least 8 inches and can endure at least 450F in the oven. What's my best option?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_313", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I've got this thing for big pans, at least 8 inches, and I only buy T-fal or Bialetti. What's the first product you can recommend?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal` with asin: B000S6I4ZE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Bialetti\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Bialetti\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND (brand = 'T-fal' OR brand = 'Bialetti') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_314", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Look, I'm a bit of a brand snob and I need an Anolon pan. But it has to be bigger than 8 inches. Get me the details of such a product if you have it.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Anolon\" AND size > 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Anolon\" AND size > 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Anolon' AND size > 8;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_425", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "How durable is the non-stick surface of the pan with proper care?", "long_answer": "The non-stick surface of the pan is considered durable by customers when the pan is properly cared for, which includes using suitable utensils and cleaning methods to preserve the non-stick coating's effectiveness over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_315", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm looking for a sizeable, non-copper pan. Find me your largest pan that's 12 inches or over, but make sure it's not copper ok?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND NOT color = \"copper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND NOT color = \"copper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND color != 'copper' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_316", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I ain't too fond of grey, but I need a pan that can take the heat, at least 450°F. What's the cheapest one you got that fits my needs?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND NOT color = \"grey\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND NOT color = \"grey\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND NOT color = \"grey\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'grey' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_426", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Does the handle of this cookware remain cool during typical cooking conditions?", "long_answer": "The handle is crafted to be slip-resistant and is designed to remain cool under typical cooking conditions. However, there is a possibility that the handle could become hot, so caution should always be exercised.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_317", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I ain't paying a penny over 50 bucks for a pan. But it sure as hell needs to withstand high oven temperatures. So show me the one that can handle the most heat within my budget.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_318", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm not a fan of grey colored pans. Find me the cheapest non-grey pan you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"grey\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"grey\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"grey\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'grey' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_427", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are lids included in the Green Earth Frying Pan set by Ozeri?", "long_answer": "The Green Earth Frying Pan set by Ozeri does not come with lids as part of the set, but certain customers have discovered that lids from different pan sets can fit these pans.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_319", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm cooking for a whole troop and I'll need sizable pans. Get me the most affordable pan that's larger than 10 inches.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_320", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm doing some serious cooking and need a pan that can withstand at least 600F. Has Cuisinart got anything like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND brand = \"Cuisinart\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND brand = \"Cuisinart\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Cuisinart' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_321", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I need a pan that can handle high heat, at least 500 degrees F. It's either Cuisinart or Matfer Bourgeat for me. What's the first one that comes up?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Cuisinart', 'Matfer Bourgeat') AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_428", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Will the pan likely change color as it ages and is used more frequently?", "long_answer": "With regular use, it is common for the pan to experience discoloration. However, this discoloration can typically be remedied by using the appropriate cleaning methods and products.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_429", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with the T-fal Professional pan?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Professional pan is designed with a Prometal Pro nonstick interior that is highly durable and resistant to scratches, thereby allowing the use of metal utensils without damaging the surface. Despite this durability, it is recommended to handle the utensils carefully to extend the lifespan of the pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_430", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Does the saucepan's handle have a feature that allows it to be hung for storage?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed with a bright chrome handle that is equipped with hanging holes, which enables the saucepan to be hung up for convenient storage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_322", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that's at least 8 inches, but I ain't paying more than 50 dollars for it. Point me to the cheapest one you got that's the right size.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND price < 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND price < 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND price <= 50 \nORDER BY price ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_431", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Does the wok have a stable base that prevents it from tipping over?", "long_answer": "The wok is designed with rubberized feet that ensure its base remains stable during use, as confirmed by positive feedback from customers who have purchased and used the wok.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_323", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm not looking to drop too much cash, and I'll only trust All-Clad or ZWILLING J.A. Henckels. Show me the cheapest pan you have from them that's under 20 bucks.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('All-Clad', 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels') AND price < 20 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_324", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm after a big pan, either green or blue. Which is the largest one you've got in those colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('green', 'blue') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_432", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is this pan suitable for baking a variety of baked goods beyond its primary intended use?", "long_answer": "This pan is versatile and suitable for making various types of baked goods, as customers have reported successfully using it to bake items such as hot dog buns, bread sticks, and cakes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_433", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the saucepan come with an additional handle for support when lifting and pouring?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is equipped with a solid stainless steel riveted handle, which is designed to stay cool to the touch, providing extra support for safely lifting and pouring contents from the pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_434", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this nonstick saucepan?", "long_answer": "The nonstick saucepan is advertised as being compatible with metal utensils. However, to preserve the nonstick surface and ensure its longevity, it is advised to use utensils made from silicone, wood, or plastic instead.", "short_answer": "No", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_325", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I've got a thing for Matfer Bourgeat pans. Give me the product ID of one of their pans you have in stock.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Matfer Bourgeat' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_120", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is it safe to clean this pan in the dishwasher on a regular basis without causing any harm to it?", "long_answer": "Certainly, you can confidently wash this pan in your dishwasher. Our pans are crafted from robust materials such as stainless steel and aluminum, ensuring they can endure the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without degradation.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_326", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that's bigger than a 10 inch. Also gotta be blue. What's the best option you got?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND color = \"blue\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND color = \"blue\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND color = 'blue' ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_121", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "My kitchen features numerous tricky nooks and limited space. Could I face difficulties in storing this pan?", "long_answer": "Certainly, you may face challenges when trying to store a round-shaped pan in a kitchen that has numerous awkward corners and scant space, since its shape isn't well-suited to these constraints. Opting for a pan whose design more aptly conforms to the distinct nooks of your kitchen would probably be more appropriate.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_327", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Look, I need a pan that can handle the heat, specifically over 400F, and I'm not interested in anything smaller than 10 inches. What's the best you got for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size > 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size > 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size >= 10 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_328", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I've got a thing for Anolon products and I need a pan that can handle oven temperatures over 400F. Can you find me one?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray` with asin: B000069RBK", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Anolon\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Anolon\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Anolon' AND oven_safe_temperature > 400;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_435", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the exterior paint on this product prone to chipping with frequent use?", "long_answer": "The paint on the exterior of this product may display signs of wear and chipping over an extended period, particularly if the product is used frequently. To reduce the likelihood of damage, it is recommended to handle the product carefully and avoid any rough or abrasive surfaces that could compromise the integrity of the paint.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_436", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is the clean-up process quick and convenient after using this non-stick baking pan?", "long_answer": "The non-stick Americoat coating on this baking pan makes the clean-up process quick and convenient, as it usually requires only a brief rinse or a simple wipe with a paper towel.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_329", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm looking for a large copper pan for my new kitchen, something bigger than 12 inches. Do you have anything like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND size > 12 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND size > 12 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND color = 'copper';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_437", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this nonstick saucepan?", "long_answer": "Although the nonstick interior of the saucepan is designed to be scratch resistant, it is recommended not to use metal utensils. Such utensils could potentially damage the nonstick coating over time, thus reducing its longevity.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_438", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the vented tempered-glass lid both securely fitting and resistant to damage with regular use?", "long_answer": "The vented tempered-glass lid is engineered to fit securely, trapping heat and moisture efficiently. It is also durable, as the vast majority of users report that it does not become cloudy or break easily with regular use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_330", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm a big fan of the color silver and I often bake with high temperatures. Could you tell me which silver pan can withstand the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'silver' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_439", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "What cookbook do customers frequently recommend for Madeleine recipes when using this pan?", "long_answer": "Customers who have purchased this pan often recommend the \"We Love Madeleines\" cookbook, though our customer service does not officially endorse any specific cookbooks.", "short_answer": "We Love Madeleines", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_440", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is it necessary to use oil or butter to prevent food from sticking to this non-stick pan?", "long_answer": "It is recommended to use a small amount of oil or butter to ensure the best cooking results when using this pan, even though it is marketed as non-stick, to prevent food from sticking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_441", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Can the T-fal Professional fry pan be cleaned in a dishwasher?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Professional fry pan is designed to be dishwasher safe, allowing for easier and more convenient cleaning after use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_442", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "What is the maximum temperature at which I can safely use this fry pan in the oven without damaging the non-stick coating?", "long_answer": "The fry pan can tolerate oven temperatures up to 500°F, but to maintain the integrity of the non-stick coating, it should not be used at temperatures exceeding 400°F.", "short_answer": "400°F", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_443", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is it necessary to use a significant amount of oil or butter to prevent food from sticking to this pan?", "long_answer": "The pan features a non-stick surface that is specifically designed to minimize the requirement for using large amounts of oil or butter. Most users report the ability to cook effectively with little to no additional fats.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_444", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it necessary to use oil or butter to prevent sticking when cooking with this pan?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed with a non-stick surface that allows for cooking food with minimal or no oil. However, while it is not necessary, using a small amount of oil or butter could enhance the flavor and overall cooking experience.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_331", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm after only the beefiest Matfer Bourgeat pan, definitely bigger than your average size, and it's gotta withstand high cooking temperatures. Got anything like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Matfer Bourgeat' AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans);"}}
{"id": "search_qa_332", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I like the brand Chicago Metallic, but I don't want to break the bank on it. Find me their cheapest pan, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Chicago Metallic' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_445", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Do users generally find the pan difficult to maneuver due to its weight?", "long_answer": "The weight of the pan is perceived differently by users; some consider it to be on the heavier side, particularly when it's full, but the consensus seems to be that the weight contributes to a good balance and feel, making it manageable to handle.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_122", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Should I perform any particular preparation with this pan prior to its initial use?", "long_answer": "Seasoning a wok is an essential initial step before cooking. It forms a non-stick surface that stops food from adhering, enabling the use of less oil and facilitating smooth movement of ingredients. Without seasoning, the wok wouldn't function optimally, particularly in the high-temperature, rapid-cooking setting for which it is intended.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with a non-seasoned surface lack the capability to be non-stick, which is a desired feature to prevent food from sticking and to allow for the easy movement of ingredients which is characteristic of wok cooking.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "wok", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_333", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm in the market for a decent-sized pan, at least 12 inches, from either Ozeri or Chicago Metallic. Gimme the first one you find.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Ozeri\", \"Chicago Metallic\") AND size >= 12 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Ozeri\", \"Chicago Metallic\") AND size >= 12 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (brand = 'Ozeri' OR brand = 'Chicago Metallic') AND size >= 12 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_123", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Can this pan distribute heat evenly to cook my food, particularly during meat searing?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the pan's round design is engineered to evenly distribute heat, which proves especially advantageous for searing meats. This feature guarantees that food cooks uniformly, preventing the formation of hot spots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_446", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "How resistant are the nonstick surfaces of these pans to scratches when using the appropriate utensils?", "long_answer": "The pans are outfitted with a scratch-resistant nonstick coating, and to ensure this feature remains effective, users are recommended to use non-metal utensils and refrain from using abrasive cleaners that could damage the surface.", "short_answer": "very durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_124", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Can this pan sustain the appropriate conditions for dishes that require prolonged simmering?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the cast iron lid on this pan is purpose-built for that very function. It retains heat efficiently and provides uniform heat distribution during cooking, essential for appropriately simmering dishes over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a cast iron lid typically mean that they are excellent at retaining and distributing heat during the cooking process, which is essential for dishes that need consistent temperatures to cook evenly, such as slow-cooked stews or braised meats.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "cast iron lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_334", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I ain't shelling out big bucks for a fancy pan. Get me the largest pan you got that's cheaper than your average price.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_335", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I need a sturdy pan that can handle high heat in the oven, but it has to be from either ZWILLING J.A. Henckels or Utopia Kitchen. Can you find me one that's safe for at least 500 degrees Fahrenheit?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('ZWILLING J.A. Henckels', 'Utopia Kitchen') AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_447", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Can the vented glass lid of this pot be safely used in the oven?", "long_answer": "The vented glass lid, along with the entirety of the pot, is constructed to endure oven temperatures up to 350 degrees Fahrenheit, making it suitable for oven use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_448", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Will the weight of the pan with a thick aluminum core affect its stability on smaller burners?", "long_answer": "The presence of a thick aluminum core does increase the weight of the pan, but it typically remains stable on most burners when properly centered and supported, emphasizing the need for cautious handling to ensure safety.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_449", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does the white nonstick interior of the pan present difficulties in cleaning?", "long_answer": "The pan's white nonstick interior is generally found to be easy to clean by most customers, especially when they adhere to the provided care instructions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_336", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I need to get a big pan for a barbecue party this weekend, but I'm only interested in Cuisinart. Do you have any Cuisinart pan that's bigger than 10 inches?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND brand = \"Cuisinart\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND brand = \"Cuisinart\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Cuisinart' AND size > 10;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_450", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is this skillet designed to perform the functions of multiple other cookware pieces such as a deep fryer, Dutch oven, and bread baker?", "long_answer": "This skillet is praised for its versatility by many customers, as it can be used in place of several other cookware items, including a deep fryer, Dutch oven, and bread baker. It has the potential to be the main cookware piece in a collection with appropriate maintenance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_337", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I want to add some color to my kitchen. Give me the first pan you've got in grey or green.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray` with asin: B000069RBK", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"green\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"green\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color='grey' OR color='green' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_338", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Big pans are my thing, but I'm specific about color. Show me the first product you got that's 10 inches or bigger and comes in either grey or blue.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"blue\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"blue\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND color IN ('grey', 'blue') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_451", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Is the All-Clad cookware set manufactured in the USA?", "long_answer": "All-Clad is recognized for producing their cookware in the United States, and this includes the set in question, which serves as an important selling point for numerous customers who appreciate locally made products.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_339", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I don't have much to splurge, but I need a pan that can withstand some serious heat in the oven and won't cost me more than 20 dollars. What do you have?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_340", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Look, I need a blue Tramontina pan. Which model do you have, just give me the product ID.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND brand = \"Tramontina\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND brand = \"Tramontina\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Tramontina' AND color = 'blue';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_341", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm only interested in All-Clad pans safe for at least 400 degrees in the oven. Show me the biggest one you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black` with asin: B0170TFNXM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"All-Clad\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'All-Clad' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_342", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I don't want to spend more than 50 dollars and I seriously can't stand grey. What's the cheapest non-grey pan you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND NOT color = \"grey\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND NOT color = \"grey\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND color != 'grey' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_452", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the saucepan have measurement markings on the interior?", "long_answer": "The interior of the saucepan features measurement markings which serve to aid in cooking, providing a convenient way to gauge quantities without the need for separate measuring cups or tools.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_343", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm not looking to splurge, okay? Just get me the largest Copper Chef pan that's priced around or below average.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND brand = \"Copper Chef\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND brand = \"Copper Chef\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Copper Chef' AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_453", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the pot come with a glass lid that fits securely?", "long_answer": "The pot is equipped with a glass lid designed to fit snugly, ensuring a tight seal. Although there has been at least one report from a customer who experienced difficulty in fitting the lid securely, it appears to be an exceptional case rather than a common problem.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_125", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Is it simple to recycle this cookware when it's due for replacement?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this cookware is readily recyclable when replacement becomes necessary. Given that these pans are crafted from aluminum, they are highly suitable for recycling initiatives and can be reprocessed numerous times while consuming less energy.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's environmental considerations are not recommended for those who prefer to minimize their environmental footprint through recyclable and sustainable cookware options, highlighting aluminum's advantage as it can be recycled effectively.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_344", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm trying to find a silver or grey pan that can handle high oven temperatures. Which one can take the most heat?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"grey\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"grey\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"grey\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('silver', 'grey') \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_454", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Do Ozeri pans contain any PTFE, PFOA, or APEO?", "long_answer": "Ozeri pans are manufactured using a GREBLON ceramic coating from Germany, which is explicitly 100% free of PTFE, PFOA, and APEO, thereby guaranteeing that no hazardous fumes will be emitted at high temperatures.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_345", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Listen, I do a lot of oven cooking and I need a pan that can withstand more heat than the average one. Also, it's gotta be big. Tell me the largest one you have that meets this requirement.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_346", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm particular about my cookware, mind telling me the first product you have from either Matfer Bourgeat or T-fal?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"T-fal\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"T-fal\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Matfer Bourgeat', 'T-fal') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_455", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Are there any visible signs of wear within the pan after it has been used?", "long_answer": "After use, a few customers have reported dark blemishes forming on the interior of the pan, though these marks do not compromise the pan's performance. Maintaining the pan's appearance requires appropriate care and cleaning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_347", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm not one to splash the cash and I'm only willing to spend up to 20 dollars. I also have a thing for greys and coppers. So traverse through your pans and tell me the biggest one you have in these colors within my budget.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND color IN ('grey', 'copper') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_348", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm trying to upgrade my kitchenware game here and I need a badass pan that either comes in black or blue and can take a 500°F oven punch at least. Give me the cheapest one you've got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('black', 'blue') AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_456", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does the pan come pre-seasoned, or is seasoning required before first use?", "long_answer": "The pan requires seasoning prior to its first use, as it does not come pre-seasoned. Seasoning the pan is necessary to create a non-stick surface, which also contributes to extending the lifespan of the pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_349", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I only trust T-fal for my pans and I need it to be bigger than 12 inches. Which one product of yours got that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND size > 12 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND size > 12 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'T-fal' AND size > 12;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_350", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I love cooking on high heat and I'm crazy about copper colored pans. Fetch me the copper pan that can withstand over 600F, hotshot.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' AND oven_safe_temperature > 600;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_457", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Does the pan have a feature that allows it to be suspended for storage?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed with a long handle, which can potentially be used for hanging purposes, depending on the specifics of your kitchen configuration.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_351", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I enjoy cooking a lot, and I need a pan either from \"USA Pan\" or \"Matfer Bourgeat\" brands that's more than 10 inches big. Show me the most affordable one you have!", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") AND size > 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") AND size > 10 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") AND size > 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('USA Pan', 'Matfer Bourgeat') AND size > 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_352", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I got a specific taste, buddy. I need a ZWILLING J.A. Henckels pan, but only in blue or green. Can you dig up something like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") AND brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") AND brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' AND (color = 'blue' OR color = 'green');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_458", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the design of the lid handle affect the pan's ability to be stored efficiently with other cookware?", "long_answer": "The pan's design, specifically the lid handle, can impede its ability to nest seamlessly with other cookware, potentially requiring more storage space.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_459", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is this pan compatible with an electric stove and does it distribute heat evenly on it?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be compatible with all types of stovetops, including electric stoves. While it will work on an electric stove, the heat distribution might differ and may not be as even as on an induction stove due to variances in the heating characteristics of different stove types.", "short_answer": "yes, no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_460", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is cooking acidic foods in a newly seasoned cast iron skillet harmful to the pan's seasoning?", "long_answer": "Cooking acidic foods such as tomato sauce in a newly seasoned cast iron skillet can weaken the initial layer of seasoning. It is advisable to first use the skillet for cooking non-acidic foods to establish a robust patina, which can then better tolerate acidic ingredients without damaging the seasoning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_353", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I'm trying to fire up my cooking game and need a pan that can handle more than 400F in the oven. Can you identify one from your product line?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_461", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is it suitable to cook acidic foods in a seasoned cast iron skillet?", "long_answer": "Cooking highly acidic foods such as tomatoes in a seasoned cast iron skillet is typically discouraged, particularly when the skillet's seasoning layer is not well-established, because the acidity can deteriorate the seasoning.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_126", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Should I observe any particular precautions while using a dishwasher to wash this pan?", "long_answer": "No special precautions are necessary for this pan. Its dishwasher-safe design ensures it can withstand the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher, including high heat and aggressive detergents, without sustaining damage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute feature resistance to both the high temperatures and strong chemicals typical in dishwashers, which ensures they do not warp, rust, or degrade quickly when exposed to such conditions regularly.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_462", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is the pan designed to be safe for use in both the stovetop and the oven?", "long_answer": "The pan is indeed designed to be oven safe, allowing users to cook on the stovetop and then transfer it into the oven to complete the cooking process, accommodating recipes that call for this method.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_354", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I need a new pan, at least 12 inches wide. And it has to be a Presto or ZWILLING J.A. Henckels – no substitutes. Can you find me the cheapest one you have in stock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND brand IN (\"Presto\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND brand IN (\"Presto\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND brand IN (\"Presto\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Presto', 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels') AND size >= 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_463", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the Thermo-spot heat indicator feature present on every size variant of the T-fal frying pan?", "long_answer": "The Thermo-spot heat indicator is a standard feature included on all size variants of the T-fal frying pan model in question, ensuring that users can conveniently check the pan's temperature regardless of its size.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_355", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Look, I'm not trying to splash the cash here. Can you find me the biggest pan you have for 10 bucks or less?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_464", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the Presto electric wok coated with a non-stick material?", "long_answer": "The Presto electric wok is made of stainless steel and does not come with a non-stick coating, but user feedback suggests that cleaning it is relatively simple if one adheres to the manufacturer's cleaning recommendations and advice from other users.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_356", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm a fan of Ozeri pans, but I need one that can handle oven temperatures of at least 400 degrees. What's the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Ozeri\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Ozeri\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Ozeri\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Ozeri' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_465", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are the Green Earth Pans by Ozeri compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "Every pan in the Green Earth Frying Pan Set by Ozeri is designed with a magnetized bottom that is safe for use on induction stoves, which facilitates quick and efficient heat transfer.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_466", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is there a common issue with the lid's ability to seal properly on this product?", "long_answer": "There are inconsistent reports regarding the lid's sealing capabilities. Some customers have experienced issues where the lid does not fit perfectly, which may be attributed to warping, indicating that while some units may have a satisfactory seal, others do not.", "short_answer": "varies by person", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_467", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Where is this broiler set manufactured?", "long_answer": "The broiler set is manufactured in Taiwan, as indicated by the product metadata.", "short_answer": "Taiwan", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_357", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I cook on high heat and I prefer the brands Utopia Kitchen or Copper Chef. Get me a pan from these brands that can withstand temperatures of over 500F.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Copper Chef\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Copper Chef\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Utopia Kitchen', 'Copper Chef') AND oven_safe_temperature > 500;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_358", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm not trying to break the bank, but I also need a pan that can withstand some serious heat. What's the most oven-safe pan you got for under 50 dollars?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_468", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "What is the texture of the skillet's pre-seasoned surface?", "long_answer": "The skillet's pre-seasoned surface has a slightly textured feel, which can be likened to an \"orange-peel\" effect, distinguishing it from a completely smooth finish.", "short_answer": "slightly textured", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_359", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I ain't splurging over 50 dollars for a pan. Give me the product ID of the biggest one you've got within my budget.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_469", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is the saucepan designed to be lightweight or heavyweight?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed to be heavyweight, which provides stability on the cooktop and allows for more consistent heating when preparing food.", "short_answer": "heavyweight", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_470", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is it possible to fry or sauté on the nonstick surface without oil?", "long_answer": "The nonstick surface of the cookware allows food to be fried or sautéed with minimal or even no fat or oil, supporting healthier cooking practices.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_471", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the saucepan's rim facilitate spill-free pouring?", "long_answer": "The saucepan comes with a tapered drip-free pouring rim designed specifically to aid in preventing spills and messes when transferring liquids out of it.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_472", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Can cooking acidic foods in seasoned carbon steel pans lead to damage of the pan's seasoned layer?", "long_answer": "Cooking highly acidic foods such as tomatoes or sauces with lemon can lead to the removal of the patina, the protective layer built-up over time on seasoned carbon steel pans, which may consequentially lead to rusting.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_473", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan suitable for baking hot dog buns?", "long_answer": "The USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan is versatile and has been used by many customers to bake not only traditional bread loaves but also hot dog buns with great success.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_474", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the handle of this pan designed to allow for hanging storage?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed with a handle that is suitable for hanging, providing a convenient option for storing and displaying the pan in the kitchen.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_360", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that's at least 10 inches. Got anything from either Cuisinart or Utopia Kitchen? Show me the first one you find.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND (brand = 'Cuisinart' OR brand = 'Utopia Kitchen') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_475", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the stainless steel accent on the handle likely to get hot during cooking?", "long_answer": "The stainless steel accent on the handle is mainly for aesthetic purposes and should not compromise the heat-resistance of the handle, allowing it to remain comfortable to hold while cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_361", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm only interested in Cuisinart and Tramontina brands and my cooking involves high heat. So, get me a pan that can handle more than 600F in the oven.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Tramontina\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Tramontina\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Cuisinart','Tramontina') AND oven_safe_temperature > 600;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_476", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Does the angled design of the pan's sides result in a smaller bottom surface area?", "long_answer": "The design of the pan with angled sides does indeed result in a bottom surface area that is slightly smaller compared to the top, which could be an important consideration for those who have specific size needs for cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_127", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Can I safely sear meats at high temperatures using this pan?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this pan is not ideal for cooking techniques that require extremely high temperatures, such as searing meats. The sensitive non-stick surface may suffer damage under such conditions. For cooking at high heat, you should opt for a pan without a non-stick layer, such as one made of cast iron or stainless steel.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with delicate non-stick coatings cannot be used for cooking methods that involve metal utensils or very high heat, to avoid damaging the surface.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_477", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "How durable is the non-stick coating of this pan when used according to the care instructions?", "long_answer": "The non-stick coating on this pan has been reported by a majority of customers to be durable, provided that the pan is used in accordance with the manufacturer's use and care instructions.", "short_answer": "very durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_478", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is the pan intended for baking Madeleines suitable for preparing desserts or savory items of a similar size that require a shell-shaped mold?", "long_answer": "Although the pan is tailored primarily for baking Madeleines, bakers with a flair for creativity can certainly utilize it to bake other types of desserts or savory treats, provided they fit the similarly-sized, shell-shaped molds of the pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_362", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I need a pan that can withstand at least 400F in the oven, but I only want either a Cuisinart or Lodge. What's your pick?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Lodge\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Lodge\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND (brand = 'Cuisinart' OR brand = 'Lodge') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_479", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Does the Stone Earth Pan come with a warranty?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Pan includes a satisfaction guarantee, which serves as a warranty. Customers can contact the manufacturer for more details on the warranty and assistance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_480", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it recommended to season Copper Chef pans to enhance their non-stick properties?", "long_answer": "Copper Chef recommends seasoning their pans as a potential solution to address sticking problems, which may lead to improved non-stick performance similar to the process for cast iron cookware.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_481", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the T-fal Professional fry pan guaranteed to not warp with use?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Professional fry pan incorporates a stainless-steel warp-resistant base designed to maintain its shape even after prolonged use, as suggested by customer feedback.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_363", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I fancy black stuff. Get me the cheapest black pan you have in your stock.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'black' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_364", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I didn't have a great experience with Lodge, so I'm exploring other brands. Can you get me the cheapest pan you've got that isn't from Lodge?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Lodge\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Lodge\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Lodge\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Lodge' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_365", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I don't need any frilly colors for my kitchen - give me either a black or a green pan, but make it the largest one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('black', 'green') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_128", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Can I safely place this pan in the dishwasher with my other dishes, or is it better to clean it separately?", "long_answer": "It is advisable to hand wash this pan because some dishwasher detergents may be overly abrasive for aluminum pans, especially those that feature non-stick surfaces or are anodized, as this can impact their durability and functionality.", "short_answer": "handwash", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's specific maintenance needs fail to meet the requirements for indiscriminate cleaning methods such as harsh scouring pads or certain dishwasher detergents, especially if they have a non-stick layer or are anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_366", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I ain't a fan of Tramontina and I'm looking to spend no more than 30 dollars on a pan. Dig up a pan from some other brand meeting my needs, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" AND price <= 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" AND price <= 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND brand != 'Tramontina' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_367", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm looking for a bargain here. Find me the biggest pan you have that's no more than 10 bucks and larger than 12 inches.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND size > 12 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_482", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "What accessories are included with the purchase of the wok?", "long_answer": "The wok includes a long-handled wooden spatula as an accessory. It is recommended to season the spatula with mineral oil prior to its first use to properly maintain it.", "short_answer": "[long-handled wooden spatula]", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_368", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm not messing around in my kitchen - I'm looking for an Anolon pan that can withstand at least 400F in the oven. What's the best you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray` with asin: B000069RBK", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Anolon\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Anolon\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Anolon' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_483", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is the heavy-weight aluminized steel pan effective in ensuring Madeleines are evenly baked and golden colored?", "long_answer": "The heavy-weight aluminized steel composition of the pan enhances heat conduction, promoting an even bake and a consistent golden color across the Madeleines.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_369", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I do a lot of baking and need a pan that can withstand an oven temperature of over 400F. I have a thing for Matfer Bourgeat and ZWILLING J.A. Henckels, so show me the largest pan from these brands that meets my needs.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Matfer Bourgeat', 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels') AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_484", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "How likely is it for the pan to warp after repeated use?", "long_answer": "The likelihood of the pan warping after repeated use is low, provided that proper care is taken to avoid sudden temperature changes and adherence to the recommended heat settings is maintained.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_485", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this pan's nonstick interior?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed with a Prometal Pro nonstick interior which is both durable and scratch-resistant, making it safe to use metal utensils without damaging the surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_370", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm not a big fan of All-Clad and my budget's pretty tight, no more than 30 dollars. Get me the biggest non-All-Clad pan you got within that price range.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"All-Clad\" AND price < 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"All-Clad\" AND price < 30 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"All-Clad\" AND price < 30 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'All-Clad' AND price <= 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_486", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the lid handle of this product retain water after washing?", "long_answer": "It has been reported by some customers that water can get trapped inside the knob of the lid handle during the washing process. To avoid any potential accumulation of moisture, it is recommended to dry the lid thoroughly after cleaning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_371", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I have this thing for blue, and I need a pan not less than 8 inches. Which one you would suggest for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND size >= 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND size >= 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' AND size >= 8;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_372", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm cooking up a storm over here and need a pan that won't cramp my style. What's the first product you have that's at least 8 inches?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_373", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Look, I only use Tramontina and Utopia Kitchen pans, and they better be safe in an oven over 600F. I also need a big one, so find me the largest one you stock that fits these specs.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Tramontina', 'Utopia Kitchen') \nAND oven_safe_temperature > 600 \nORDER BY size DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_487", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with the Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan?", "long_answer": "It is not advisable to use metal utensils with the Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan. Instead, to ensure the nonstick coating remains intact and to prolong the pan's lifespan, use utensils made from nylon, silicone, or wood.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_488", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "What is the power output in watts of the Presto 5900 Electric Wok's heating element?", "long_answer": "The heating element of the Presto 5900 Stainless-Steel Electric Wok has a power output of 1500 watts.", "short_answer": "1500W", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_129", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Should I implement any particular measures when cleaning this pan after using it to cook acidic dishes?", "long_answer": "Certainly, if the pan comes with a non-enameled cast iron lid, it's crucial to clean it cautiously after using acidic ingredients. These substances can damage the protective seasoning layer, hence it's advisable to seldom prepare acidic recipes or opt for a variant with an enameled cast iron lid, which endures acidity better and simplifies upkeep.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a cast iron lid are not suitable for acidic foods that can strip the seasoned coating unless the cast iron is enameled, as prolonged contact with acidic substances can lead to deterioration of the seasoning and the iron could react with the food, altering its taste.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "cast iron lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_489", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is the durable stone-derived coating of the cooking equipment capable of handling acidic foods?", "long_answer": "The cooking equipment is equipped with a durable stone-derived coating specifically designed to withstand and handle various types of foods, which includes the preparation of acidic ingredients such as tomatoes or wine-based sauces.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_490", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Does the non-stick quality of the Copper Chef Pan degrade over time, necessitating more intensive cleaning methods than wiping?", "long_answer": "The non-stick coating of the Copper Chef Pan can degrade with continued use, leading to food beginning to stick and requiring more effort than just wiping to clean. Following care instructions, such as using non-metallic utensils and avoiding abrasive cleaning methods, is crucial to preserve the pan's non-stick properties and extend its usability.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_491", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the broiler set compatible with the size of most toaster ovens?", "long_answer": "The broiler set is specifically designed to be compatible with the dimensions of most toaster ovens, ensuring it can be used as a versatile cooking implement across different oven types.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_492", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is this fry pan suitable for effectively cooking eggs without them sticking?", "long_answer": "Cooking eggs in this stainless steel fry pan can be done successfully; however, extra attention is needed to prevent the eggs from sticking. To achieve the best results, it is often recommended to use lower heat settings and ensure the pan is properly preheated with oil before adding the eggs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_374", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm only interested in silver or black pans. Help me find the cheapest one you got in those colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('silver', 'black') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_375", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm after a good sized pan, 10 inches or more, in either green or grey. Make sure it can handle some serious heat too. What's the best you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"grey\") AND size >= 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"grey\") AND size >= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"grey\") AND size >= 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND (color = 'green' OR color = 'grey') AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 \nORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_493", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Are these pans suitable for high-heat cooking with oil?", "long_answer": "These pans are specifically designed to handle cooking with oils at higher heat settings, enhancing the development of foods with rich flavors, vivid colors, and crisp textures.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_494", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "What is the weight comparison between the Presto 5900 wok and traditional stovetop woks?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 wok is considered to be lightweight and more manageable when compared to the heavier traditional stovetop woks, as reported by numerous users.", "short_answer": "lightweight", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_376", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm a heavy-duty chef and I need a good, large pan that can withstand a temperature of at least 450F in the oven. Which product do you suggest?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND size >= 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND size >= 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_495", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is this black steel frying pan compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "This black steel frying pan is manufactured to be compatible with all types of hobs, which includes its suitability for use on induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_496", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this nonstick pot?", "long_answer": "To maintain the integrity of the nonstick surface, it is recommended to use wooden or silicone utensils instead of metal ones, because metal utensils have the potential to scratch and damage the non-stick coating of the pot.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_377", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I need a good sized pan, at least over 12 inches from either Cuisinart or Norpro. What's the choice you got in line?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Norpro\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Norpro\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND (brand = 'Cuisinart' OR brand = 'Norpro');"}}
{"id": "search_qa_378", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm exclusively using Norpro and need a pan that's at least a foot in diameter. What's the first product that comes up under this criteria?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Norpro\" AND size >= 12 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Norpro\" AND size >= 12 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Norpro' AND size >= 12 ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_130", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Am I able to simply wash this pan with soap and water, or does it require any specific cleaning methods?", "long_answer": "Stainless steel pans require more than just a quick wash with soap and water, as they can become discolored over time. To maintain their appearance, regular polishing is necessary in addition to your normal cleaning habits. This added upkeep is worth considering if you prefer low-maintenance cookware.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with stainless steel material are not suitable for those seeking the easiest maintenance, as they can develop discoloration and require regular polishing to keep their appearance pristine.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "stainless steel", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_131", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Do I have to dedicate considerable time to maintain the pan's appearance as if it were new?", "long_answer": "If you seek a low-maintenance shine, be aware that pans equipped with stainless steel lids may not retain a carefree appearance indefinitely. To preserve their gleam, they often necessitate frequent polishing and can display water spots unless promptly dried following cleaning.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a stainless steel lid fail to meet the requirements for maintenance-free aesthetics over time, as they may require polishing if the shine is to be maintained and are susceptible to water spots if not dried promptly.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "stainless steel lid", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_132", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Can this pan be stored effectively in unconventional kitchen spaces due to its versatility?", "long_answer": "Please note that the pan's circular design may present difficulties when trying to fit it into atypical kitchen areas. This could restrict your storage possibilities if your kitchen features a unique configuration.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_379", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Look, I'm hoping to get a blue pan that's no less than 10 inches. Out of all your options, which one's the cheapest?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND size >= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND size >= 10 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND size >= 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' AND size >= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_133", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I seek a pan that's easy to maintain and keep looking like new. Would this be the right selection for me?", "long_answer": "If you prefer a low-maintenance alternative, you may wish to explore options beyond stainless steel. Although resilient, stainless steel pans may not retain their pristine look without frequent polishing to offset discoloration, suggesting they may not be the best suited for your needs.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with stainless steel material are not suitable for those seeking the easiest maintenance, as they can develop discoloration and require regular polishing to keep their appearance pristine.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "stainless steel", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_380", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I have a thing for Lodge products. Find me a pan from that brand, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Lodge\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Lodge\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Lodge';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_497", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is the nonstick coating on this pan free from PFOA?", "long_answer": "The pan boasts a high-performance nonstick coating that is indeed reinforced to be free from PFOA, ensuring a safer alternative for cooking activities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_498", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is the ZWILLING Spirit 8\" Thermolon Fry Pan compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The ZWILLING Spirit 8\" Thermolon Fry Pan is designed to be compatible with various types of cooktops, including induction. It can be used on gas, induction, ceran, halogen, and electric cooktops, ensuring versatility in its use across different heating sources.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_499", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Can the non-stick pan be safely washed in a dishwasher?", "long_answer": "It is recommended to refer to the care instructions that come with the pan to determine if it is dishwasher safe. While hand washing typically helps to prolong the life of non-stick pans, the manufacturer's guidelines should always be checked for the definitive answer regarding dishwasher compatibility.", "short_answer": "Consult care instructions", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_381", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I need a pan that can take the heat, something oven-safe over 500F. But make sure it's not that ZWILLING J.A. Henckels brand. What's the product you suggest?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND brand != 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_382", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm looking for a new pan, and it's got to be either blue or copper. Just show me the cheapest one you have in those colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('blue', 'copper') \nORDER BY price ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_500", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the stainless steel Norpro set an effective replacement for an old aluminum broiler pan?", "long_answer": "Customers have often replaced their old aluminum broiler pans with this Norpro stainless steel set and have been pleased with its performance, indicating its effectiveness as a replacement.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_501", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the Thermo-Spot heat indicator reliable in indicating when the pan has reached the optimal cooking temperature?", "long_answer": "The majority of customers consider the Thermo-Spot heat indicator a useful tool for determining if the pan has achieved the proper cooking temperature, but there are occasional remarks about the indicator's clarity not meeting some users' expectations.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_502", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Does the pan come with a lifetime warranty, and what does that warranty entail?", "long_answer": "The brand may provide a lifetime warranty with the purchase of the pan. However, the exact coverage details are crucial and can only be understood by examining the warranty's terms and conditions. If any issues arise with the pan, the recommended course of action is to reach out to the brand's customer service to inquire about assistance or potential replacement under the warranty.", "short_answer": "yes, consult service", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_383", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm only interested in T-fal or Copper Chef brands. Can you tell me the first pan from these brands that you have in store?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Copper Chef\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Copper Chef\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('T-fal', 'Copper Chef') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_134", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I am in search of cookware that can expedite my cooking time. Do pans equipped with glass lids contribute to quicker cooking?", "long_answer": "Pans with tempered glass lids provide the convenience of monitoring your food during cooking, yet they might not be the best choice for faster cooking times. Owing to possibly less efficient heat retention, they could mildly prolong cooking duration relative to pans with solid, heavier lids that better preserve heat.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids are not recommended for users looking for the most energy-efficient cookware, as they might not insulate heat as well as some heavier, more solid lid options, potentially leading to slightly increased energy use over time.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_135", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I seek a multipurpose pan that is capable of both simmering soups and handling frying tasks. Would this be the appropriate type for my needs?", "long_answer": "A saucepan is ideal for simmering soups and sauces because of its tall sides and design that favors cooking with liquids. However, it's not the best choice for frying. You'd be better off using a pan with lower sides designed to endure direct, intense heat when cooking foods.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan cannot be used for high-heat searing or frying due to their high sides and design focusing more on liquid-based cooking methods.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_384", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm a fan of good brands, I'm specifically looking at \"All-Clad\" and \"Matfer Bourgeat\" for pans. Give me the cheapest one you have from these brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"Matfer Bourgeat\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('All-Clad', 'Matfer Bourgeat') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_503", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Are there any current promotions or coupons available for the wok?", "long_answer": "The availability of promotions and coupons for the wok, like the 5% off offer noted, is subject to change and depends on the place and time of purchase.", "short_answer": "Varies", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_385", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I need a big pan, something larger than 12 inches, but don't rip me off. Can you find the most affordable one you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_386", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I ain't keen on spending more than 50 dollars and I only trust Lodge and Bialetti for quality. So, can you dig up the largest pan within that price from these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal` with asin: B000S6I4ZE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"Bialetti\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"Bialetti\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"Bialetti\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Lodge', 'Bialetti') AND price <= 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_504", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Can non-metallic utensils such as plastic or bamboo be safely used with this pan?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be compatible with utensils made from non-metallic materials, including wood, plastic, silicone, or bamboo, ensuring safe usage without damage to the pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_505", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is it necessary to remove the electric component from the wok before cleaning it?", "long_answer": "Before washing the wok, you should indeed remove the electric probe with the heat control because it is not designed to be submerged in water.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_387", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I do a lot of high heat cooking, so I need a tough pan. Which one from either Tramontina or Utopia Kitchen can withstand the highest oven safe temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch` with asin: B009HBKQR0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Tramontina', 'Utopia Kitchen') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_506", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan suitable for baking cake buns in addition to bread?", "long_answer": "The USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan is a multi-purpose baking tool that is not only meant for baking bread but can also be aptly used for a multitude of recipes, including cake buns, which allows for versatility in baking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_507", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Does the pan's handle remain cool to the touch during cooking?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed with large, stay-cool loop handles that ensure the handle remains cool and allows for safe maneuvering and control, even when the user is wearing oven mitts.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_508", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with these non-stick ceramic coated pans?", "long_answer": "Using metal utensils on non-stick ceramic coated pans is discouraged because metal can scratch the coating. To maintain the pan's surface and ensure longevity, it's advised to use utensils made of wood, plastic, or silicone instead.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_388", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that's either copper or black and can withstand some serious heat. Which one's the most heat-tolerant you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"black\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"black\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"black\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('copper', 'black') \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_509", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Can the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set be used to bake fish?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Roast Pan Set is indeed suitable for baking fish. The pan set is designed to accommodate a range of foods, making it versatile for cooking tasks such as baking fish, preparing meatballs, or cooking bacon. It is particularly ideal for smaller portions, suitable for individual servings or meals intended for two people.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_389", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm trying to upgrade my kitchen here. I need a grey pan, and make it larger than the average sizes you got. Get me one now.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND color = \"grey\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND color = \"grey\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'grey' AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_390", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I've got a thing for Bialetti, but I'm not looking to break the bank. Show me the cheapest pan they make.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal` with asin: B000S6I4ZE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Bialetti\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Bialetti\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Bialetti\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Bialetti' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_510", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is the Matfer Bourgeat Black Steel Frying Pan compatible with gas, electric, and ceramic stovetops?", "long_answer": "The Matfer Bourgeat Black Steel Frying Pan is designed to be compatible with a range of stovetops, including those that are gas, electric, or ceramic, thereby enhancing its versatility for use with different heat sources in cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_511", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Are the All-Clad Hard Anodized Nonstick Fry Pans compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The All-Clad Hard Anodized Nonstick Fry Pan set is designed with a stainless-steel bonded Anti-Warp base that renders them suitable for use on induction cooktops, optimizing them for such cooking methods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_512", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "What is the durability of the non-stick coating when maintained with proper care?", "long_answer": "When users adhere to proper maintenance, which includes utilizing low to medium heat settings, refraining from the use of cooking sprays, and employing gentle cleaning practices, the non-stick coating has been reported to exhibit high levels of durability.", "short_answer": "durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_513", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Does the pan provide even heat distribution across its cooking surface?", "long_answer": "The pan incorporates an induction plate which is engineered to distribute heat evenly. Despite this design feature, some variations in temperature can occur, specifically if the pan is not utilized on the correct heat setting.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_514", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Does the pan have a smooth finish and lack sharp edges?", "long_answer": "The pan is predominantly characterized by a smooth finish and is free of sharp edges, as reported by the majority of customers who have used the product.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_391", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I need a big pan of over 8 inches, grey or silver in color. Tell me the one that can withstand the highest oven temperature, please.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"silver\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"silver\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"silver\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND (color = 'grey' OR color = 'silver') \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_136", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is it possible to use this pan for cooking on the stove as well as presenting food at the dining table?", "long_answer": "As this is a saucepan, it is primarily intended for cooking purposes rather than for table presentation. It is not advisable to serve food directly from it, as it is constructed to prioritize heat distribution and cooking performance.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan are not recommended for serving food directly due to their construction, as they are primarily designed for cooking rather than table presentation.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_515", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Can the Copper Chef pan be safely used in an oven at high temperatures?", "long_answer": "The Copper Chef pan is designed to be oven-safe and can endure temperatures up to 850°F, facilitating versatile cooking methods such as searing a steak on the stove and subsequently finishing the cooking process in the oven.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_137", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Should I follow any specific cleaning procedures to preserve the surface of this pan?", "long_answer": "To preserve this pan's surface integrity, refrain from employing abrasive cleaners or scouring pads that may scratch the anodized aluminum. Instead, it is recommended that gentle cleaning be performed with a soft sponge or cloth to maintain the pan's non-reactive and non-stick characteristics.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with anodized aluminum are not suitable for use with metal utensils that can scratch the hardened surface, potentially compromising its non-reactive properties.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_516", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the Presto 5900 Wok equipped with any non-stick coatings?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 Wok is constructed with a stainless-steel body and lacks any non-stick coatings, making it a durable cookware option without non-stick features.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_517", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this non-stick pot?", "long_answer": "It is not recommended to use metal utensils with this non-stick pot as doing so could damage the non-stick coating. To ensure longevity and prevent scratches, it is better to use utensils made of wood, plastic, or silicone.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_392", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm after a silver pan that can withstand some serious heat, more than 600F. What's the biggest one you've got?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'silver' AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_518", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is it safe to use this pan on high heat for stovetop cooking?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to withstand temperatures up to 500°F when used in the oven. However, for stovetop cooking, to preserve the pan's longevity and maintain the non-stick coating, it is recommended to use the pan on low to medium heat settings rather than high heat.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_138", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is it possible to prepare lemon-based sauces in this pan without adversely affecting its appearance over time?", "long_answer": "No, unless the pan is expressly designed or anodized, preparing lemon-flavored sauces or other acidic dishes may result in gradual discoloration due to the pan's susceptibility to acid reactions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with reactivity to acidic and alkaline foods feature a potential for metallic taste transfer and discoloration, rendering them less suitable for long-term cooking of tomato sauces or citrus-based dishes unless they're treated or anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_519", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the T-fal saucepan come with features that allow visibility of the contents during cooking without removing the lid?", "long_answer": "The T-fal saucepan includes a vented glass lid which enables you to observe the cooking progress without needing to lift the lid, thereby maintaining a consistent cooking temperature and preventing potential spills or heat loss.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_520", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is the Lodge cast iron skillet safe to use both on the stovetop and in the oven?", "long_answer": "The Lodge cast iron skillet is designed for versatility and can safely transition from the stovetop directly to the oven, accommodating a wide range of cooking techniques.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_139", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "My apartment features a rather compact kitchen with minimal storage. Can this pan be maintained easily in tight spaces?", "long_answer": "The pan in question is not suitable for the dishwasher, indicating a need for more attentive care than simply placing it in with the rest of your dishes. It necessitates room for handwashing and an area for prompt drying post-washing. Should your kitchen space be at a premium and unable to afford the additional space required for this upkeep, you may wish to opt for a pan that demands less in terms of after-use care and storage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are not recommended for use by consumers who may not be willing or able to invest the time and effort into the careful maintenance these pans require, which includes correct hand-washing techniques and immediate drying to prevent damage.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_393", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I'm whipping up a storm in the kitchen and require a pan that can withstand oven temps of 400F or more and doesn't cost an arm and a leg. So, which is the cheapest one you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price < 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price < 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature>=400 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_140", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Will the coating of this pan deteriorate if it is subjected to frequent dishwasher cycles?", "long_answer": "No, frequent dishwashing will not compromise the finish. The pans are crafted from durable, coated, or anodized metals designed to withstand the rigors of dishwashing and preserve their high-quality finish.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_521", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Are there any issues with the stability of the wok's legs during use?", "long_answer": "Certain customers have reported that the legs of the wok may become loose with regular use. It is advisable to regularly inspect the legs and tighten them if needed, with caution to avoid over-tightening which could lead to damaging the screws.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_522", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the pan resistant to scratching when used on a glass-topped stove?", "long_answer": "The pan is crafted with durability in mind, yet it requires careful handling to avoid scratching, especially when it is used on surfaces like glass-topped stoves that are prone to showing scratches.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_523", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Does the tri-ply construction of this pan result in even heat distribution during cooking?", "long_answer": "The tri-ply construction of the pan is designed to distribute heat evenly, which helps to prevent the creation of hot spots and allows food to cook consistently throughout the pan, as reported by the majority of customers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_394", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Listen, I'm lookin' for a pan that's at least 8 inches big and can take the heat, like 500 F or more. Give me the deets for one, come on.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_395", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm a big fan of big pans by Cuisinart and USA Pan. Got any that are at least 8 inches? But just show me one, okay?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"USA Pan\") AND size >= 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"USA Pan\") AND size >= 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Cuisinart', 'USA Pan') AND size >= 8 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_396", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I've had enough with blue stuff and need a pan larger than 8 inches. What's the cheapest one you got that isn't blue?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" AND size >= 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" AND size >= 8 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" AND size >= 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND color != 'blue' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_524", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the entire pan, including its sides, constructed with tri-ply stainless steel material?", "long_answer": "The pan's construction utilizes tri-ply stainless steel for its entire body, including the sides, which is engineered to ensure optimal and even heat distribution when cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_397", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm adding a pop of color to my kitchen without breaking the bank. Get me the largest black or blue pan you got for up to $10.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") AND price <= 10 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") AND price <= 10 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") AND price <= 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (color = 'black' OR color = 'blue') \nAND price <= 10 \nORDER BY size DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_398", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I've been cooking up a storm and need a big pan. What's the product ID for the largest Anolon brand pan you have that's at least 12 inches?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Anolon\" AND size >= 12 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Anolon\" AND size >= 12 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Anolon' AND size >= 12 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_141", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Can this pan maintain the appropriate conditions for dishes that require extended simmering?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the cast iron lid of this pan is purpose-built for this function. It efficiently retains heat and guarantees uniform heat distribution during cooking, which is crucial for adequately simmering meals over an extended period.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a cast iron lid typically mean that they are excellent at retaining and distributing heat during the cooking process, which is essential for dishes that need consistent temperatures to cook evenly, such as slow-cooked stews or braised meats.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "cast iron lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_399", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I don't want anything from ZWILLING J.A. Henckels and I need a pan that can handle more than 450F in the oven. Find me the least expensive one you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_142", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is it safe to wash this pan's lid in the dishwasher without risking any harm?", "long_answer": "No, you cannot. Pans with cast iron lids are not suitable for cleaning in a dishwasher or for extended soaking, as this can lead to rust formation. These lids require manual upkeep, which involves drying and oiling after each wash to preserve their condition.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a cast iron lid lack the capability to be washed in a dishwasher or left to soak without proper drying and oiling as this can lead to rust formation, requiring more hands-on maintenance compared to some other materials used for lids.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "cast iron lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_143", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is any special equipment required to utilize this pan on various types of stoves?", "long_answer": "When transitioning between various stovetop styles, our aluminum and copper frying pans are compatible with gas, electric, and glass top ranges. However, an additional ferrous disk is required for use on induction stovetops, as the non-magnetic properties of these materials do not engage with induction technology.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_144", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I enjoy preparing omelets; would this pan be appropriate for that task?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the pan's circular design promotes uniform heat dispersion over its surface, which is optimal for preparing delicate dishes such as omelettes, guaranteeing a consistent and gentle cooking process.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_400", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I don't have a fortune to spend here, and I'm partial to Ozeri. Can you find me the biggest pan they produce for under 30 dollars?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Ozeri' AND price < 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_525", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the handle on the lid of this cookware tend to get hot during use?", "long_answer": "Based on customer feedback, while the lid's handle generally performs well, it has been observed that it can become hot during cooking, suggesting that precautions such as using a pot holder may be necessary for safety.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_401", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm in the market for a new pan and only got 10 dollars to spare. Can you find me a green or copper one for that price?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"copper\") AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"copper\") AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND (color = 'green' OR color = 'copper');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_526", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "What is the volume that the saucepan can hold in quarts?", "long_answer": "The saucepan has a volume capacity, allowing it to hold up to 2 quarts of liquid.", "short_answer": "2 quarts", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_402", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm only interested in green or silver pans. What's the first product you have in those colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"silver\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"silver\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('green', 'silver') \nORDER BY product_id \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_403", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm trying to save a few pennies here but still need a decent size pan, something like 10 inches or more. And, by the way, it needs to withstand some serious heat in the oven. Can you find me the one that can handle the highest temperature under 10 bucks?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND size >= 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND size >= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND size >= 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND size >= 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_145", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I aim to invest in eco-friendly cookware. Does purchasing these pans align with that objective?", "long_answer": "Certainly, purchasing these pans would align with your objective of acquiring sustainable cookware. Made from aluminum, these pans are highly recyclable and contribute to environmental conservation, consistent with sustainability principles.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's environmental considerations are not recommended for those who prefer to minimize their environmental footprint through recyclable and sustainable cookware options, highlighting aluminum's advantage as it can be recycled effectively.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_404", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I use T-fal pans exclusively but my recipes ask for oven temperatures of at least 500F. What's your most affordable pan that can handle that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'T-fal' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_405", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm big into cooking and need a pan that can handle the heat. Find me the largest pan you've got that can withstand over 600°F.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_527", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is this pan compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "This pan is equipped with a stainless steel induction plate, ensuring it is compatible with all types of stovetops, which includes induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_528", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Do users have difficulty placing a square pan on round stovetop burners?", "long_answer": "The square pan is compatible with round stovetop burners, and there have been no prevalent user reports of problems regarding the fit between the square pan and round burners.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_529", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Do users generally find the pan handles comfortable to grip?", "long_answer": "The pan handles are contoured with the intent of providing a comfortable grip, yet there is variation in user experiences due to the weight of the pans, which may influence the perceived comfort of the handles.", "short_answer": "subjective", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_146", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I worry about overcooking and drying out fish. Can this pan prevent that?", "long_answer": "This pan features a stainless steel lid designed to form a tight seal, effectively locking in moisture, thus making it an excellent option for cooking delicate dishes such as fish, preventing them from drying out. The airtight seal assists in maintaining an optimal cooking temperature, ensuring the fish stays succulent.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a stainless steel lid are known for providing an effective seal to lock in heat and moisture, enhancing cooking methods like simmering and braising.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "stainless steel lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_530", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the T-fal 3 Quart pot considered durable and well-balanced by its users?", "long_answer": "The T-fal 3 Quart pot is regarded by users as sturdy and well-balanced, with its solid construction contributing to its reputation as a dependable kitchen item.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_531", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Do the stainless-steel handles of the pan have the same heat resistance as the pan's main body?", "long_answer": "The stainless-steel handles are engineered to resist heat, however, they can still become warm after extended periods of cooking, hence it is advisable to use potholders to handle them.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_406", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm in need of a pan that can stand the heat, specifically more than 500F, and also, I don't want to spend more than 30 dollars. Can you find me something like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND price < 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND price < 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND price <= 30;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_532", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Does the size and weight of the pan make it difficult to store in a kitchen or pantry?", "long_answer": "The pan's considerable size and weight have led some customers to experience difficulty in storing it conveniently. It is advisable to allocate a specific, accessible area for the skillet to ensure it does not encroach upon valuable workspace on a daily basis.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_407", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm a big fan of ZWILLING J.A. Henckels and Bialetti, but I don't want to spend more than 50 dollars this time. Which is the cheapest pan from these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal` with asin: B000S6I4ZE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"Bialetti\") AND price < 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"Bialetti\") AND price < 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('ZWILLING J.A. Henckels', 'Bialetti') AND price <= 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_408", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Alright, I've got my eyes on either a Cuisinart or Lodge pan. Can you let me know which one of these brands has the least expensive pan in stock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Lodge\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Lodge\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Lodge\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Cuisinart', 'Lodge') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_533", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Does the Madeleine Pan come with a recipe included?", "long_answer": "The Madeleine Pan includes a recipe, although owners are advised to try different recipes to suit their individual taste preferences and desired texture outcomes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_409", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that can handle some serious heat, like over 500F serious, and no pricey stuff. What's the best you got that won't run me over 50 dollars?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND price <= 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND price <= 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND price < 50;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_410", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I've got a thing for green colored stuff. Get me your cheapest green pan.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'green' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_534", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the wok dishwasher safe and easy to clean?", "long_answer": "The wok, along with its lid, is designed to be dishwasher safe, allowing for hassle-free cleaning. Moreover, users often find the wok to be easy to clean by hand, usually requiring only a soaking period followed by light scrubbing to remove stuck food. Certain cleaning products may be applied to remedy any discoloration that arises from cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_411", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I'm partial to ZWILLING J.A. Henckels and Anolon brands. What's the biggest pan you have from either of these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"Anolon\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"Anolon\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\", \"Anolon\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('ZWILLING J.A. Henckels', 'Anolon') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_412", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm not throwing big money around for a pan. Can you help me find the largest one under 30 dollars?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_147", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "If I fail to maintain this pan meticulously, will its appearance alter as time passes?", "long_answer": "Certainly, because the pan is not dishwasher safe, it may need to be polished to maintain its look, as well as routine upkeep such as seasoning, depending on its material, to avoid aesthetic degradation.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" do not have a function of self-maintenance and will need regular seasoning (for cast iron or carbon steel) or polishing (for aesthetic reasons) to maintain their best condition.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_535", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Can the Lodge cast iron skillet endure for several generations with appropriate maintenance?", "long_answer": "The lifespan of a Lodge cast iron skillet is greatly extended by proper maintenance, such as ensuring it is thoroughly dried after washing and regularly seasoned. This level of care can result in the skillet being durable enough to last for multiple generations.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_536", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the pan resistant to warping when exposed to high temperatures?", "long_answer": "Customer reviews widely suggest that the pan is robust and maintains its shape without warping under high temperature conditions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_413", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm a bit rough on my pans and need one that can handle an oven temp of at least 500 degrees. I don't care about the frills, just give me your cheapest one.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_414", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I cook at really high temperatures and need a pan that can withstand it. What's your top pan that can handle at least 600F in the oven?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_537", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the T-fal Professional fry pan designed to be dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Professional fry pan is manufactured to be dishwasher safe, which means it can be conveniently cleaned in a dishwasher without causing any damage to the pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_538", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is it recommended to cook highly acidic foods like tomatoes in a new cast iron skillet?", "long_answer": "Cooking highly acidic foods such as tomatoes in a cast iron skillet is generally not recommended, particularly if the skillet's seasoning is not yet well-established. The acidity can erode the protective seasoning layer, but as the skillet becomes increasingly seasoned over time, it can gradually become more resilient against such foods.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_539", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Is seasoning required for maintaining these non-stick pans?", "long_answer": "These non-stick pans do not require seasoning. Adhering to the manufacturer's care and usage instructions is recommended for preserving the functionality of the pan's surface.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_540", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is it necessary to grease the pan to release Madeleines easily?", "long_answer": "While the pan has a non-stick coating that is meant to prevent sticking, it is often recommended by users to lightly grease the pan to enhance the likelihood of a smooth release of the Madeleines.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_415", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm cooking up a storm and don't need my pans failing on me at high heat. Pull up the cheapest pan you have that can withstand more than 600°F.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_416", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Honestly, I've had it with the USA Pan brand. Can you find me a blue-colored pan from a different brand?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" AND color = \"blue\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" AND color = \"blue\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'USA Pan' AND color = 'blue';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_541", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Does the nonstick surface make this pan easy to clean?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed with a nonstick surface, contributing to its ease of cleaning. Based on customer reports, soaking the pan in hot soapy water simplifies the process, particularly when the pan is allowed to cool before cleaning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_542", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this non-stick ceramic coated pan?", "long_answer": "Metal utensils are not recommended for use with this non-stick ceramic coated pan, as they can scratch and damage the surface. To preserve the pan's integrity and non-stick capability, it is advised to use utensils made of wood, plastic, silicone, or bamboo.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_417", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I need a blue pan, just not from Tramontina. Do you have any other brand I can look at?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' AND brand != 'Tramontina';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_418", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm cooking up a storm for a big party and I need a darn big pan that can withstand at least 450F in the oven. What's the biggest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450\nORDER BY size DESC\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_148", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for recipes involving broiling?", "long_answer": "The pan is also suitable for broiling. Its stainless steel lid can withstand the high temperatures of a broiler without sustaining damage. Nonetheless, ensure that the pan handle can endure the broiler's high heat, especially if it is not crafted from stainless steel.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a stainless steel lid are ideally used for oven recipes due to their high heat tolerance, provided that the handle is also oven-safe if it is not made from stainless steel.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "stainless steel lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_543", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Do these die-cast aluminum pans provide even heat distribution during cooking?", "long_answer": "These pans are crafted from die-cast aluminum, a material known for its capability to distribute heat evenly across the cooking surface. This uniform heat distribution ensures that food cooks consistently without the presence of hot spots, leading to evenly cooked meals with excellent browning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_544", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the saucepan designed to be oven-safe according to the product description?", "long_answer": "The product description does not explicitly state the oven-safe temperature for the saucepan. To determine if it can be used in the oven and to what temperature it is safe, it's recommended to consult the manufacturer's guidelines.", "short_answer": "Check manufacturer's guidelines", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_419", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm looking for a big pan, something larger than a foot in diameter. But don't give me any of those dull colors - I just want silver or green. Also, I need it to stand high heat, the hotter the better. What's your top recommendation for such a product?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND color IN (\"silver\", \"green\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND color IN (\"silver\", \"green\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND color IN (\"silver\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 \nAND color IN ('silver', 'green') \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_420", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm whipping up recipes that require a lot of heat, and I want a bigger size pan than average. Show me your cheapest pan that can take over 450F and is larger than the usual.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans)\nAND oven_safe_temperature > 450\nORDER BY price \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_421", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm not looking to empty my wallet so find me the cheapest pan from Anolon you guys have in stock.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray` with asin: B000069RBK", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Anolon\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Anolon\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Anolon\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Anolon' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_545", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Are temperature adjustments necessary when cooking with these pans compared to other nonstick pans?", "long_answer": "These pans may require a slight adjustment in cooking temperature, as their construction could cause them to take longer to heat up, although they do retain heat effectively. The extent of temperature adjustment might depend on the type of heat source you are using.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_546", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Are metal utensils safe to use with the Stone Earth Pan's non-stick surface?", "long_answer": "Using metal utensils with the Stone Earth Pan is not advised because they might compromise the integrity of the non-stick surface, despite the pan having a hardened scratch-resistant coating.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_547", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Can the pan adequately prepare meals for a family of three?", "long_answer": "The pan is capable of cooking meals for three people, provided the portion sizes are managed accordingly, as customers have successfully used it for such servings.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_548", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is a lifetime warranty included with the purchase of this crepe pan?", "long_answer": "The crepe pan includes a lifetime warranty, providing buyers with assurance in the durability of their purchase and its sustained functionality over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_422", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I'm looking for a large pan, but only in copper or grey. What's the biggest one you've got in those colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"grey\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"grey\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"grey\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('copper', 'grey') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_549", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "What material is the saucepan's lid made of?", "long_answer": "The saucepan includes a lid constructed from stainless steel, which is designed to seal in moisture and nutrients effectively, rather than being made of glass.", "short_answer": "stainless steel", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_423", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm not shelling out more than 50 bucks. Get me an oven pan that can withstand more than 450 degrees Fahrenheit. Give me your best deal.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_550", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Do the cups of the Madeleine pan provide the traditional Madeleine shape with the classic hump?", "long_answer": "The cups of the Madeleine pan are considered to be sufficiently deep, allowing customers to successfully achieve the traditional Madeleine silhouette, including the characteristic hump.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_551", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "What type of warranty is included with the T-fal pan purchase?", "long_answer": "The T-fal pan includes a limited lifetime warranty; however, it's important to be aware that this warranty may not extend to cover damages to the nonstick coating if they occur under specific conditions that fall outside the warranty terms.", "short_answer": "limited lifetime warranty", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_149", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is it possible to use this pan with various cooking techniques, such as in an outdoor brick oven?", "long_answer": "An outdoor brick oven's direct and intense heat is unsuitable for this type of pan whose material and handle are not made to withstand the extreme temperatures typical of those cooking settings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan lack the capability to be used on open fires or grills without risking damage to their handles or materials that are not designed to withstand such direct, intense heat.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_424", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm all about those Copper Chef products, and I need a black one to match my kitchen. Can you find me a pan from them in that color?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND color = \"black\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND color = \"black\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Copper Chef' AND color = 'black';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_552", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Can the handle with the silicone sleeve attached be safely used in an oven up to 400 degrees Fahrenheit (204 degrees Celsius)?", "long_answer": "Yes, the handle, inclusive of the silicone sleeve, is designed to withstand temperatures up to 400 degrees Fahrenheit (204 degrees Celsius) when placed in the oven. However, it is important to handle with care as the handle may still become hot during use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_553", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Does the ZWILLING Spirit range offer pans in sizes larger than the one inquired about?", "long_answer": "The ZWILLING Spirit range provides a selection of pans in various diameters, allowing customers to choose pans that suit different cooking requirements, including sizes larger than the initial product in question.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_425", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I like to cook big meals and put pans in the oven, so I need a large pan that can withstand at least 400F. But try not to break my bank, ok? What's the least expensive one you got that fits my needs?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_150", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm in search of a lightweight camping pan; would this be a suitable choice?", "long_answer": "Should weight be a major factor in choosing your camping cookware, consider pans featuring lids crafted from lighter materials. Pans outfitted with stainless steel lids offer durability but fall short in weight efficiency when juxtaposed with lids constructed of glass or aluminum.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a stainless steel lid are not suitable for those prioritizing weight reduction in their cookware, given that stainless steel, while not excessively heavy, adds more weight compared to alternative materials like glass or aluminum.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "stainless steel lid", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_554", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the T-Fal Specialty Nonstick pot prevent rice from sticking while cooking?", "long_answer": "The T-Fal Specialty Nonstick pot is designed for cooking rice and other grains effectively without the issue of sticking, as evidenced by positive customer feedback.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_555", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Do the handles on the pan remain cool during cooking to allow for a comfortable grip?", "long_answer": "The pan features riveted silicone handles that are specifically engineered to stay cool while cooking, offering a secure and comfortable grip.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_556", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Does the Lodge cast iron skillet provide better heat retention and distribution compared to non-stick pans?", "long_answer": "The Lodge cast iron skillet is favored for its excellent heat retention and even cooking capabilities, often outperforming non-stick pans in heating efficiency and reducing cooking times.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_426", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm trying to up my baking game and need a pan that can handle some heat, more than your average ones. Plus, it's gotta be blue. What you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND color = \"blue\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND color = \"blue\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans);"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_557", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Do these pans distribute heat evenly during cooking?", "long_answer": "The pans are constructed from die-cast aluminum, which is a material known for its ability to distribute heat evenly. This results in even cooking without creating hot spots, according to product metadata and the feedback from the majority of customers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_427", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm looking for a decent-sized, dark-colored pan, at least 8 inches, you know? But it's got to withstand the heat. Give me your best option with the highest safe oven temp.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"grey\") AND size >= 8 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"grey\") AND size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"grey\") AND size >= 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND (color = 'black' OR color = 'grey') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_558", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "What type of warranty is provided with the All-Clad frying pan set?", "long_answer": "The All-Clad frying pan set includes a limited lifetime warranty, which is a promise from the manufacturer to the purchaser to repair or replace the product if it experiences defects under normal use conditions for the life of the product.", "short_answer": "limited lifetime warranty", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_559", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Does the skillet have a feature that allows it to be stored by hanging?", "long_answer": "The skillet is designed with a loop on its handle, specifically allowing it to be hung up for storage. This design feature offers a convenient space-saving solution for those who prefer to store their kitchenware in this manner.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_560", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Can the Copper Chef pan be cleaned using a dishwasher without damaging it?", "long_answer": "The Copper Chef pan is designed to be dishwasher safe, allowing for easy and convenient cleaning. Nevertheless, to maintain the integrity of the non-stick coating and extend the lifespan of the pan, it is advisable to wash it by hand using a mild detergent and water.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_561", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Does the Presto 5900's temperature control present any usability concerns regarding adjustability and safety?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900's temperature control is designed to allow users to adjust heating levels; however, there have been customer reports indicating that the control can become excessively hot to the touch. Hence, caution is advised, and it is recommended to use a cloth when making adjustments to avoid potential discomfort or burns.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_562", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is the Madeleine Pan beginner-friendly?", "long_answer": "The Madeleine Pan comes with a non-stick coating that simplifies the baking process and clean-up, making it highly suitable for novices in baking as well as for seasoned bakers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_563", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is the durable ceramic coating of the pan capable of withstanding acidic ingredients?", "long_answer": "The pan in question comes with a durable ceramic coating that is engineered to withstand the cooking of a diverse array of foods, encompassing those that are acidic in nature.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_428", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Grey is a total no-go for me, just not my color. Tell me which of the non-grey pans can withstand the highest oven temperature.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"grey\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"grey\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"grey\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'grey' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_564", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Does the All-Clad Fry Pan remain stable on the cooktop when in use?", "long_answer": "The All-Clad Fry Pan is specifically designed with a weight that contributes to its stability while cooking, ensuring it stays firmly in place on the cooktop during use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_429", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I'm looking for a decent-sized Ozeri pan, at least 8 inches. Can you find me the cheapest one you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Ozeri' AND size >= 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_151", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is it possible to utilize this kind of pan for preparing dishes that tend to stick and scorch?", "long_answer": "Indeed, thanks to the uniform heat distribution of a saucepan, it is adept at averting the development of hot spots, thereby reducing the likelihood of food sticking or burning in contrast to other types of cookware.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan are known for their even heat distribution which is essential for preventing hot spots that could scorch delicate sauces or custards.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_430", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I need a pan with a particular color scheme, I'm looking for either green or grey. Could you find me the one that can withstand the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"grey\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"grey\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"grey\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('green', 'grey') \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_565", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is it possible to have my pan replaced if it does not sit flat upon arrival?", "long_answer": "If your pan has a defect on arrival, such as a slight rock or wobble indicating it does not sit flat, you can contact the seller to organize a replacement or to receive a refund for the product.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_566", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Do the side loop handles of the wok remain cool during cooking to allow for safe handling?", "long_answer": "The design of the wok incorporates side loop handles that are crafted to remain cool throughout the cooking process, providing safety against burns when handling the wok.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_431", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Not too picky about colors as long as it's black or blue. Hunt me down the cheapest pan in those colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('black', 'blue') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_567", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "How durable is the stainless steel used in the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is constructed using stainless steel, which is recognized for its qualities of strength and durability, ensuring the pan's resilience over time.", "short_answer": "very good", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_432", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Blue just isn't my style, you know? Find me your most affordable pan that's not that color.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color <> 'blue' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_568", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does the pan have a handle that is designed to provide comfort and safety during cooking?", "long_answer": "The pan incorporates an extra-long, soft-touch handle, which is specifically designed to offer a comfortable grip and ensure safety when handling the pan as you cook.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_569", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is it necessary to use oil or butter to prevent food from sticking to this pan?", "long_answer": "According to the product's instructions, using a small amount of oil or butter is recommended to optimize the non-stick performance when cooking with this pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_433", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm only interested in Norpro and Cuisinart brands. Give me a product from one of those brands, would you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"Cuisinart\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"Cuisinart\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Norpro', 'Cuisinart') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_570", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is it necessary to use oil or butter when cooking eggs in these non-stick pans?", "long_answer": "Although the pans are engineered with non-stick properties that can potentially reduce the need for oil, it is recommended to use a small amount of oil or butter to achieve the best non-stick performance, as also observed by some users.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_434", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I'm looking for a bang-for-my-buck pan under 10 dollars and also want to stick it in the oven sometimes. Which one can withstand the highest temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_152", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Do these pans work well for recipes that begin on the stovetop and are completed in the oven?", "long_answer": "Certainly, a ceramic pan is suitable for recipes requiring a transition from stovetop to oven, provided that the shift in temperature is gradual. Ceramic pans are safe for oven use, yet it's crucial to avoid abrupt temperature fluctuations to maintain the pan's condition.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with ceramic material cannot be used for cooking techniques that require rapid changes in temperature as they might not be as efficient as metal pans in adjusting quickly to heat changes.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "ceramic", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_571", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Do Madeleines retain sharp and classic ridges when baked in this particular pan?", "long_answer": "This pan is reputed to produce Madeleines with sharp, classic ridges and nicely browned edges, according to customer reviews.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_153", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I need a multipurpose pan that's suitable for both simmering soups and frying. Would this be the appropriate choice?", "long_answer": "A saucepan, with its high sides and design tailored for liquid cooking, excels at simmering soups and sauces; however, it is not the best choice for frying. Frying calls for a pan with lower sides that allows for direct, intense heat exposure to foods.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan cannot be used for high-heat searing or frying due to their high sides and design focusing more on liquid-based cooking methods.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_435", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm in need of a heavy-duty pan that can resist high oven temperatures. Tell me, what's the toughest pan by Utopia Kitchen or Lodge you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Lodge\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Lodge\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Lodge\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Utopia Kitchen', 'Lodge') \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_572", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Can the pan accommodate cooking multiple items simultaneously because of its shape and size?", "long_answer": "The pan's square shape and large size are specifically designed to allow for the cooking of multiple items at the same time, making it possible to prepare dishes such as two grilled cheese sandwiches or four dollar pancakes concurrently.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_573", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Does the actual color of the pans match the color depicted in the product images?", "long_answer": "The pans are presented in a distinctive green color in the product images, which should accurately reflect the true color of the pans. However, if there is any doubt or concern regarding the matching of colors, it is recommended to contact the customer service team to address these issues.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_574", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the bottom of the pan designed to be flat for even heating?", "long_answer": "The pan is indeed designed with a flat bottom to ensure even heating. However, it should be noted that a minority of customers have reported some instances of slight warping.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_575", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the wok's adjustable temperature control capable of accommodating various cooking tasks?", "long_answer": "The wok is equipped with adjustable temperature control that can accommodate a variety of cooking tasks. It is advisable to monitor the temperature closely while cooking delicate items to account for the heating element's tendency to cycle on and off, as noted by some customers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_154", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "My flat features a rather compact kitchen that has minimal storage. Would maintenance of this pan be hassle-free despite the restricted space?", "long_answer": "The pan in question is not suitable for the dishwasher, meaning it necessitates a little more attention than simply throwing it in with the rest of your dishes. It needs room for manual cleaning and an area to air-dry straight after being washed. Should your kitchen be constrained in terms of space and unable to afford the additional room for this upkeep routine, you may wish to opt for a pan that is more low-maintenance with regard to its care and post-use storage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are not recommended for use by consumers who may not be willing or able to invest the time and effort into the careful maintenance these pans require, which includes correct hand-washing techniques and immediate drying to prevent damage.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_436", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm looking for a Copper Chef pan that is at least 10 inches or larger. What do you have in that brand and size?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND size >= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND size >= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Copper Chef' AND size >= 10;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_437", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm in need of a big, copper pan, needs to be more than 12 inches. Also, I usually cook at high temperatures, can you find me the one that can withstand the most heat?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND color = \"copper\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND color = \"copper\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' AND size > 12 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_576", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Does Copper Chef offer a variety of cookware to complete a kitchen set beyond the 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan?", "long_answer": "Copper Chef provides a diverse range of cookware options, allowing consumers to find various sizes and sets that can be combined to form a complete kitchen cookware collection, including products beyond the 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_155", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I frequently plan on searing meats. Would this pan be a suitable addition to my collection?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this pan should be on your list if you're looking to sear meats. It's not dishwasher-safe due to its material, but that's intentional, as the pan is crafted to support cooking methods such as searing that take advantage of its superior ability to retain heat.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are ideally used for traditional or specialized cooking methods that take advantage of their unique material properties, such as the heat retention of cast iron.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_438", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm a fan of Matfer Bourgeat pans and only looking for either silver or copper ones. So, what's the highest oven-safe temperature product from these preferences? Get me the details ASAP!", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND color IN (\"silver\", \"copper\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND color IN (\"silver\", \"copper\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND color IN (\"silver\", \"copper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Matfer Bourgeat' AND color IN ('silver', 'copper') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_439", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I need a decent sized pan from either Anolon or All-Clad, it's got to be at least 10 inches. Now, which one of those you'd recommend?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black` with asin: B0170TFNXM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"All-Clad\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"All-Clad\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Anolon', 'All-Clad') AND size >= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_577", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does the non-stick performance of this carbon steel or cast iron pan improve with regular use and proper maintenance?", "long_answer": "The non-stick properties and overall cooking performance of this carbon steel or cast iron pan are designed to improve over time with consistent use and adherence to proper maintenance routines.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_156", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "May I simply place this pan among my other dishes during cleanup?", "long_answer": "Regrettably, this pan is not suited for the dishwasher alongside other dishes. It requires specific care during cleaning to preserve its quality. This involves hand-washing and possibly extra measures like re-seasoning to ensure it remains in optimal condition.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" fail to meet the requirements for easy maintenance and may involve extra steps like re-seasoning or careful hand-polishing to uphold their performance and appearance standards.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_440", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I've got something for USA Pan or Utopia Kitchen, but it's got to be silver. And it better be able to take the heat in the oven. Pin down the one that can go hottest.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") AND color = \"silver\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") AND color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") AND color = \"silver\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('USA Pan', 'Utopia Kitchen') AND color = 'silver' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_578", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "What is the maximum oven-safe temperature for the break-resistant glass lid?", "long_answer": "The break-resistant glass lid is designed to withstand oven temperatures up to 375 degrees Fahrenheit without damage.", "short_answer": "375 degrees Fahrenheit", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_157", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm concerned about burning chocolate during the melting process; does this pan have a feature to prevent that from happening?", "long_answer": "The uniform heat distribution of a saucepan reduces the likelihood of hot spots, crucial for melting chocolate so it remains scorched-free and maintains a silky texture.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan are known for their even heat distribution which is essential for preventing hot spots that could scorch delicate sauces or custards.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_579", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for both frying on the stovetop and baking in the oven?", "long_answer": "The Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet is designed to perform effectively for frying a range of items on the stovetop as well as baking various dishes in the oven, allowing users to explore a multitude of skillet-oriented recipes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_580", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Does the Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan have a heat-resistant handle?", "long_answer": "The saucepan comes equipped with a bright chrome handle that includes a comfortable rubber grip. This grip is slip-resistant and designed to stay cool, ensuring that it does not heat up during cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_581", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Does the Madeleine Pan's manufacturing location in China affect its quality?", "long_answer": "The Madeleine Pan's production in China does not compromise its quality and performance, as it meets the high standards established by the Chicago Metallic brand.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_582", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Are these frying pans dishwasher-safe?", "long_answer": "The frying pans are advertised as being dishwasher-safe, adding a layer of convenience; however, to preserve both the longevity and the performance of their nonstick coating, it is advised to hand wash them instead.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_441", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I only got eyes for black and green pans. Show me one of those, the first one you find would do.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('black', 'green') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_158", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I need a pan suitable for both stovetop and oven use. Can you recommend a type designed for this purpose?", "long_answer": "Certainly, a cast iron skillet is a superb option for dishes that begin on the stovetop and end in the oven, thanks to its high heat tolerance and remarkable heat retention characteristics.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being made from cast iron typically mean that they are a preferred choice for recipes that benefit from steady heat and long cooking times, such as stews and braises, due to their excellent heat retention.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "cast iron", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_159", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Can this pan retain its shape when subjected to very high heat?", "long_answer": "Regrettably, an aluminum pan tends to have difficulty retaining its shape when subjected to very high temperatures, unlike pans crafted from robust materials like stainless steel or cast iron. The lower tolerance for intense heat renders it less suitable for high-temperature cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's lack of high heat tolerance lack the capability to withstand searing and broiling applications that require maintaining structural integrity at very high temperatures, unlike cookware made of materials like stainless steel or cast iron.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_442", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I don't have time for pans that can't take the heat, especially if they're not black. Do you have any black pans that can handle over 600 degrees?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'black' AND oven_safe_temperature > 600;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_160", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Does this pan provide even cooking, particularly during the searing of meat?", "long_answer": "Yes, the pan's round design facilitates even heat distribution, which is especially advantageous for searing meats, ensuring that your food cooks evenly without creating hot spots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_443", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm looking for a blue pan that can withstand 400F oven heat. Help me find one, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND color = \"blue\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND color = \"blue\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_161", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it possible to prepare a larger quantity of food simultaneously in this pan compared to the one I currently use?", "long_answer": "Indeed, given its square design, this pan offers an expanded surface area, thereby allowing you to cook increased quantities of food simultaneously when compared to a round pan of identical size. This feature makes it a more practical choice for preparing larger meals or for cooking in batches.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with square shapes are known for having a larger surface area compared to round pans of similar size, allowing for thicker recipes to be prepared satisfactorily.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "square", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_162", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Can this pan be used for broiling in the oven?", "long_answer": "No, this pan is unsuitable for oven broiling. The aluminum construction cannot endure the extreme temperatures necessary for broiling, potentially resulting in damage or compromised structural integrity, unlike stainless steel or cast iron alternatives.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's lack of high heat tolerance lack the capability to withstand searing and broiling applications that require maintaining structural integrity at very high temperatures, unlike cookware made of materials like stainless steel or cast iron.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_583", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Can the Stone Earth Pan by Ozeri be used on an induction stovetop?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Pan by Ozeri features a magnetized base engineered for rapid heat transfer, which enables its compatibility with induction stovetops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_163", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm in search of a pan capable of transitioning from the stovetop directly to the oven. Could you recommend a suitable type for this purpose?", "long_answer": "Certainly, a cast iron skillet is an outstanding selection for dishes that commence on the stovetop and are completed in the oven, as it can endure high heat and retains warmth exceptionally well.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being made from cast iron typically mean that they are a preferred choice for recipes that benefit from steady heat and long cooking times, such as stews and braises, due to their excellent heat retention.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "cast iron", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_584", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is it recommended to clean the Green Earth Pan Set by Ozeri in a dishwasher?", "long_answer": "The frying pans from the Green Earth Pan Set by Ozeri should not be cleaned in a dishwasher. To maintain the integrity of the non-stick ceramic coating, it is advised to hand wash the pans using mild soap and water.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_164", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is it possible to conveniently clean this pan in the dishwasher after I've cooked a steak?", "long_answer": "The specialized material properties of this pan, designed precisely for traditional or specific cooking tasks that demand superb heat retention like steak preparation, make it unsuitable for dishwasher cleaning. To preserve its condition and functionality, hand washing is advised.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are ideally used for traditional or specialized cooking methods that take advantage of their unique material properties, such as the heat retention of cast iron.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_585", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Can the Presto 5900 wok maintain the high temperatures needed for deep frying?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 wok is designed to reach and sustain the high temperatures that are necessary for deep frying, which has been confirmed by user experiences who have successfully used it for this cooking method.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_586", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Can the pan be returned to Amazon if it does not fit inside my toaster oven?", "long_answer": "In the event that the pan does not fit within your toaster oven, you are allowed to return it to Amazon, subject to compliance with the Amazon return policy and the fulfillment of the necessary return conditions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_587", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Do the handles of this cookware remain cool to the touch while cooking on the stove?", "long_answer": "The handles are crafted to remain cool when used on the stovetop, though under certain cooking conditions they may heat up, hence it is advised to employ potholders or oven mitts for safety.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_444", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Not a fan of green. Get me the pan that can handle the highest oven temperature, but absolutely no green ones.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'green' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_445", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that's bigger than average, but my wallet's feeling the squeeze. Can you find me the most affordable one that ticks that box?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price = (SELECT price FROM all_pans WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1) and size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans);"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_588", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is stainless steel resistant to scratching when using metal utensils?", "long_answer": "Stainless steel is susceptible to scratches, especially when using metal utensils, which can compromise its appearance and integrity. Thus, it is recommended to use utensils made of wood or silicone to maintain the saucepan's condition.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_589", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Does the Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet come with a lid?", "long_answer": "The Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet includes a cast iron cover as part of the purchase. This cover is useful for cooking techniques such as braising, as it helps to retain moisture in the food.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_446", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm all about those high-heat recipes, so I need a pan from either Ozeri or Cuisinart that can handle over 450°F. What's my best choice here?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Ozeri\", \"Cuisinart\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Ozeri\", \"Cuisinart\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Ozeri', 'Cuisinart') AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_447", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm not crazy about copper colored pans. Can you find me the cheapest non-copper one you have in your catalog?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'copper' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_448", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm tired of all these silver pans, plus I need one that can handle the heat better than average. Find me a non-silver pan that can stand the heat and won't break the bank.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'silver' AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_165", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Do I need to purchase any extra cleaning supplies if I acquire this pan?", "long_answer": "Given that this pan is not suitable for the dishwasher, it would be wise to acquire cleaning products designed for manual washing, such as a non-abrasive sponge and gentle detergent. Additionally, it's important to have a towel on hand for prompt drying to prevent water marks or the possibility of rust, depending on the pan's material.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are not recommended for use by consumers who may not be willing or able to invest the time and effort into the careful maintenance these pans require, which includes correct hand-washing techniques and immediate drying to prevent damage.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_449", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I do some serious cooking and need a silver pan that can handle heat up to 600F. What's the first one you got that fits my needs?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'silver' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_590", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Can the handle of the pan be safely placed in an oven?", "long_answer": "The pan has a cast stainless steel handle that can be safely placed in an oven up to 400 degrees Fahrenheit or 204 degrees Celsius. However, if the pan has a silicone sleeve, it is advisable to remove this sleeve before placing the pan in the oven.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_450", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm looking for a grey pan, specifically from Anolon or Utopia Kitchen. Can you help me find one?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray` with asin: B000069RBK", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" AND brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" AND brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'grey' AND (brand = 'Anolon' OR brand = 'Utopia Kitchen');"}}
{"id": "search_qa_451", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm only interested in Cuisinart and Bialetti. Can you get me the product id of any pan from these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal` with asin: B000S6I4ZE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Bialetti\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Bialetti\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Cuisinart', 'Bialetti') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_591", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this nonstick pan?", "long_answer": "Using wooden or silicone utensils is advised to preserve the integrity of the nonstick surface of the pan. Employing metal utensils can lead to scratches or deterioration of the nonstick coating with repeated use.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_452", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I need a pan that can stand the heat, but doesn't clean out my wallet. What's your largest pan that's oven-safe up to at least 500 degrees and cost no more than 50 bucks?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND price <= 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND price <= 50 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND price <= 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND price <= 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_592", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Do the riveted handles on this product present challenges in cleaning?", "long_answer": "Some users have expressed that the riveted handles can be difficult to clean; however, the design choice for using rivets is aimed at ensuring the handles are durable over an extended period.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_166", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Can I safely put this pan in the dishwasher, or do I need to wash it manually to avoid deterioration?", "long_answer": "This pan is entirely safe for dishwasher use. It is designed to withstand the intense heat and strong detergents typically found in dishwashers, ensuring it won't warp, rust, or deteriorate rapidly. This promises both durability and convenience when cleaning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute feature resistance to both the high temperatures and strong chemicals typical in dishwashers, which ensures they do not warp, rust, or degrade quickly when exposed to such conditions regularly.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_453", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm after a grey or green pan that can withstand higher temperatures than your average one. Get me the best option for this.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"green\") AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"green\") AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'green') \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_454", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm looking for a bargain on a pan, it's gotta be larger than 8 inches and not cost more than 20 dollars. What's the best you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND size >= 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND size >= 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND size > 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_167", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "May I utilize this pan for baking a cake in the oven?", "long_answer": "No, this pan, which comes with a tempered glass lid, is not suited for cake baking. Baking demands dry heat, whereas the tempered glass lid is designed to retain moisture, potentially altering the cake's texture and leavening.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids are not suitable for recipes requiring “dry cooking” methods such as roasting or baking without moisture, as the lids are designed to retain moisture within the pan.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_593", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is the weight of the pan a result of its heavy-duty construction?", "long_answer": "The pan is indeed heavier than some other pans, which is attributed to its heavy-duty construction designed to ensure durability and promote even heat distribution across its surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_455", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm all about the brand game. Dig up a copper-colored pan for me from either Anolon or T-fal.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"T-fal\") AND color = \"copper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"T-fal\") AND color = \"copper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' AND (brand = 'Anolon' OR brand = 'T-fal');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_594", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is it safe to use non-stick cooking spray on this non-stick pan?", "long_answer": "It is not advisable to use non-stick cooking spray on this pan as it may accumulate and potentially harm the non-stick coating. Butter or oil is the preferred alternative for cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_456", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm not looking to break the bank, but I need a pan that can handle serious heat, over 450F. What's the cheapest option you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND price < 20 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND price < 20 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_595", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with the non-stick surface of this pan?", "long_answer": "To maintain the integrity and longevity of the pan's non-stick surface, it is advised to use utensils made of plastic, wood, or silicone. Using metal utensils can scratch and damage the ceramic coating, thus compromising its non-stick properties.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_596", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is this pan safe for use in the oven at temperatures up to 400 degrees Fahrenheit?", "long_answer": "Yes, the pan is designed to be oven-safe and can withstand temperatures up to 400 degrees Fahrenheit, thus offering versatility for different cooking methods that require oven use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_457", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm a big fan of Norpro. Can you tell me which pan from them you have in stock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches` with asin: B0012BR1XU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Norpro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Norpro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Norpro';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_458", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I've got a thing for Tramontina pans, and I'm looking for either a grey or green one. What's the cheapest you got?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Tramontina\" AND color IN (\"grey\", \"green\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Tramontina\" AND color IN (\"grey\", \"green\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Tramontina\" AND color IN (\"grey\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Tramontina' AND (color = 'grey' OR color = 'green') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_168", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I have quite limited cupboard space; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?", "long_answer": "Round pans might not be the most space-efficient option for storage in cramped kitchens, presenting a drawback when it's essential to utilize every available inch. If fitting cookware into a limited cupboard or shelf space is necessary, square or angular pans could be a more suitable choice.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_459", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I love cooking with Ozeri pans and I got an oven that goes all the way to 600F. Can you find me the biggest Ozeri pan that can withstand that kind of heat?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Ozeri\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Ozeri\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Ozeri\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Ozeri' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600\nORDER BY size DESC\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_460", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I don't got big bucks to splash around, but my family loves big pancakes. Show me the biggest pan I can get for no more than 50 dollars.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND price <= 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND price <= 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_461", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Look, I need a pan that's not anything under 10 inches, from Utopia Kitchen or Anolon. What's the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch` with asin: B00X4WQMAS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Anolon\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Anolon\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Anolon\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND (brand = 'Utopia Kitchen' OR brand = 'Anolon') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_462", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I ain't flush with cash and only need a pan that's cheaper than average, and can take high heat. Get me the one that can withstand the highest temperature in the oven without costing an arm and a leg, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans)\nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_597", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Does the saucepan feature handles with hanging holes for storage?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed with bright chrome handles that include hanging holes, allowing the option to hang the saucepan for convenient storage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_463", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Look, I've got to be able to stick my pans in an oven that's cranked up to at least 500F, and I don't want any of those copper ones. Show me your biggest pan that will do the trick.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND NOT color = \"copper\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND NOT color = \"copper\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND NOT color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'copper' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_598", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is a separate strainer required when cooking pasta with the T-fal saucepan that comes with a vented glass lid?", "long_answer": "While the vented glass lid can assist with straining to some extent, it is advisable to employ a separate strainer to achieve optimal results and ensure safety during the process.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_169", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is special equipment necessary to use this pan on various stoves?", "long_answer": "Our aluminum and copper frying pans are compatible with gas, electric, and glass top ranges, accommodating your transition between various stovetop types. However, for induction stovetops, a separate ferrous disk is required for these non-magnetic materials to engage with the induction system.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_170", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I like to blacken fish; would this pan be suitable for such cooking?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, this pan is unsuitable for cooking methods such as blackening fish that demand the pan endures extremely high temperatures. Its aluminum makeup lacks the robust heat resistance found in materials like cast iron or stainless steel, which are more appropriate for such techniques.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's lack of high heat tolerance lack the capability to withstand searing and broiling applications that require maintaining structural integrity at very high temperatures, unlike cookware made of materials like stainless steel or cast iron.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_464", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm after a pan that can take the heat, say up to 600°F, preferably from either USA Pan or Copper Chef. But don't break my bank - what's the most affordable one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Copper Chef\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Copper Chef\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Copper Chef\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('USA Pan', 'Copper Chef') AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_171", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is this pan designed to be easily manageable when filled with food?", "long_answer": "Typically, it's manageable, yet be aware that pans featuring a stainless steel lid tend to be heavier than pans with lids crafted from lighter substances. This could impact the convenience of use when the pan brims with food, particularly when weight is a factor to consider.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a stainless steel lid are not suitable for those prioritizing weight reduction in their cookware, given that stainless steel, while not excessively heavy, adds more weight compared to alternative materials like glass or aluminum.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "stainless steel lid", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_599", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the glass lid from the cookware set dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The glass lid is designed to be dishwasher safe, which allows for easy cleaning. However, the pan should be hand washed to preserve its nonstick surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_465", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I need my kitchenware to match, so show me the first silver or black pan from either Tramontina or ZWILLING J.A. Henckels.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch` with asin: B009HBKQR0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") AND brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") AND brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (color='silver' OR color='black') AND (brand='Tramontina' OR brand='ZWILLING J.A. Henckels') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_466", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm a regular in the kitchen, usually with the oven cranked high and dealing with big portions. Get me the pan that can withstand at least 600F and is larger than your average size.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans);"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_600", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Does the pan set offer a 6 inch or smaller 'one egg' size pan?", "long_answer": "The pan set only includes sizes of 8, 10, and 12 inches, and does not offer a 6 inch or smaller 'one egg' size pan, based on the product metadata.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_601", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is this All-Clad frying pan compatible with induction cooktops and does it offer even heat distribution?", "long_answer": "The All-Clad frying pan is designed to be induction compatible and is recognized for performing well on induction cooktops. The pan is crafted to provide even heat distribution across its surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_467", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I've got a soft spot for Ozeri makes. Can you find me their biggest pan?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Ozeri\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Ozeri\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Ozeri\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Ozeri' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_602", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is this pan suitable for cooking a range of foods such as omelets and pancakes in addition to crepes?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be versatile and is particularly effective for cooking not just crepes, but also other foods like pancakes and omelets, thanks to its non-stick surface which allows for effortless food release.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_172", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Should I employ specific care methods while cleaning this pan to preserve its surface integrity?", "long_answer": "To preserve the integrity of the pan's surface, refrain from using abrasive cleaners or scouring pads that can scratch anodized aluminum. For keeping the pan's non-reactive and non-stick qualities intact, it's advisable to clean gently using a soft sponge or cloth.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with anodized aluminum are not suitable for use with metal utensils that can scratch the hardened surface, potentially compromising its non-reactive properties.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_468", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm looking for a large pan, at least 10 inches, in either blue or copper. But it has to handle some serious heat. Which one can take the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"blue\") AND size >= 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"blue\") AND size >= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"blue\") AND size >= 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND color IN ('blue', 'copper') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_469", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I don't have much dough to spare, but I still want a decent pan. Can you dig up a product from Utopia Kitchen or Copper Chef that goes for 10 bucks or less?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Copper Chef\") AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Copper Chef\") AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Utopia Kitchen', 'Copper Chef') AND price <= 10;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_603", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the pot suitable for high heat settings on gas stoves without damaging the non-stick coating?", "long_answer": "This pot is created to withstand use on various stove types, including gas stoves, yet for optimal performance and to maintain the integrity of the non-stick coating, it is advisable to cook on low to medium heat settings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_173", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Can chemicals from this type of pan seep into my food?", "long_answer": "Indeed, since the grill pan in question features a non-stick coating, there exists the possibility for chemicals to leach into your food, particularly if the pan is misused or as the non-stick surface wears down over time and through usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with non-stick coatings fail to meet the requirements for environmentally conscious consumers who are concerned about the potential for chemical components entering their food or the environment.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "grill pan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_470", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Hey, I need a pan, something cheap under $50, and it’s got to be either black or blue. What's the best option you got for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND (color = 'black' OR color = 'blue') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_604", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the pan designed specifically for crepes suitable for cooking a range of other foods?", "long_answer": "Yes, the pan is designed primarily for crepes and pancakes, but its versatile construction makes it suitable for a variety of other cooking tasks, such as searing meats and preparing one-pot meals.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_605", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is the non-stick surface of the pan designed to withstand cooking at high temperatures?", "long_answer": "The non-stick surface of the pan is heat resistant up to 850°F, indicating that it can indeed withstand high-heat cooking. However, it is important to note that the efficient heat distribution properties of the cookware may reduce the need for using such high temperatures during the cooking process.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_606", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the wok capable of cooking frozen vegetables quickly and easily based on user reports?", "long_answer": "According to users, the wok is indeed capable of efficiently cooking frozen vegetables. The design and heating capabilities allow for a quick and straightforward cooking process, making it suitable for handling frozen produce.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_174", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I seek a kitchenware option that requires minimal upkeep. Would this pan suit my needs?", "long_answer": "Should low maintenance be a priority for you, it may be wise to explore alternative choices. This pan is not dishwasher-safe, requiring additional attention like manual cleaning and occasional re-seasoning to maintain its optimal performance over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" fail to meet the requirements for easy maintenance and may involve extra steps like re-seasoning or careful hand-polishing to uphold their performance and appearance standards.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_607", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the wok suitable for use in steaming dishes?", "long_answer": "The wok is indeed suitable for steaming dishes; by adding water and employing a steamer tray or bamboo steamers, a range of steamed cuisine can be prepared effectively.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_608", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the pan compatible with gas range cooking?", "long_answer": "The pan is explicitly designed to be compatible with all types of stovetops, which include gas, electric, and induction cooktops, ensuring versatility in its use across different cooking platforms.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_609", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "How durable is the non-stick property of this pan based on customer usage over time?", "long_answer": "Customers have reported that they have used this pan repeatedly for extended periods and have not observed any deterioration in its non-stick properties or signs of wear.", "short_answer": "durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_175", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Can I safely place this pan in the dishwasher with my other dishes, or does it require washing by hand?", "long_answer": "It is advisable to hand wash this pan, since some dishwasher soaps may be overly abrasive for aluminum pans, especially those with non-stick surfaces or anodized finishes, potentially impacting their durability and functionality.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's specific maintenance needs fail to meet the requirements for indiscriminate cleaning methods such as harsh scouring pads or certain dishwasher detergents, especially if they have a non-stick layer or are anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_610", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this stainless steel saucepan?", "long_answer": "Although stainless steel is resistant to scratches, there is an elevated risk that using metal utensils will scratch it over time. To preserve the saucepan's surface and appearance, opting for silicone or wooden utensils is advised.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_611", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is the Matfer Bourgeat black steel fry pan suitable for high heat cooking techniques such as searing?", "long_answer": "The Matfer Bourgeat black steel fry pan is designed to retain high heat and withstand the temperatures of both a range and an oven, which makes it highly suitable for techniques that require high heat, including searing.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_612", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "What is the maximum oven-safe temperature rating for the tempered glass lid?", "long_answer": "The tempered glass lid can safely be used in an oven as long as the temperature does not exceed its maximum rating of 500 degrees Fahrenheit. Exceeding this temperature can result in damage to the lid.", "short_answer": "500 F", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_176", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm in search of cookware that can help me cook faster. Do pans featuring glass lids contribute to a quicker cooking time?", "long_answer": "Pans with tempered glass lids provide the convenience of viewing your food while it cooks. However, they may not be the most efficient choice for faster cooking. Owing to potentially lower heat insulation, these lids might somewhat increase the cooking time compared to pans with solid, heavier lids that offer superior heat retention.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids are not recommended for users looking for the most energy-efficient cookware, as they might not insulate heat as well as some heavier, more solid lid options, potentially leading to slightly increased energy use over time.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_613", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Do the pans come with handles that can resist heat?", "long_answer": "Each pan is equipped with a silicone-coated handle designed to resist heat, providing a safer experience during cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_614", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is a lid included with the purchase of the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti 12-inch saute pan is sold individually and does not come with a lid, even though the product description might refer to sets that include lids.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_615", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is this skillet designed to be oven-safe for baking purposes?", "long_answer": "Yes, the skillet is categorized as oven-safe, allowing it to be utilized not only for stovetop cooking but also for baking activities within an oven.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_471", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm not looking to shell out a lot, just need a simple pan under 20 dollars. What's the cheapest you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_472", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that ain't too bold in color. Got any grey or silver ones from Norpro?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches` with asin: B0012BR1XU", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"silver\") AND brand = \"Norpro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"silver\") AND brand = \"Norpro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'silver') AND brand = 'Norpro';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_616", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is the Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet suitable for use on a campfire?", "long_answer": "The Utopia Kitchen Cast Iron Skillet is designed to be used on multiple heat sources, such as stovetops, ovens, and including directly on a campfire, highlighting its versatility in various cooking environments.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_473", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm looking for a good sized pan that can take some heat, at least larger than 12 inches and able to handle the average oven temp. What's the first product that comes to mind?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND size >= 12 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND size >= 12 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 350 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_617", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is the tempered glass lid designed to fit securely on the pan and help in heat retention for faster cooking?", "long_answer": "The tempered glass lid is specifically designed to fit securely on the pan, aiding in the retention of heat, which contributes to faster cooking outcomes by trapping in the warmth.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_474", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I need a big pan from USA Pan in either copper or grey. Which is the largest one you got in these colors?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"grey\") AND brand = \"USA Pan\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"grey\") AND brand = \"USA Pan\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"grey\") AND brand = \"USA Pan\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'USA Pan' AND color IN ('copper', 'grey') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_618", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Does the ZWILLING Spirit Fry Pan have an environmentally friendly non-stick coating?", "long_answer": "The pan has an eco-friendly ceramic non-stick coating, which is a safer choice for the environment as it does not emit harmful fumes when used at high temperatures, setting it apart from conventional non-stick coatings known for their negative environmental impact.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_177", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is this pan suitable for use with my compact baking appliance?", "long_answer": "Given that smaller baking appliances often feature limited interior room, the size of this pan may not be suitable, potentially preventing the appliance door from closing properly or hindering the efficient distribution of heat.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with rectangular shapes are not suitable for small countertop ovens where their size might prevent the door from closing or limit the circulation of heat due to limited space.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "rectangular", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_475", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm cooking for a big family event, so I need a massive pan. Which one's the largest in your collection?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_619", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are protective liners included with the pans to prevent scratching when stacked?", "long_answer": "The set comes with protective liners designed to be placed between the pans during storage, which helps prevent the surfaces from getting scratched when they are stacked on top of each other.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_620", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does the pan come pre-seasoned from the manufacturer?", "long_answer": "The pan is not pre-seasoned. It arrives with a protective layer applied that must be removed prior to performing the initial seasoning yourself, as per the instructions provided by the manufacturer.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_476", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I fancy the ZWILLING J.A. Henckels brand, but am a hardcore oven user. Let me know which one of their pans can handle the highest temperature.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_477", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I need a pan that won't flinch at a 500-degree oven and has got a decent size too. Can ya tell me the biggest one you have that can handle the heat?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_478", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I've been using Utopia Kitchen products for a long time and I'm pretty happy with them. Can you find me the largest pan they have in their offering?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch` with asin: B00X4WQMAS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Utopia Kitchen' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_479", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I’m gonna need to heat things up in the oven. Give me a pan that can take more than 500F. But remember, it's gotta be All-Clad or Utopia Kitchen only.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('All-Clad', 'Utopia Kitchen') AND oven_safe_temperature > 500;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_480", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I don't want anything from USA Pan and I need a pan bigger than 8 inches. Give me the first product that meets these criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" AND size > 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" AND size > 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'USA Pan' AND size > 8 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_481", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I don't need anything fancy, just the biggest pan you've got that can handle really high temperature, like 600F. But the size must be larger than 12 inches for the meals I'm planning. Got anything like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_621", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan?", "long_answer": "Using metal utensils with the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan is not recommended, as it can damage the nonstick coating. To protect the pan's surface and prolong its lifespan, utensils made of nylon, silicone, or wood are advised.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_482", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Listen, I'm after a pan of minimum 10 inches, and mind you it's got to be either from USA Pan or Chicago Metallic. Just give me one option to consider.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Chicago Metallic\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Chicago Metallic\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND (brand = 'USA Pan' OR brand = 'Chicago Metallic') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_622", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the pot's bottom have a sufficient diameter for cooking methods such as frying and sautéing?", "long_answer": "The pot features a wider bottom, which customers find suitable and appreciate for a variety of cooking tasks, especially including frying and sautéing.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_623", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the vented glass lid with strainer holes perform effectively for draining and steaming purposes?", "long_answer": "The vented glass lid, equipped with strainer holes, is regarded as a convenient and effective addition by numerous customers, primarily because it allows for the draining of pasta and the steaming of vegetables without the necessity for a separate straining tool.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_624", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is the bottom of the saucepan designed to be compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The saucepan's bottom is made of uncoated hard-anodized aluminum which may not work well with induction cooktops. It is important to verify whether the specific model of the cookware is labeled as induction compatible before use.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_483", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I am dealing with some big meals here and need a pan that's at least 10 inches. Get me the one that can stand the highest oven temperature.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_625", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils on the non-stick surface of the Madeleine pan?", "long_answer": "Using metal utensils with sharp edges, such as knives, can be harmful to the pan's non-stick coating. To preserve the quality and extend the life of the pan, it is best to use utensils made of silicone, wood, or plastic.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_626", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "What is the weight characteristic of the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is characterized as lightweight, facilitating ease of handling and compatibility with toaster ovens.", "short_answer": "lightweight", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_627", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Does the weight of the pan set strike a balance between quality and functionality?", "long_answer": "Customer feedback suggests that the pan possesses a substantial feel that is associated with quality, yet it is not excessively heavy, thus achieving a practical balance between conveying sturdiness and being manageable to handle.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_628", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the T-fal Professional pan suitable for deep-frying large quantities of food?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Professional pan, featuring deep sides, is capable of shallow frying or sautéing; however, it is not engineered with the intention of deep-frying large amounts of food.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_178", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I enjoy preparing omelets; would this pan be appropriate for that task?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the pan's circular design promotes uniform heat distribution throughout its surface, which is perfect for preparing sensitive dishes such as omelets, guaranteeing they are cooked uniformly and softly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_629", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is this cast iron skillet suitable for oven use?", "long_answer": "The skillet is designed to be oven-safe, allowing for various cooking methods including baking, braising, and roasting. Its versatility permits seamless transition from stovetop cooking to oven baking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_179", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is there a risk of encountering hot spots when I sauté vegetables in this pan?", "long_answer": "No, you are not supposed to encounter hot spots when sautéing vegetables, since the pan's rounded design ensures even heat distribution, essential for uniformly cooking vegetables during sautéing.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_484", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I won't shell out a dime more than 10 bucks and I'm only interested in Chicago Metallic. Find me a pan that meets both these conditions.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND brand = 'Chicago Metallic';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_485", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I ain't splurging more than 30 dollars on a pan, but it better withstand at least 600 degrees in the oven. So which pan do you suggest?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 600;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_486", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I'm not interested in anything from Copper Chef and I can't shell out more than 50 bucks. What's the biggest pan you have outside of that brand within that price limit?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND price < 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND price < 50 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND price < 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Copper Chef' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_630", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the aluminum encapsulated base of this cookware come into direct contact with food?", "long_answer": "The aluminum encapsulated base is specifically created for efficient and uniform heating. Its design ensures that the aluminum does not make direct contact with the food, thereby maintaining the safety of the cookware for food preparation.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_487", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I've had it with my Matfer Bourgeat pans. Can you find me a different brand of pan that can handle higher than average oven temperatures? Oh, and it better be the biggest you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Matfer Bourgeat' AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_631", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it possible to start cooking a steak on the stovetop and then finish it in the oven with this pan?", "long_answer": "This pan is designed to be used on both the stovetop and in the oven, allowing for cooking methods that involve searing on the stovetop followed by baking in the oven.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_488", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I need a good-sized pan for my cooking. What's the first product you got from either Chicago Metallic or Norpro that's at least 8 inches?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Chicago Metallic\", \"Norpro\") AND size >= 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Chicago Metallic\", \"Norpro\") AND size >= 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Chicago Metallic', 'Norpro') AND size >= 8 ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_180", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "My kitchen features numerous tight corners and limited space. Will storing this pan pose any difficulties for me?", "long_answer": "Indeed, you may face challenges when trying to store a round-shaped pan in a kitchen that has numerous awkward corners and restricted space, since its shape is not conducive to efficiently utilizing those spaces. Opting for a pan that more closely conforms to the peculiarities of your kitchen's layout would probably be a more appropriate choice.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_632", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Does the stainless steel pan show signs of tarnishing or discoloration after being used?", "long_answer": "Reports from some customers indicate that tarnishing may occur over time with the stainless steel pan, particularly when it is subjected to high heat. However, this discoloration does not impair the pan's performance or functionality.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_633", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "What is the exact depth measurement of the T-fal Professional fry pan?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Professional fry pan features a depth of approximately 2 1/2 inches, providing ample cooking space suitable for various dishes that require more volume.", "short_answer": "2 1/2 inches", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_634", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Can the Lodge Cast Iron Skillet withstand high-temperature cooking without damage?", "long_answer": "The Lodge Cast Iron Skillet can indeed endure very high temperatures, which makes it an excellent choice for cooking methods that require searing, such as when cooking meats, as cast iron is known for its high heat tolerance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_635", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Do the pan's rims feature an outward roll to facilitate easier pouring?", "long_answer": "The pan's design includes rolled rims that are specifically intended to make pouring easier and more efficient. However, there is a suggestion from some customers that, for added precision, utilizing a guide spoon when pouring could be beneficial.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_489", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm looking for a sturdy pan that can withstand high oven temperatures, more than 600F. But blue just ain't my color. Get me one that fits this description, won't you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT color = \"blue\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT color = \"blue\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND color <> 'blue';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_636", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "What material is the pan primarily made of?", "long_answer": "The pan is primarily constructed using tri-ply stainless steel, which provides excellent heat conduction and contributes to the pan's durability.", "short_answer": "tri-ply stainless steel", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_637", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does Bialetti offer complementary pans to create a matching cookware set?", "long_answer": "Bialetti provides a variety of cookware options, allowing customers to select complementary pieces and form their own matching set based on their cooking requirements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_490", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I don't care for Copper Chef so don't bother showing me those. Give me the largest pan you have from any other brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Copper Chef' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_181", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is this pan suitable for use under a broiler?", "long_answer": "No, it's advisable to refrain from using this non-stick skillet in a broiler as the extreme temperatures can damage the non-stick surface. For broiling, opt for pans that are explicitly designed to withstand broiler heat.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with delicate non-stick coatings cannot be used for cooking methods that involve metal utensils or very high heat, to avoid damaging the surface.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_491", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I'm not a fan of Chicago Metallic, and I need a pan larger than 8 inches. Hook me up with your best product fitting these conditions.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Chicago Metallic' AND size > 8 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_492", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I need a big pan, at least 10 inches, and I don't want any brand other than Chicago Metallic or T-fal. What's your best option?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand IN (\"Chicago Metallic\", \"T-fal\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand IN (\"Chicago Metallic\", \"T-fal\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND (brand = 'Chicago Metallic' OR brand = 'T-fal') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_638", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Should the surface of a newly purchased cast-iron skillet feel rough to the touch?", "long_answer": "It is common for a cast-iron skillet to possess a somewhat rough and pebbled surface after the casting process. This texture typically diminishes gradually, becoming smoother and acquiring non-stick properties with consistent seasoning and usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_493", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I'm looking to spice up my kitchen with some color but I only trust Cuisinart and ZWILLING J.A. Henckels. Can you help me find the cheapest green or grey pan from these brands?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"grey\") AND brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"grey\") AND brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"grey\") AND brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('green', 'grey') AND brand IN ('Cuisinart', 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_494", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I am after a pan that's at least 8 inches, you know, something big enough to cook a weeknight dinner. Oh, and it has to be in blue or green. What's the first option you have for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND (color = 'blue' OR color = 'green') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_639", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the pan suitable for broiling, roasting, and baking?", "long_answer": "The pan is versatile and customers have successfully used it for broiling, roasting, and baking, alongside cooking items that require grease drainage such as bacon.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_182", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is this pan suitable for preparing acidic sauces, considering that it's not dishwasher-safe?", "long_answer": "Designed for hand washing, the pan offers advantages like effective heat retention, ideal for conventional cooking techniques. However, it's worth noting the potential reactivity with acidic ingredients. Depending on its composition, extra caution may be necessary when concocting acidic recipes to ensure the pan’s durability.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are ideally used for traditional or specialized cooking methods that take advantage of their unique material properties, such as the heat retention of cast iron.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_640", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is the pan compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The pan is explicitly designed with a magnetized base to facilitate rapid heat transfer, making it perfectly compatible with induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_495", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm in need of a frying pan that can handle some serious heat, something above 600F. Got any cheap ones from Ozeri?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Ozeri' AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_183", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Does this pan ensure even cooking on all types of stoves?", "long_answer": "Our aluminum and copper frying pans and skillets are renowned for their superior heat conductivity, ensuring evenly cooked meals. Nevertheless, when using an induction cooktop, bear in mind that these materials lack intrinsic compatibility because they don't possess magnetic characteristics. Therefore, without a ferromagnetic plate to enable induction, cooking efficacy may be affected.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_641", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the electric wok designed with a non-stick coating?", "long_answer": "The electric wok does not have a non-stick coating; instead, it features a durable stainless-steel body.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_642", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is this pan likely to warp with proper use according to the manufacturer's guidelines?", "long_answer": "Under normal circumstances adhering to the manufacturer's usage instructions, the pan is designed not to warp. Nonetheless, some instances of warping have been reported, possibly due to variations in use and the level of heat applied, which can happen with pans from any brand.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_643", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Does the surface of this pan have a flat design or is it designed with grooves?", "long_answer": "The pan's surface is not flat; it features a perforated design complete with grooves and \"dimples\" that facilitate the drainage of grease, thereby contributing to healthier cooking outcomes.", "short_answer": "grooves and \"dimples\"", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_644", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Does the electrical cord for the wok tend to disconnect easily during use?", "long_answer": "There have been reports from some customers indicating that the electrical cord might not remain securely connected during usage. It is important to make sure the cord is properly attached to the wok to ensure optimal performance and avoid any difficulties while cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_496", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm not here for any Anolon pans, but I need something that can take the heat, you know, like 500F or more. Find me the cheapest you got of those.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND NOT brand = \"Anolon\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND NOT brand = \"Anolon\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND NOT brand = \"Anolon\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Anolon' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_645", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Can the Cuisinart 719-16 saucepan cook rice effectively without causing scorching?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart 719-16 saucepan is commonly used by customers to cook rice. They report that it provides even heat distribution, which helps in cooking rice successfully without any scorching.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_646", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Can the stainless steel pan withstand high-heat cooking methods like broiling?", "long_answer": "Yes, the pan in question is constructed of stainless steel, a material celebrated for its robustness and enduring qualities, making it well-equipped to handle high-heat cooking applications, including broiling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_647", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "What materials are used in the non-stick coating of the pan?", "long_answer": "The pan features a non-stick ceramic coating that is free from both PTFE and PFOA, reflecting an environmentally friendly choice in its design.", "short_answer": "ceramic", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_497", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Look, I'm in the market for a copper pan but I don't want to pay an arm and a leg for it. Can you find me one that's cheaper than your average price?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND color = \"copper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND color = \"copper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' AND price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans);"}}
{"id": "search_qa_498", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm partial to \"All-Clad\" and \"Tramontina\". Can you dig up the cheapest pan from either of these brands for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch` with asin: B009HBKQR0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"Tramontina\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"Tramontina\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"All-Clad\", \"Tramontina\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('All-Clad', 'Tramontina') \nORDER BY price ASC\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_648", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Does the pan come with a recipe book included in the purchase?", "long_answer": "There is no recipe book provided as a standard with the pan; however, some customers have noted that they found instructions or recipes included on the packaging. For more cooking options, an abundant selection of recipes can be accessed online that are tailored for this pan's size.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_649", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is the pan considered heavy by users when handled?", "long_answer": "The pan is a heavy-duty cooking utensil designed to distribute heat evenly. Due to this construction feature, the pan has additional weight, making it heavier than some users anticipate.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_499", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm only looking for either a \"Copper Chef\" or \"Ozeri\" pan. Which one can survive the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Ozeri\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Ozeri\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Ozeri\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Copper Chef', 'Ozeri') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_650", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is it safe to use dish soap to clean this pan?", "long_answer": "It is not recommended to use dish soap on this pan because it may strip away the seasoning. Instead, you should clean the pan by wiping it with a paper towel or rinsing it with hot water, and re-season it if needed.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_500", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I've had enough of Norpro and I need a pan that can take the heat, over 400F. What's the cheapest one you got that doesn't come from Norpro?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Norpro\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Norpro\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Norpro\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Norpro' AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_184", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is it possible for me to conveniently wash this pan in the dishwasher after frying a steak?", "long_answer": "Due to its specialized material properties that are crafted for traditional or specific cooking methods necessitating superior heat retention, such as steak preparation, this pan is not suitable for dishwasher cleaning. To preserve its quality and functionality, it is advisable to hand wash the pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are ideally used for traditional or specialized cooking methods that take advantage of their unique material properties, such as the heat retention of cast iron.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_501", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I'm trying to make some larger meals and need a pan that's at least 12 inches. I'm not looking to break the bank though, so find me the cheapest one you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_502", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I definitely don't want a green pan. Not my style. What's the cheapest non-green pan you got in stock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'green' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_651", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Does the cookware have a feature that allows me to observe the cooking process without removing the lid?", "long_answer": "The cookware comes with a lid constructed from break-resistant, domed glass, which enables you to visually monitor the food as it cooks while keeping the heat contained.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_652", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Is the All-Clad frying pan set suitable for high-heat methods like searing?", "long_answer": "The All-Clad frying pan set is designed to handle high-heat cooking and is particularly well-suited for methods like searing, where oils are used to achieve rich flavors and textures in foods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_503", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm a T-fal fan and I want a pan that won't warp in the oven over 400F. Show me the cheapest you got.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'T-fal' AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_185", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Can the lid handle withstand high temperatures without emitting any hazardous materials?", "long_answer": "It depends. If the pan's tempered glass lid has a handle with a coating that deteriorates because of high heat or other conditions, this could result in the introduction of undesirable substances into your food, which would be less than ideal.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids fail to meet the requirements for completely non-reactive cooking conditions, especially if any sort of coating on the lid's handle or edges were to degrade and interact with the food.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_653", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is this Madeleine pan suitable for novice bakers?", "long_answer": "The Madeleine pan has been reported to yield good results for new bakers, suggesting that it is user-friendly and appropriate for individuals who are inexperienced in making Madeleines.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_654", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is the pan intended for baking multiple individual loaves or buns simultaneously?", "long_answer": "The pan is crafted for baking a singular large loaf or bun. It does not have dividers for individual portions, but it includes lines that suggest where to cut or separate the baked good after it has been baked.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_504", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm thinking of a blue pan that's oven safe at extremely high temperatures. Which one can withstand the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_655", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Can the loose handle of a Bialetti pan be tightened without voiding the warranty?", "long_answer": "It is not recommended to attempt tightening the handle of a Bialetti pan yourself because doing so may void the warranty. In case of issues with the handle, contacting customer service is the correct course of action to ensure the problem is resolved without affecting the warranty coverage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_186", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is it safe to use my metal spatula with this pan without damaging it?", "long_answer": "Avoid using metal utensils with this pan to preserve its integrity. Constructed from anodized aluminum, the pan is robust but susceptible to scratching from metal implements. Such damage may impair the pan's non-reactive qualities and reduce its lifespan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with anodized aluminum are not suitable for use with metal utensils that can scratch the hardened surface, potentially compromising its non-reactive properties.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_656", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "What type of warranty is included with the purchase of the pan?", "long_answer": "The pan includes a limited lifetime warranty, indicating that the manufacturer guarantees the quality of the product and offers support for any issues that might occur during its lifetime.", "short_answer": "limited lifetime warranty", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_505", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm not about to bust my wallet on a pan. If it's from Matfer Bourgeat and under 10 dollars, count me in. Can you find a pan like that for me?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Matfer Bourgeat' AND price < 10;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_187", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for dishes that necessitate swift temperature adjustments during cooking?", "long_answer": "No, this pan is unsuitable for those recipes as it is equipped with a cast iron lid. Due to the nature of its material, it is vulnerable to rapid temperature fluctuations and is at risk of thermal shock. This may cause the lid to crack or warp, ultimately compromising the pan's integrity.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a cast iron lid cannot be used for quick cooking methods that rely on rapid temperature changes, as cast iron can be prone to thermal shock when exposed to sudden shifts in temperature, potentially leading to cracking or warping.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "cast iron lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_188", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is this pan suitable for use on both an induction cooktop and over a campfire during camping trips?", "long_answer": "Absolutely, this pan is compatible with both induction cooktops and open flames, such as those found in campfires. Its cast iron lid enables it to accommodate diverse heating methods, offering exceptional versatility in cooking, regardless of your location.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a cast iron lid are ideally used for cooking on various types of heat sources, including induction and open flame, providing versatility across different cooking environments.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "cast iron lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_657", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the surface of the pan designed to be smooth or porous?", "long_answer": "The pan features a double-layer nonstick interior that is designed to be smooth. Proper maintenance, such as avoiding high heat and using appropriate cleaning methods, is necessary to prevent the surface from becoming porous over time.", "short_answer": "smooth", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_506", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm going to be cranking the oven up past 500, and I need something tough from Utopia Kitchen. Which pan can withstand that kind of heat?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Utopia Kitchen' AND oven_safe_temperature > 500;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_507", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm not looking to break the bank, but I need a pan that's bigger than 12 inches and costs less than 10 bucks. Can you also make sure it can handle some heat? Find me the one with the highest oven-safe temperature.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND size > 12 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND size > 12 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND size > 12 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND price < 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_508", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Cooking at high temps is no joke, buddy, especially when looking to keep the style intact. Single out the pan which is copper-colored and can take more than 400F for me, will you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND color = \"copper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND color = \"copper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' AND oven_safe_temperature > 400;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_509", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "No offense, but I don't want any pans from Chicago Metallic. I need something sizable, at least 12 inches. What's the most heat resistant pan you got that fits my requirements?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND size >= 12 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND size >= 12 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND size >= 12 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Chicago Metallic' AND size >= 12 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_658", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the T-Fal pot appropriate for cooking recipes that require extended cooking times?", "long_answer": "The T-Fal pot is designed to handle a range of cooking methods, which encompass recipes that call for extended periods of cooking. To maintain the integrity of the nonstick coating, it is recommended to opt for lower heat settings during use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_659", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the saucepan's mirror finish remain durable with proper maintenance?", "long_answer": "The saucepan's mirror finish is designed to endure and keep its professional appearance, provided that it is well-maintained with hand washing and occasional polishing.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_510", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm looking for a blue or grey pan but I don't want anything from Matfer Bourgeat. Can you find me the one that can handle the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"grey\") AND NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"grey\") AND NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"grey\") AND NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (color = 'blue' OR color = 'grey') \nAND brand <> 'Matfer Bourgeat' \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_189", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is this pan suitable for both intense high-heat searing and delicate simmering?", "long_answer": "Certainly. The carbon steel composition of the pan lends it the flexibility to handle high-heat searing as well as low-heat simmering with ease. Being a wok, it is designed to withstand intense heat for cooking, while also providing the capability for careful temperature regulation, ensuring that sauces and other components can be simmered gently without the risk of burning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with carbon steel construction are known for their rapid conduction of heat and the ability to respond quickly to temperature changes, making them excellent for the dynamic cooking methods used in wok cooking.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "wok", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_511", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I care about quality and brand. Show me the biggest pan you've got from either Cuisinart or ZWILLING J.A. Henckels.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Cuisinart', 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_660", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Does the pan retain its shine and visual appeal with regular use and proper care?", "long_answer": "With regular use and proper care, including occasional polishing with a suitable cleaner, the pan is designed to maintain its shine and aesthetic appeal over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_661", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Does food tend to stick to the rivets, necessitating more cleaning effort?", "long_answer": "Although it is not a widespread issue, some customers have reported that food tends to stick around the rivets, suggesting that more diligent or frequent cleaning may be necessary to prevent buildup.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_662", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "How satisfied are consumers with the safety and durability of the pan's construction materials?", "long_answer": "Customers generally express satisfaction with the pan's construction and materials, regarding them as safe for use. However, there have been some concerns raised about the durability of those materials, noting a decline in condition over extended periods. With regular maintenance and correct usage, the longevity of the pan can be significantly increased.", "short_answer": "mixed", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_663", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this non-stick pan?", "long_answer": "Non-metal utensils are recommended for use with this pan to protect its non-stick coating and prolong its lifespan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_512", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm only interested in green or silver pans, but they gotta withstand some serious heat. Can you find me the one with the highest oven-safe temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"green\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"green\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('green', 'silver') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_664", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the T-fal saucepan have non-stick coating on both its interior and exterior surfaces?", "long_answer": "The T-fal saucepan is designed with non-stick surfaces on both the interior for effortless cooking and cleanup, as well as on the exterior.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_513", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm not looking to burn my wallet for a pan, and it has to match my kitchen. What's the cheapest grey pan you have that's under or exactly 20 dollars?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND color = \"grey\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND color = \"grey\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color='grey' AND price <= 20 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_190", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Could using a dishwasher to clean the pan pose a risk of warping it?", "long_answer": "Using a dishwasher to clean this pan poses no considerable risk of distortion. It is constructed from materials that were selected for their resilience to withstand the temperatures and water pressure of a dishwasher, ensuring it maintains its form.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_514", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I don't have time for any fancy stuff, just show me a pan from either Utopia Kitchen or Anolon. And, make it quick!", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray` with asin: B000069RBK", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Anolon\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Anolon\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Utopia Kitchen', 'Anolon') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_665", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Does the skillet have a smooth or rough interior surface?", "long_answer": "The interior surface of the skillet is typically slightly rougher compared to some other brands, though this characteristic does not impair its cooking capabilities. With regular seasoning and use, the surface can become smoother.", "short_answer": "rough", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_666", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the pot include a vented glass lid to prevent boiling over and allow monitoring of the cooking process?", "long_answer": "The pot is equipped with a vented glass lid, which serves the dual purpose of allowing one to observe the food while it cooks and helping to avoid incidents of boiling over.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_191", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "What kind of maintenance will be needed for this pan as time goes on?", "long_answer": "Over the years, maintaining this pan will demand extra care compared to other choices, given that it is not dishwasher-safe. To ensure it continues to function optimally and retains its aesthetic appeal, it is necessary to hand wash it and carry out specific maintenance procedures, such as re-seasoning, as a routine part of its care.", "short_answer": "handwash", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" fail to meet the requirements for easy maintenance and may involve extra steps like re-seasoning or careful hand-polishing to uphold their performance and appearance standards.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_667", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is this skillet resistant to thermal shock from sudden temperature changes?", "long_answer": "This skillet, made of cast iron, is not designed to withstand sudden changes in temperature, as drastic shifts from hot to cold may cause the skillet to crack or warp, thus it's recommended to avoid such thermal shocks.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_668", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does the white ceramic interior of the appliance improve visibility during cooking?", "long_answer": "The white ceramic interior enhances visibility while cooking due to its light color, which contrasts with the food, making it easier to monitor the cooking process compared to appliances with darker finishes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_669", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart FCT23-24NS Crepe Pan is specifically designed to be compatible with induction cooktops, ensuring that it can be used effectively on such stoves.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_515", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I've got a thing for copper colored pans, but I'm so over Lodge. What's another brand you carry that has what I'm looking for?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND NOT brand = \"Lodge\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND NOT brand = \"Lodge\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' AND brand != 'Lodge';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_670", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Can the Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri be safely used in an oven?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri is specifically designed for stovetop use rather than oven use, as it is not advertised as being oven-safe. To ensure both safety and optimal performance, it is recommended to use the pan on the cooktop.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_516", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm not interested in anything from Presto and I've only got 20 bucks. Show me the biggest pan you can that fits my criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" AND price < 20 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" AND price < 20 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" AND price < 20 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Presto' AND price <= 20 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_517", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I've been keeping an eye on Utopia Kitchen and Norpro brands, but I need to watch my spending. Can you find me a pan from these brands that's priced at or below the average cost?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch` with asin: B00X4WQMAS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Norpro\") AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Norpro\") AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Utopia Kitchen', 'Norpro') \nAND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans WHERE brand IN ('Utopia Kitchen', 'Norpro'));"}}
{"id": "search_qa_518", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm looking for a big pan, at least 12 inches, from T-fal. What's the product ID for that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand = \"T-fal\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand = \"T-fal\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND brand = 'T-fal';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_671", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Does the material of the skillet contribute to its weight?", "long_answer": "The skillet is made of cast iron, a material known for its weightiness. Cast iron cookware is generally heavy due to the material's properties that provide excellent heat retention and allow for even cooking throughout the food.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_672", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the pan designed for making crepes also suitable for other cooking methods like sautéing?", "long_answer": "The pan is versatile and not limited to making crepes; it can indeed be used for sautéing as well as other cooking methods, as verified by customer reports expressing satisfaction with its performance in various cooking applications.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_673", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Can the Bialetti fry pan be safely used in an oven?", "long_answer": "This specific fry pan manufactured by Bialetti is not intended for use in an oven, as it lacks an oven-safe design.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_519", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I've had enough of Utopia Kitchen's stuff. Can you sort me out with the highest oven-safe temperature pan not from them?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Utopia Kitchen' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_674", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the Presto 5900 electric wok suitable for deep frying?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 electric wok is primarily designed for stir-frying and may not reach the necessary temperatures for deep frying when using more than 3 tablespoons of oil, as indicated by customer feedback. Therefore, it's recommended to choose a kitchen appliance that is specifically made for deep frying to achieve optimal results.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_520", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Look, I don't want any other color or brand. Just find me a blue pan from either Norpro or Lodge, okay?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"Lodge\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"Lodge\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' AND (brand = 'Norpro' OR brand = 'Lodge');"}}
{"id": "search_qa_521", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I've been eyeing pans from Copper Chef and Utopia Kitchen. Point me to the first product you got from either of these brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Copper Chef', 'Utopia Kitchen') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_675", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Can metal utensils be safely used with this Bialetti saute pan without damaging it?", "long_answer": "Although the product description states that the Bialetti saute pan is safe to use with metal utensils, customer feedback suggests that it's best to avoid metal to preserve the non-stick surface. It is recommended to use nylon, silicone, or wood utensils in order to prolong the pan's lifespan and maintain its cooking performance.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_522", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I do a lot of big meals and I'm not messing around when it comes to oven heat. Do you have a pan that's at least 12 inches and can withstand more than 400F? Show me the first one you find.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_676", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is the Tramontina nonstick fry pan considered heavy compared to other nonstick pans?", "long_answer": "The Tramontina nonstick fry pan is built using heavy-gauge aluminum, which may contribute to a heavier weight in comparison to some other nonstick pans. However, this construction is beneficial for even heat distribution and increased durability.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_523", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I need a pan that can take the heat and won't warp in my oven — it has to withstand over 600F. Oh, and I'm tired of black ones. Give me the first one you find that's not black.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT color = \"black\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT color = \"black\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND color != 'black' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_677", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Do the handles of this cookware remain cool to the touch while being used for cooking?", "long_answer": "The cookware features ergonomically designed handles that are specifically crafted to remain cool during the cooking process, providing both comfort and safety. This has been corroborated by feedback from customers who have generally reported favorable experiences regarding the temperature of the handles while cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_524", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I need a tough-as-nails pan that won't whimper in a 400-degree oven. Show me the one that can take the heat.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_678", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is the non-stick coating of the Copper Chef pan resistant to scratches when using metal utensils or abrasive cleaning materials?", "long_answer": "The non-stick coating on the Copper Chef pan is durable but not completely impervious to scratches. To reduce the chance of damaging the coating, it is recommended to use utensils made of non-metallic materials and to steer clear of abrasive cleaning products.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_679", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the stainless-steel surface prone to tarnishing or staining after being subjected to high-heat cooking?", "long_answer": "After high-heat cooking, a few users have observed some slight discoloration on the stainless-steel surface of the wok, but it does not impact the cookware's performance. Such tarnish or stains can typically be removed utilizing a stainless-steel cleaner, thus restoring the appearance of the wok.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_525", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm not shelling out more than 10 bucks for a pan. Got anything from Bialetti or Utopia Kitchen that won't break the bank?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Utopia Kitchen\") AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Bialetti', 'Utopia Kitchen') AND price <= 10;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_526", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm trying to save some cash, and the Ozeri brand has never let me down before. Show me the biggest pan they have that's under 20 dollars.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Ozeri' AND price < 20 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_527", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm bored of my black pan and looking for a change. Can you find me a pan, which is any color but black and larger than 10 inches? Just give me one option.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND size > 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND size > 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'black' AND size > 10 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_528", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Look, I don't do blue in my kitchen. Give me the highest oven-safe temperature pan you've got, just make sure it's not blue.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color!='blue' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_529", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I do a lot of hefty baking and need a big strong pan that can withstand at least 500F and is more than a foot across. Give me the best option you've got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_530", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm a bit picky on style - looking for a T-fal pan and only in silver or black. Got anything like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black` with asin: B004VJMT78", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'T-fal' AND (color = 'silver' OR color = 'black');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_680", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are the silicon-coated handles of the pans safe for oven use?", "long_answer": "The silicon-coated handles of these pans are designed to be heat-resistant, making them safe for use in an oven. However, the maximum temperature they can withstand is determined by the manufacturer's use and care instructions that should be referred to for precise information.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_681", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Does the hard-anodized aluminum saucepan have a lightweight design?", "long_answer": "The saucepan, constructed from heavy-gauge, hard-anodized aluminum, is built to be durable and long-lasting. While it is made to be manageable, it does have a certain heft to it, particularly when full, as some users have reported.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_531", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I don't want any products from Tramontina. Tell me about the largest pan you got that's not from that brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Tramontina' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_682", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is advised to be hand washed according to the product description. Users have reported a decrease in durability after dishwasher use; therefore, hand washing is recommended to extend the pan set's lifespan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_192", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Will the pan's lid retain its non-toxic characteristics over time?", "long_answer": "Over time, the tempered glass lid of the pan might lose its non-toxic properties. Should the coating on the handle or the lid's rim begin to deteriorate, it could lead to undesirable reactions with your food, potentially compromising the non-toxic nature of your cooking space.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids fail to meet the requirements for completely non-reactive cooking conditions, especially if any sort of coating on the lid's handle or edges were to degrade and interact with the food.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_683", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is this pan compatible with induction hobs?", "long_answer": "This pan is designed to be suitable for all types of hobs, induction hobs included, allowing for versatile cooking options.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_532", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Look, I'm not burning money. I need a pan under 50 bucks from either Utopia Kitchen or Norpro. What's the best you can dig up for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch` with asin: B00X4WQMAS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Norpro\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Norpro\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND (brand = 'Utopia Kitchen' OR brand = 'Norpro') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_684", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Can this pan be used reliably in a professional kitchen environment?", "long_answer": "The pan features heavy-duty construction, enabling it to withstand the rigorous demands of a professional kitchen, thereby making it suitable for use in such environments.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_193", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is this pan capable of maintaining an even temperature throughout for dishes that require consistent heat?", "long_answer": "Indeed, a saucepan is crafted to distribute heat evenly, ensuring a stable temperature that is ideal for recipes sensitive to varying heat levels, like fine sauces or custards that may quickly burn.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan are known for their even heat distribution which is essential for preventing hot spots that could scorch delicate sauces or custards.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_685", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is a discount coupon available for this product when purchasing from Amazon?", "long_answer": "The product does have a promotional offer that provides a 5% discount for those buying it on Amazon, although certain restrictions may be in place that could affect eligibility or usage of this discount.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_194", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "In recipes requiring exact cooking durations, do I need to more diligently monitor the food while employing this pan?", "long_answer": "Indeed, owing to its square shape, you might need to keep a closer watch on your food and possibly tweak the cooking times. The corners may cook differently than the rest of the pan, so staying vigilant is smart to ensure the desired cooking consistency is reached.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with square shapes lack the capability to evenly cook foods in the corners at the same rate as the center, which may necessitate an adjusted cooking approach to prevent uneven baking results.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "square", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_533", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm cooking up a storm in a hot-ass oven and I need a tough Ozeri pan that can handle at least 500F. Can you find me one?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND brand = \"Ozeri\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Ozeri' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_534", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I have a thing for Copper Chef, you know. And I'm particularly keen on either a grey or a copper colored pan. Now can you find me one?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") AND brand = \"Copper Chef\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") AND brand = \"Copper Chef\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Copper Chef' AND (color = 'grey' OR color = 'copper');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_686", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is this pan compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "This pan is incompatible with induction cooktops; instead, it is specifically designed for electric, gas, ceramic, and glass stovetops.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_195", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it safe to frequently clean this pan in the dishwasher without causing harm?", "long_answer": "Certainly, you can confidently clean this pan in your dishwasher. It's crafted from robust materials such as stainless steel and aluminum, ensuring it can endure the intense conditions of a dishwasher without degrading.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_535", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm after a blue pan that can withstand at least 400 degrees in the oven. Don't break my bank though, what's your best cheap option?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'blue' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_687", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is seasoning required before using a new Copper Chef pan?", "long_answer": "Seasoning a Copper Chef pan is not required because it includes a nonstick coating designed to perform effectively without any additional seasoning process.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_688", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is it necessary to grease and flour a non-stick cake pan before baking?", "long_answer": "The non-stick nature of the pan is designed to aid in the easy release of cakes, but applying a light coating of butter and flour is still advised to further ensure that cakes do not stick, as recommended by various users.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_689", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the non-stick coating on this cookware prone to scratching or chipping under normal use?", "long_answer": "The non-stick coating on this product has been reviewed by customers as durable, with reports indicating that it resists chipping and scratching well, suggesting it remains intact with typical usage over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_196", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is it possible to conveniently clean this pan in the dishwasher following the preparation of a steak?", "long_answer": "We advise against placing this pan in the dishwasher because of its distinctive material composition, tailored for conventional or gourmet culinary techniques that demand superior heat retention, like preparing steak. To preserve its quality and functionality, hand washing is the preferred method.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are ideally used for traditional or specialized cooking methods that take advantage of their unique material properties, such as the heat retention of cast iron.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_536", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I ain't dropping more than 10 dollars for a pan. But it's gotta resist high oven temps of above 500F. Can you track down the best cheap pan for that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_197", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I recently acquired a new cooktop and want to ensure I purchase a pan that's compatible. Is there something specific I should look for?", "long_answer": "When looking for a new pan, opt for one with a round design for enhanced compatibility with different cooktops, especially newer induction ones. Just confirm that the pan is constructed from a magnetic material if you're using an induction cooktop to guarantee seamless functionality.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_537", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm gonna need a hefty pan that can handle heat over 450F and measures more than 10 inches. But I'm tight on cash, so find me the cheapest one you got that fits my requirement.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND size > 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND size > 10 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND size > 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_690", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Does food stick to the pan contrary to the advertisement claims when used correctly?", "long_answer": "When the pan is utilized properly, which includes using it on lower heat settings and with suitable oils, most customers report that foods do not stick. To maintain the nonstick quality, it is vital to care for and maintain the pan appropriately.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_691", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set designed with a non-stick surface?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Pan Set is constructed from stainless steel and does not feature a non-stick coating. Consumers often suggest applying a thin layer of oil or using foil lining to mitigate food adherence and facilitate cleaning.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_692", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Can the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan be safely washed in a dishwasher?", "long_answer": "The Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan is designed with a high-performance, reinforced PFOA-free nonstick surface, which allows it to be safely cleaned in a dishwasher without damaging the pan's quality and functionality.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_538", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I've heard some good things about this Ozeri pans. Could you find me a product ID for one of them?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Ozeri\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Ozeri\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Ozeri' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_198", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "May I put this pan in the dishwasher without concern for long-term damage?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this pan is built to endure the elevated temperatures and strong detergents typically present in dishwashers, maintaining its form and integrity through consistent wash cycles and resisting warping, rusting, or deterioration.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute feature resistance to both the high temperatures and strong chemicals typical in dishwashers, which ensures they do not warp, rust, or degrade quickly when exposed to such conditions regularly.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_539", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I tend to cook in high heats and my oven often reaches 450F. I need a non-green pan that can handle it. Which is the biggest one you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND NOT color = \"green\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND NOT color = \"green\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND NOT color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND color != 'green' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_540", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I do a lot of high-heat cooking and I'm looking for an oven-safe black pan. Do you have anything that can withstand at least 450 degrees Fahrenheit? Find me one, ASAP.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'black' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_541", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Alright, I need a Bialetti pan that's not over 30 dollars. Does anything pop up?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal` with asin: B000S6I4ZE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND brand = \"Bialetti\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND brand = \"Bialetti\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Bialetti' AND price <= 30;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_199", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Are there any particular things I should refrain from preparing in this pan?", "long_answer": "When utilizing a cast iron skillet, it's best to steer clear of extended cooking times for acidic ingredients. The acid may interact with the cast iron, eroding the essential seasoning that provides flavor and non-stick qualities, and it might also infuse a metallic flavor into your meal. Conversely, non-acidic foods can be prepared without any worries.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being made from cast iron cannot be used for acidic foods like tomato sauce for extended periods, as the acid can strip the seasoning and cause the food to take on a metallic taste.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "cast iron", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_693", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is the pan compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The pan is specifically designed for use on gas, electric, and ceramic glass cooktops, as indicated in the product metadata. There is no mention of compatibility with induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_694", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is the pan designed to be oven-safe for baking or roasting?", "long_answer": "The construction of the pan is designed to be versatile, making it suitable for oven use in addition to various stovetop applications including baking and roasting.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_695", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Does the Tramontina pan's nonstick coating contain PFOA?", "long_answer": "The Tramontina pan features a high-performance, reinforced nonstick coating that is free from PFOA, promoting safe and healthy cooking practices.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_696", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Does the unique corrugated surface design of the Hearth Bread Pan allow for even baking due to improved air circulation?", "long_answer": "The Hearth Bread Pan features a corrugated surface that promotes enhanced air circulation, leading to uniformly baked goods and facilitating the quick release of those goods once baked.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_200", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is this pan suitable for use under a broiler?", "long_answer": "Do not use this non-stick frying pan under a broiler, as the intense heat may damage the non-stick surface. For broiling, opt for pans that are expressly designed to be broiler-safe.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with delicate non-stick coatings cannot be used for cooking methods that involve metal utensils or very high heat, to avoid damaging the surface.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_201", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "May I simply place the pan in the dishwasher post-use for effortless cleaning?", "long_answer": "Unfortunately, these pans are not suitable for dishwasher use and lack dishwasher-safe capabilities. To maintain them in the best possible condition, it's essential to hand wash and properly care for them, which includes seasoning as required for specific materials.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" do not have a function of self-maintenance and will need regular seasoning (for cast iron or carbon steel) or polishing (for aesthetic reasons) to maintain their best condition.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_542", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Look, I've got a thing for black and green pans, and I need one that can withstand high oven temperatures. Which among these pans can handle the highest temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('black', 'green') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_543", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm looking for a copper pan for under 20 dollars. Just give me the biggest one you've got.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND price < 20 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND price < 20 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND price < 20 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' AND price < 20 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_202", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I have quite limited cupboard space; is this pan designed for easy storage when it's not in use?", "long_answer": "Round-shaped pans may not be the most space-efficient for storage in cramped kitchens, presenting a drawback when optimizing every inch is essential. If you must fit your cookware into a tight cupboard or shelf, square or more angular pans could prove more suitable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_544", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I've been cooking with Matfer Bourgeat pans and let me tell you, they need to withstand over 500F. Get me the cheapest one you have that is up to the task.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Matfer Bourgeat' AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_545", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Look, I need a big pan, specifically from either T-fal or All-Clad. Point me to the largest one you have from those brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"All-Clad\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"All-Clad\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"All-Clad\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('T-fal', 'All-Clad') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_546", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm a freak for All-Clad and I need a pan that can really take the heat, at least 500F. What's the best you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black` with asin: B0170TFNXM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND brand = \"All-Clad\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND brand = \"All-Clad\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'All-Clad' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC, price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_697", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "What is the maximum temperature the Madeleine Pan can withstand in an oven?", "long_answer": "The Madeleine Pan is designed to be oven safe and can tolerate temperatures up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit or 232 degrees Celsius. However, it should not be utilized under a broiler as this exceeds its intended usage parameters.", "short_answer": "450F / 232C", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_698", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the All-Clad Stainless 10-Inch fry pan heavier than other All-Clad fry pan models?", "long_answer": "The All-Clad Stainless 10-Inch fry pan features a 3-ply bonded construction making it less heavy than some of the 5-ply models from All-Clad, offering a balance between easy handling and durability for regular use.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_699", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is the lid designed to fit any 10 1/4-inch diameter Lodge pans?", "long_answer": "The lid is specifically designed to be interchangeable and should comfortably fit any other Lodge pans that have a diameter of 10 1/4 inches.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_203", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this pan without risking damage?", "long_answer": "Avoid using metal utensils with this pan to maintain its condition. Crafted from anodized aluminum, the pan is robust but susceptible to scratching from metal kitchen tools. Such scratches may impair the pan's non-reactive qualities and reduce its lifespan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with anodized aluminum are not suitable for use with metal utensils that can scratch the hardened surface, potentially compromising its non-reactive properties.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_700", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the T-fal Thermo-Spot heat indicator effective in signaling when the pan is adequately preheated?", "long_answer": "The Thermo-Spot heat indicator in T-fal pans performs as claimed for most customers, as it provides a clear visual signal that the pan has reached the appropriate preheating temperature, which enhances the cooking experience and is a feature well-regarded by users.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_547", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I ain’t looking to burn cash on fancy pans, but need something that wont burn up in the oven. Give me the cheapest pan you got, costing less than 10 dollars that can handle an oven temperature of over 500F.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_548", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I'm only interested in Cuisinart and Tramontina. Gimme the biggest pan you have from either of those brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Tramontina\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Tramontina\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Tramontina\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Cuisinart', 'Tramontina') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_701", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the entire Cuisinart French Classic pan constructed with tri-ply material?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart French Classic line features tri-ply construction not just on the bottom, but all the way up the sides as well, contributing to its ability to cook food evenly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_702", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is this skillet a good gift option for cooking enthusiasts or people who appreciate durable cookware?", "long_answer": "The skillet is an excellent choice as a gift, particularly for individuals who have a passion for cooking or value high-quality and versatile cookware. Its robustness and adaptability make it a thoughtful and practical present.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_204", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm concerned that chemicals from the dishwasher might affect the material of the pan. Should I be worried about this issue?", "long_answer": "Rest assured that chemicals from the dishwasher won't impact this pan. It's made with materials that can withstand the common chemicals in dishwasher detergents, so it will keep its integrity even after numerous wash cycles.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_549", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I need a pretty large pan that can withstand high oven temperatures, something over 10 inches and safe for more than 450F. What's the first thing you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_703", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is the Madeleine Pan made from durable carbon steel considered heavy or lightweight?", "long_answer": "Although the Madeleine Pan is made from durable carbon steel, it is designed to be lightweight. This design choice is appreciated by customers who prioritize ease of handling and convenience in storing the pan.", "short_answer": "lightweight", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_704", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the Presto 5900 Wok compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 is exclusively an electric wok with a built-in 1500W heating element and is not constructed for placement on any stove types, which encompasses induction cooktops. It operates independently by being plugged into an electrical outlet.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_705", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is this pan suitable for use on glass top stoves?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is specifically designed to sit securely and flat on glass top stoves, which ensures its suitability and performance on this type of cooking surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_550", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm doing some high-heat cooking and need a pan that can handle more than 450F in the oven. Find me the most affordable one you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_706", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Can this heavy-weight aluminized steel pan produce a golden brown texture on Madeleines?", "long_answer": "This pan, made of heavy-weight aluminized steel, provides even heat distribution, which greatly contributes to creating the desirable golden brown texture on Madeleines when they are baked as per the recommended guidelines.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_551", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I've got a thing for grey stuff, it matches my kitchen. Get me the cheapest grey pan you have in stock.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color='grey' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_707", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Does soaking the pan for cleaning result in rust formation?", "long_answer": "Soaking the pan for cleaning has led to rust marks for some customers, indicating that it is prone to rusting if not dried thoroughly post-wash.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_205", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is this type of pan suitable for stir-frying that requires high heat and rapid cooking?", "long_answer": "A cast iron skillet may not be ideally suited for stir-frying. Its gradual heat conductivity can hinder the pan from achieving the high temperatures needed for rapid cooking promptly, and its substantial weight could render it difficult to handle during the continuous motion stir-frying demands.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being made from cast iron are not recommended for rapid cooking or recipes requiring quick temperature changes, due to their slow heat conductivity and weight.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "cast iron", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_708", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the T-fal Specialty Handy Pot suitable for preparing soups and sauces?", "long_answer": "The T-fal Specialty Handy Pot is designed with a depth that is particularly well-suited for cooking soups and sauces, and it is also recognized for its convenience when it comes to cleaning, even after preparing complex sauces.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_709", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is the heavy gauge aluminized steel bread pan resistant to warping over time?", "long_answer": "The bread pan is made from heavy gauge aluminized steel, which is designed to be resistant to warping. Customer feedback suggests that the pan reliably maintains its shape with repeated use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_710", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "What is the country of origin for the manufacturing of USA Pan Bakeware?", "long_answer": "USA Pan Bakeware is crafted in the United States by a family-operated business, which takes pride in the high quality and dependability of their products.", "short_answer": "USA", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_552", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I want a pretty big pan, at least a foot across, but I've had it with those copper ones. Find me the cheapest you have that fits what I'm looking for.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND NOT color = \"copper\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND NOT color = \"copper\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND NOT color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color <> 'copper' AND size >= 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_711", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set large enough to fit two decent-sized steaks at the same time?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is sized sufficiently to hold two decent-sized steaks or a small roast simultaneously.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_206", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "My kitchen includes various awkward corners and limited space. Will storing this pan pose a problem?", "long_answer": "Certainly, you may find it challenging to store a round-shaped pan in a kitchen that has numerous awkward corners and constrained space, since its form doesn't efficiently utilize such areas. Opting for a pan that more appropriately conforms to the distinct contours of your kitchen might be a more fitting choice.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_553", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I do a lot of high-heat cooking and I need a pan that can handle the heat and has a decent size. What's the best you have that has an oven safe temperature over 400F and a size larger than 8 inches?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size > 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size > 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size > 8 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC, size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_554", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I have a thing for Cuisinart and Ozeri. Can you reorder your shelves and show me the first pan that's from either one of these brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Ozeri\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Cuisinart\", \"Ozeri\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Cuisinart', 'Ozeri') ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_712", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is the pan with dimensions of 12 x 5.63 x 2.25 inches suitable for use in a toaster oven?", "long_answer": "The pan can be used in a toaster oven provided the oven is spacious enough to fit the pan's dimensions and that the operating temperature does not exceed the pan's maximum temperature tolerance of 450F.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_713", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Does the underside of the lid of this cookware include features to manage condensation and keep dishes moist during cooking?", "long_answer": "The lid is equipped with tips on the underside designed to manage condensation effectively. The condensing liquids can drip down and moisten the food, essentially basting it and helping to maintain moisture in the dishes throughout the cooking process.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_714", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this frying pan?", "long_answer": "Metal utensils can be used with this frying pan as its durable construction is specifically designed to tolerate the rigors of cooking with metal tools.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_555", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I need a big pan for family dinners, and it has to handle oven temps over 400F. Which of your pans is the largest and can withstand the heat?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_556", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I ain't paying more than 10 dollars and I want it either black or copper. Find me a pan like that.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"copper\") AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"copper\") AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND (color = 'black' OR color = 'copper');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_715", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is this pan suitable for broiling?", "long_answer": "The pan is oven-safe up to 450 degrees Fahrenheit or 232 degrees Celsius, however, it is not designed to withstand the direct heat of the broiler.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_716", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it safe to cook on high heat with this non-stick pan?", "long_answer": "It is not advisable to use high heat with this non-stick pan as such temperatures can damage its surface, leading to impaired performance over time. To preserve the integrity of the pan's non-stick quality, cooking should be done at low to medium heat.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_717", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the saucepan compatible with gas stovetops?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed to be used on multiple types of stovetops, with specific suitability for gas stovetops, accommodating even larger flame sizes without issue.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_557", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I've had enough of ZWILLING J.A. Henckels products, show me a blue pan from a different brand.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND color = \"blue\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND color = \"blue\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' AND color = 'blue';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_558", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm a big fan of Utopia Kitchen. Can you tell me which is the cheapest pan they've got in your inventory?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch` with asin: B00X4WQMAS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Utopia Kitchen' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_718", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it necessary to use non-metallic utensils with the Copper Chef pan to maintain the non-stick surface?", "long_answer": "To maintain the non-stick surface of the Copper Chef pan, it is recommended, though not required, to use utensils made of non-metallic materials like wood, plastic, silicone, or bamboo. These materials are less likely to damage the surface compared to metallic utensils.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_559", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm not looking to spend more than 20 dollars, but I want a good-quality pan that can handle high temperatures. Point me to your top performer.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_719", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is it safe to submerge the wok in water for cleaning purposes after removing the heat control?", "long_answer": "The wok is designed to be fully immersible and safe for cleaning in water once the heat control is detached, enhancing its convenience and ease of maintenance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_720", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the surface of the Norpro broiler set non-stick?", "long_answer": "The Norpro broiler pan is constructed from stainless steel and lacks a non-stick coating. Despite this, customers have indicated that the cleaning process is relatively easy, especially when utilizing a nylon sponge or after the pan has been soaked.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_207", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm in search of cookware that can assist me in cooking faster. Do pans featuring glass lids contribute to a quicker cooking time?", "long_answer": "Pans equipped with tempered glass lids provide the advantage of allowing you to monitor your food during cooking, but they may not be optimal for speedier meal preparation. The potentially inferior heat retention of glass lids might lead to slightly prolonged cooking durations when compared to pans with solid, heavier lids that are more proficient at preserving heat.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids are not recommended for users looking for the most energy-efficient cookware, as they might not insulate heat as well as some heavier, more solid lid options, potentially leading to slightly increased energy use over time.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_721", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is Cuisinart known for its reliability in cookware products and customer service?", "long_answer": "Cuisinart has established a reputation as a reliable brand in the realm of cookware, with customer feedback frequently highlighting satisfaction with both their product quality and the customer service provided.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_722", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Will the appearance of the nonstick pan change with prolonged use?", "long_answer": "With prolonged use, there can be some changes in color and appearance of the nonstick coating of the pan, which are considered normal and do not impact the pan's functionality.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_723", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan dishwasher safe?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti 12-inch saute pan is indeed dishwasher safe, but it is recommended to hand wash the pan using non-abrasive cleansers and liquid dishwashing soap to extend the durability of the non-stick coating.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_208", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is this pan compatible with my induction stove for effective cooking?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the pan will function effectively on an induction stove provided it is constructed from a magnetic material. Its round design enhances its compatibility with various types of stovetops, encompassing those with induction technology.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_560", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm looking for a grey pan that can withstand high temperatures, something above 600F. What's the best option you have for me?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"grey\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'grey' AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_561", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm looking for a Presto pan that can stand some serious heat, something above your average oven-safe temperature, but I ain't too flush right now. Hook me up with the most affordable one you've got.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND brand = \"Presto\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND brand = \"Presto\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND brand = \"Presto\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Presto' AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_209", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Can this pan achieve uniform browning of meat?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the pan is specifically crafted with a broad, flat base and perpendicular walls, which makes it perfect for uniformly browning and searing meats. This contributes to a uniform cooking outcome, indicative of a top-notch sauté pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a wide flat bottom and straight sides typically mean they facilitate easy flipping and tossing of ingredients during sautéing, making them ideal for this cooking technique as well as browning and searing meats evenly.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saute pan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_562", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Listen, I'm a brand-specific guy, I only use T-fal and Copper Chef for my kitchenware. Show me the largest pan you got from these brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Copper Chef\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Copper Chef\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Copper Chef\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('T-fal', 'Copper Chef') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_563", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm on the hunt for a copper pan, nothing too fancy. Could you direct me to the cheapest one you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_564", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm looking for a pretty big pan and it has to be Chicago Metallic. Do you have any pans that are at least 10 inches?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Chicago Metallic' AND size >= 10;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_724", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it recommended to cook with virgin olive oil in this non-stick pan without causing sticking or damage to the coating?", "long_answer": "It is suggested to use refined oils with a higher smoke point when cooking in the pan to avoid sticking and potential damage to the non-stick coating. Virgin olive oil, which has a lower smoke point, may not be the ideal option as it could lead to sticking and even harm the pan's surface if used on high heat settings.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_565", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm looking for a big pan, needs to be over 12 inches, and I prefer either USA Pan or Tramontina brand. Got anything like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Tramontina\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Tramontina\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND (brand = 'USA Pan' OR brand = 'Tramontina');"}}
{"id": "search_qa_566", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm needing a new pan that can resist over 500 degrees F in the oven, but I'm kind of tight on money so it needs to cost less than 30 bucks. What's the largest pan you got that meets these requirements?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND price < 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND price < 30 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND price < 30 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND price < 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_725", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with these non-stick ceramic-coated pans?", "long_answer": "Using metal utensils with these non-stick ceramic-coated pans is not advisable because it could result in damage to the coating. To ensure the longevity of the pans, it is better to opt for utensils made from materials such as wood, plastic, silicone, or nylon.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_726", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is the pan safe to use in an oven, and if so, up to what maximum temperature?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be oven safe and can withstand temperatures up to 500 degrees Fahrenheit, allowing for its use in a range of cooking techniques that require oven baking or roasting.", "short_answer": "yes, 500°F", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_727", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the saucepan come with a lid that seals in moisture and nutrients effectively?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is equipped with a Flavor Lock Lid that is designed to fit tightly, thereby sealing in moisture and nutrients to produce healthier and more flavorful food.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_567", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm looking for a new pan, I'm really into blue and silver ones. Can you help me out and find the first one in this color scheme?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"silver\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"silver\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('blue', 'silver') ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_568", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm only interested in Norpro and All-Clad brands. Point me to the first pan you've got from either of them.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black` with asin: B0170TFNXM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"All-Clad\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"All-Clad\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Norpro', 'All-Clad') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_728", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the pan's handle designed to stay cool during cooking?", "long_answer": "The pan's handle is specifically designed to be heat resistant, allowing it to remain cool and comfortable to the touch throughout the cooking process, according to reports from the majority of users.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_569", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I ain't looking to blow more than 10 dollars and I want it to be either grey or green. Help me find a pan that meets my requirements.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"green\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"green\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND (color = 'grey' OR color = 'green');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_729", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is it safe to cook acidic foods in this non-stick pan without damaging the surface?", "long_answer": "Cooking acidic foods in this non-stick pan is generally safe as the surface is designed to be durable. Nonetheless, to maintain the integrity of the non-stick coating, it is recommended to avoid prolonged exposure to highly acidic ingredients.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_570", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm putting together a dinner party and need a big pan that can take the heat in the oven. Show me your largest pan that can endure over 500F.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_571", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm a busy cook and need a pretty large pan that can withstand high oven temps over 500F. Hand me the details of the biggest one you have that can take the heat.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_572", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I've been cooking a lot these days and am looking for a big time pan in either grey or black that can handle the highest oven temperature. Show me what you got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'black') \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC, size DESC\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_730", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Does cooking acidic foods in a stainless steel pan alter their taste?", "long_answer": "Stainless steel is widely recognized for its non-reactive properties, making it an excellent material for cookware. When acidic foods such as tomatoes are cooked in a stainless steel pan, the flavor is typically unaffected because the material does not interact with the food's acidity.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_731", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with the Presto 5900 Electric Wok?", "long_answer": "While the Presto 5900 Electric Wok is constructed from stainless steel, it is advisable to utilize wooden or silicone utensils instead of metal ones to protect the wok's cooking surface from scratches and preserve its integrity.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_573", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Look, I only got 50 bucks to spare and I'm only interested in Tramontina brand. Can you find me a pan within that limit?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch` with asin: B009HBKQR0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND brand = \"Tramontina\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND brand = \"Tramontina\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Tramontina' AND price <= 50;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_574", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I have this weird thing for green pans and it has to be at least 10 inches. Hook me up with one, would you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" AND size >= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" AND size >= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'green' AND size >= 10 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_732", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "What is the capacity of the Cuisinart Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan has a capacity of 1 1/2 quarts, making it appropriate for boiling eggs as well as preparing small to medium-sized dishes.", "short_answer": "1 1/2 quarts", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_575", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm in the mood for something classic – either copper or black. Find me the least expensive pan in those colors would ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"black\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"black\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"black\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('copper', 'black') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_733", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils on this frying pan without causing damage?", "long_answer": "The frying pan is made to be durable; however, the use of metal utensils is not recommended as it can scratch the seasoning of the pan. To preserve the integrity of the non-stick surface, it is advised to use utensils made from materials such as wood or silicone.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_734", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is seasoning necessary for a new stainless steel non-stick pan?", "long_answer": "Seasoning stainless steel pans with a non-stick surface is generally not necessary. However, some users may choose to season their pan to guarantee the best possible non-stick performance, though it remains a matter of personal preference.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_576", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Listen, I need a pan that's at least 10 inches, but I ain't looking to drop more than 20 dollars. Can you find me the cheapest one that fits the bill?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND size >= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND size >= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND price <= 20 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_577", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I don't have time to scroll through all your products. Just give me one pan from either the Lodge or All-Clad brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"All-Clad\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"All-Clad\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Lodge', 'All-Clad') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_578", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm not a big fan of flashy colors. Got any black pans in stock? Show me the first one you find.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"black\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'black' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_735", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the broiler pan suitable for cooking various types of meats such as steak or chicken?", "long_answer": "The broiler pan is specifically designed to be suitable for a variety of meats, which includes rib and loin cuts of meat as well as boneless chicken. It can also be used for other foods like fish, shellfish, vegetables, and breads, providing optimal results for individual or two-person servings.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_579", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I need a new pan, but I ain't splashing out more than 30 dollars, and it better be black or silver. So, what's the best deal you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND color IN (\"silver\", \"black\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND (color = 'black' OR color = 'silver') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_736", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the product manufactured by a reputable and recognized brand?", "long_answer": "The product is manufactured by Norpro, a brand that has a reputation for quality products, as indicated by customer reviews. Moreover, the manufacturing takes place in Taiwan, which is often associated with the production of various reputable electronics and consumer goods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_737", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the exterior of the pan likely to stain or discolor after prolonged use?", "long_answer": "The exterior of the pan is susceptible to discoloration, especially when exposed to high heat over a period, despite the interior being resistant to scratching and sticking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_210", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I seek cookware that can hasten my cooking time. Do pans equipped with glass lids contribute to a faster cooking process?", "long_answer": "Pans fitted with tempered glass lids provide the advantage of allowing you to monitor your food while it cooks; however, they may not be the best choice for speedy cooking. The potentially less efficient heat retention of these lids could lead to a slight increase in cooking duration when compared to pans that have solid, heavier lids that are more effective at heat conservation.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids are not recommended for users looking for the most energy-efficient cookware, as they might not insulate heat as well as some heavier, more solid lid options, potentially leading to slightly increased energy use over time.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_738", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Does the weight and build quality of this pan resemble that of commercial bakeware?", "long_answer": "Customers confirm that the pan is indeed heavy and possesses a thickness that mirrors the high-quality and robust construction typical of commercial bakeware, indicating its substantial build.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_580", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I need a decently big pan that won't crap out in the oven above 400 degrees. Point me to your best option that's at least 8 inches.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_739", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "What is the length of the power cord provided with this wok, and is an extension cord required for optimal use?", "long_answer": "Reviewers have suggested that the power cord of the wok is relatively short, which might necessitate positioning the wok close to an electrical outlet or using an extension cord to enhance flexibility and ease of use in the kitchen.", "short_answer": "short, yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_581", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I've had it up to here with Presto brand, show me the cheapest pan you have that's not made by them.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price = (SELECT price FROM all_pans WHERE brand != 'Presto' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1);"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_740", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the Presto 5900 Electric Wok appropriate for use in a professional kitchen environment?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 Electric Wok is mainly designed for domestic cooking. While its primary intention is not for professional kitchens, there are instances where customers have successfully used it in semi-professional contexts such as classrooms and catering, but its suitability for a full-scale professional kitchen has not been explicitly established.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_741", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Does the nonstick surface of this cookware scratch easily?", "long_answer": "The nonstick surface can incur light scratches if not handled with care. Using suitable utensils and cleaning practices is recommended to maintain the integrity of the nonstick coating.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_211", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I need a pan that's suitable for sautéing pasta with vegetables on high heat. Would this be the right option?", "long_answer": "For sautéing pasta with vegetables over high heat, a round pan would be more suitable. The curved edges of a round pan facilitate the swift and effective stirring and flipping of ingredients, which is essential for this cooking method.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with rectangular shapes cannot be used for high-heat cooking methods such as stir-frying or sautéing typically performed in round pans where ingredients are tossed and moved around frequently.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "rectangular", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_582", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I can't shell out more than 20 dollars and I need a pan that can take the heat, at least 500 degrees F. What's the best option you guys have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_742", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is there a tendency for madeleines to brown excessively fast when baked in this pan?", "long_answer": "While there have been reports by some users experiencing quick browning of madeleines in this pan, this is generally manageable given that madeleines have inherently short baking times. Monitoring the baking process closely should help achieve the preferred level of browning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_212", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Will this pan allow me to achieve neat and uniform servings when I bake for my guests?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the pan's square design is perfect for baking treats like brownies or bars that benefit from uniform and tidy portions, guaranteeing that each serving looks as impeccable as the one before it.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with square shapes typically mean they are preferred for baking desserts like brownies and bars due to the desirable clean edges and uniformity.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "square", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_743", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Can the Matfer Bourgeat Black Steel Round Frying Pan be used on any cooktop?", "long_answer": "The Matfer Bourgeat Black Steel Round Frying Pan is crafted to be compatible with all types of cooktops, allowing for its use across various heating sources and enhancing its utility in different cooking scenarios.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_744", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the pan possess a heavy and durable construction or is it lightweight?", "long_answer": "The consensus among customers is that the pan is characterized by a substantial, heavy feel, indicative of its durable build quality, as opposed to being lightweight.", "short_answer": "heavy and durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_583", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I don't want any of that Cuisinart stuff. Show me the pan that can take the highest oven temperature you've got from a different brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Cuisinart\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Cuisinart\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Cuisinart\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Cuisinart' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_745", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan is designed to be induction ready, thus making it suitable for use on induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_746", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Can this pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be dishwasher safe. Despite this, to maintain the quality of the pan's non-stick coating, it is advised to wash it by hand using gentle, non-abrasive cleaning products.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_747", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is the pan's handle oven-safe and what precautions should be taken when using it?", "long_answer": "The pan's handle is designed to be oven-safe, offering a secure grip. However, it heats up in the oven and thus requires the use of oven mitts when being handled. Note that while the handle is oven-safe, the tempered glass lid that comes with the pan can withstand temperatures only up to 500°F.", "short_answer": "yes, need mitts", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_584", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm a bit of a perfectinoist in the kitchen and need a pan that can take the heat and is also big enough. Which of your pans can withstand at least 400F and is at least 12 inches? Give me the first one that comes up.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND size >= 12 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND size >= 12 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND size >= 12 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_748", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Does the weight of this cast iron skillet require two-handed handling?", "long_answer": "Indeed, due to the nature of cast iron cookware, this skillet tends to be heavier, necessitating the use of both hands for safe and secure handling, especially when moving or carrying it to ensure even heat distribution and longevity.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_213", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "With limited cupboard space, is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?", "long_answer": "Since round pans are not the most space-efficient for storage in compact kitchens, this may be a disadvantage if optimizing every inch is essential to you. Square or angular pans could be more suitable if you need to fit them into a tight cupboard or shelf.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_585", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I've got a family to feed, so I need something sized 8 inches or more. Give me the cheapest pan you got that fits that.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_586", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Look, I need a green pan and I'm not looking to spend more than 10 bucks. Point me to the cheapest one you got.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" AND price <= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" AND price <= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'green' AND price <= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_587", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I'm looking for a pan, either blue or silver. Don't care which, but it needs to be the cheapest one you got. Can you find that for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"silver\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"silver\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"silver\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('blue', 'silver') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_588", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm only interested in Cuisinart stuff. Now get me the cheapest Cuisinart pan you have in the store.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Cuisinart\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Cuisinart\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Cuisinart\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Cuisinart' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_589", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Look, I'm trying to get a pan for less than 20 bucks and it needs to withstand over 500F. Get me the largest one you have that meets my requirements.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_749", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "What is the recommended amount of batter to fill a Madeleine cup to achieve the traditional shape without overflowing?", "long_answer": "Each Madeleine cup should be filled with batter up to the rim, which is the ideal amount to allow the Madeleines to rise properly and achieve their characteristic shape without causing the batter to overflow during baking.", "short_answer": "fill to rim", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_750", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Can the red silicone sleeve on the handle be removed?", "long_answer": "The red silicone sleeve on the handle is designed to be removable, allowing for flexibility in use and ease of maneuverability.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_751", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is the pan equipped with handles to facilitate its removal from the oven?", "long_answer": "The pan lacks handles, which has been noted by some customers as a drawback for oven use convenience. Handling the pan requires caution, and the use of oven mitts is recommended.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_590", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I can't stand the color copper and I need a pan that can take the heat. Show me your biggest pan that can handle at least 450F. Just make sure it's not copper.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND color <> 'copper' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_752", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Does the saucepan come equipped with features that facilitate cooking pasta?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed with a straining lid, which provides added convenience for tasks like cooking pasta by simplifying the process of draining water.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_753", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the All-Clad frying pan dishwasher-safe?", "long_answer": "The All-Clad frying pan is safe to be washed in a dishwasher for ease of cleaning, although to maintain its visual appeal and extend its lifespan, hand washing is the preferred method of cleaning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_754", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is the surface of the pan completely smooth or textured?", "long_answer": "The pan's surface is slightly textured because of the pre-seasoning process it undergoes. However, if a smooth surface is desired, additional seasoning can be applied by the user or a different variant of the pan without pre-seasoning can be chosen.", "short_answer": "textured", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_214", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Can this pan safely withstand high heat when searing meats?", "long_answer": "This pan is unsuitable for cooking techniques that require extremely high temperatures, such as searing meats, since the sensitive non-stick surface may get damaged. For high-temperature culinary applications, opting for a non-coated pan, such as one made of cast iron or stainless steel, would be advisable.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with delicate non-stick coatings cannot be used for cooking methods that involve metal utensils or very high heat, to avoid damaging the surface.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_591", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that can withstand my oven's crazy heat and must be either green or blue. Can you find one that fits my crazy kitchen?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"blue\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('green','blue') AND oven_safe_temperature > 500;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_215", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Do I need to carry out any specific cleaning or maintenance procedures for these pans?", "long_answer": "Indeed, given that these pans aren't dishwasher safe, regular seasoning will be necessary for cast iron or carbon steel varieties, as well as polishing to preserve both their aesthetic and functional qualities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" do not have a function of self-maintenance and will need regular seasoning (for cast iron or carbon steel) or polishing (for aesthetic reasons) to maintain their best condition.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_755", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is the Lodge Cast Iron Skillet designed for both stove top and oven use?", "long_answer": "The Lodge Cast Iron Skillet is explicitly designed to be oven-safe, allowing it to be used for recipes that start on the stove top and need to be finished in the oven, ensuring versatility in cooking methods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_756", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "What is the maximum temperature recommended for using this pan in the oven?", "long_answer": "This pan is safe for oven use and can withstand temperatures up to 500°F without compromising its integrity or performance.", "short_answer": "500°F", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_757", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the wok and its lid dishwasher-safe?", "long_answer": "The wok along with its lid is designed to be dishwasher-safe, providing users with the convenience of easy cleaning by utilizing a dishwasher without damaging the product.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_592", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm in need of a cheap pan, no more than 20 bucks, and it's gotta be green or silver. And one more thing, it must handle heat very well. What's the best you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND color IN (\"green\", \"silver\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND color IN (\"green\", \"silver\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND color IN (\"green\", \"silver\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND (color = 'green' OR color = 'silver') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_593", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm looking for a good sized pan, definitely not silver and I can only splash out 50 dollars max. Which is the biggest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND NOT color = \"silver\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND NOT color = \"silver\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND NOT color = \"silver\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND color <> 'silver' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_594", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I can't stand green, and I need a big pan, definitely bigger than 12 inches. Get me your least expensive non-green pan pronto.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND size > 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND size > 12 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"green\" AND size > 12 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'green' AND size > 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_758", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Can the T-fal E93897 fry pan be used on an induction cooktop?", "long_answer": "The T-fal E93897 fry pan is designed to be compatible with various cooking methods, and it is specifically safe to use on induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_759", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "How many Madeleines can be made simultaneously with this pan?", "long_answer": "This pan is designed with 12 shell-shaped cups, allowing the simultaneous preparation of 12 Madeleines in a single batch.", "short_answer": "12", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_595", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I can't stand blue pans, they just clash with my kitchen. Also, I got only 30 dollars to spare. Show me your largest non-blue pan that I can afford.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" AND price < 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" AND price < 30 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" AND price < 30 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'blue' \nAND price <= 30 \nORDER BY size DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_760", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is the pan made from carbon steel both lightweight and long-lasting?", "long_answer": "The pan is constructed from carbon steel, which is known for excellent heat conduction. Its design strikes a balance between being lightweight, facilitating easy handling, and durable, ensuring it lasts a long time with proper care.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_596", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I don't want any pans from Tramontina. So what's the product that can withstand the highest oven temperature from the other brands?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Tramontina\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Tramontina' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_761", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Can the pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher without damaging its non-stick coating?", "long_answer": "While the pan can technically be cleaned in a dishwasher, it is recommended to hand wash the pan in order to maintain the integrity of the non-stick coating and extend the lifespan of the pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_762", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Does the ZWILLING Spirit 8\" Thermolon Fry Pan require a lot of oil for cooking?", "long_answer": "The ZWILLING Spirit 8\" Thermolon Fry Pan is equipped with a nonstick ceramic coating, which enables cooking with a minimal amount of oil while preventing food from sticking to the surface of the pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_763", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does the pan come with a feature that allows visual monitoring of the food without removing the lid?", "long_answer": "Yes, the pan is equipped with a glass lid designed to enable you to observe the cooking process without the need to lift the lid, thus maintaining the cooking environment.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_597", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm only interested in black or green pans. Get me the cheapest one you have in those colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('black', 'green') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_764", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the broiler pan resistant to warping at high temperatures?", "long_answer": "The broiler pan is generally resistant to warping when exposed to high temperatures, based on the fact that most users have not experienced issues with warping during use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_216", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Will this pan ensure that my food cooks evenly on all types of stoves?", "long_answer": "Our frying pans and skillets are crafted from aluminum or copper, renowned for their superior heat conduction, ensuring uniform cooking. Be aware, though, when using an induction cooktop, these materials are not naturally compatible because they lack magnetic properties. This could affect cooking efficiency unless a ferrous plate is used to enable induction.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_765", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is the pan compatible with various types of stovetops, including gas, electric, ceramic, and induction?", "long_answer": "The pan is crafted with a design that ensures compatibility with a range of cooking surfaces, such as gas, electric, ceramic, and induction stovetops. It is important, however, for users to adhere to the manufacturer's instructions to achieve optimal performance and to maintain the pan's integrity.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_766", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the saucepan's handle remain cool to the touch when cooking on the stovetop?", "long_answer": "The saucepan includes a Cool Grip Handle crafted from solid stainless steel, which is designed to stay cool on the stovetop, therefore ensuring safety and comfort during cooking activities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_767", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the fry pan's handle remain cool to the touch while cooking?", "long_answer": "The fry pan features riveted silicone handles specifically engineered to stay cool to the touch, thereby providing a secure and comfortable grip even when the pan is heated.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_598", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Listen up, I need a pan that's no smaller than your average size and can handle at least 450 degrees. Don't try to upsell me either, just give me your cheapest option that checks both boxes.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_599", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm looking for a green pan that can handle high heat. What's the highest oven-safe temperature for this kind of pan?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'green' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_217", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Can I safely put this pan in the dishwasher, or is it better to wash it by hand to avoid wear and tear?", "long_answer": "This pan is entirely safe for dishwasher use. It is designed to withstand both the high temperatures and the strong cleaning agents found in dishwashers. As a result, it will neither warp, corrode, nor deteriorate rapidly, ensuring long-lasting durability and convenient cleaning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute feature resistance to both the high temperatures and strong chemicals typical in dishwashers, which ensures they do not warp, rust, or degrade quickly when exposed to such conditions regularly.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_600", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm not looking to drop more than a tenner on a pan. Hit me with the cheapest option you've got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_768", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Can using sharp utensils damage the non-stick coating on this pan?", "long_answer": "Using sharp-edged utensils and knives is discouraged when cooking with this pan, as they can damage the non-stick surface, leading to its deterioration and potential loss of non-stick properties over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_769", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the non-stick interior of the pot durable enough to withstand regular usage?", "long_answer": "The non-stick interior of the pot is designed to be durable and customer feedback suggests that it withstands regular use effectively. To ensure the longevity of the non-stick surface, it is advised to adhere to the provided care instructions, which include using low to medium heat and opting for hand-washing over machine washing whenever feasible.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_601", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I'm looking for a pan but I only got 50 bucks to spare and I really can't stand copper colored ones. Get me the cheapest option that's not copper.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND NOT color = \"copper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND NOT color = \"copper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND color != 'copper' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_770", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is the Stone Earth Pan by Ozeri dishwasher safe for cleaning?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Pan by Ozeri should be hand washed for optimal care and to ensure its longevity, as opposed to cleaning it in a dishwasher.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_602", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I've heard good things about Anolon. Do you have any pans from that brand in stock? Show me one.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray` with asin: B000069RBK", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Anolon\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Anolon\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Anolon' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_771", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does the Bialetti 6168 Fry Pan have a heat-resistant handle?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti 6168 Fry Pan is equipped with an extra-long soft-touch handle designed to resist heat, ensuring comfortable handling during cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_772", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Is the nonstick coating on this cookware intended to resist scratches?", "long_answer": "The nonstick coating applied to the cookware is manufactured to have scratch-resistant properties. However, to preserve the integrity and longevity of the surface, it is advisable to use non-metal utensils and exercise proper care during cleaning and usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_603", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm a big fan of Copper Chef. Can you give me the product id for one of their pans?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Copper Chef\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Copper Chef\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Copper Chef' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_604", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I can't splurge more than 20 dollars and absolutely don't want anything from Ozeri. Can you find the pan with the highest oven-safe temperature in that price range?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND brand != 'Ozeri' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_773", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "What is the maximum temperature to which this saucepan is oven safe?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is capable of withstanding temperatures up to 350 degrees Fahrenheit when used in an oven, which provides flexibility in cooking techniques. However, caution should be exercised by using oven mitts to handle the pan since the handles may become heated.", "short_answer": "350 degrees Fahrenheit", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_605", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I am looking for a pan that can tolerate high heat in the oven, say above 500 degrees. Also, it has to be either green or black. What's the cheapest one you've got that matches these preferences?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND color IN (\"green\", \"black\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND color IN (\"green\", \"black\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND color IN (\"green\", \"black\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('black', 'green') AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_774", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "What is the color of the pan's surface, and can it influence baking outcomes?", "long_answer": "The pan is made from durable carbon steel with a non-stick coating. While the precise color is not explicitly stated, consensus from user feedback implies it has a darker shade. Dark-colored pans are known to potentially alter baking times and the level of browning due to their heat absorption properties.", "short_answer": "dark, yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_775", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Does the pan come with a recipe booklet or any included recipes?", "long_answer": "The available product information does not explicitly mention the inclusion of recipes with the pan. Customer feedback additionally does not indicate that any recipes are provided; instead, it appears that customers commonly utilize their own recipes or seek them out on the internet.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_776", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Do the shell-shaped cups of the Madeleine pan create well-defined Madeleine shapes?", "long_answer": "Customers often report that the shell-shaped cups provide a clearly defined shape, allowing for Madeleines to come out with an appealing and beautiful shell-like pattern.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_777", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Does the pan have sharp edges that could be considered a safety concern when handling?", "long_answer": "The pan is constructed with edges that are not rounded, coupled with a thin material, leading to the presence of sharp edges that could pose a safety concern during handling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_606", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I do a lot of high-heat cooking and need a large pan that can take the heat. Can you find me your largest pan safe for use over 500F?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size >= 12 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size >= 12 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_607", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I always cook big meals and Chicago Metallic is my brand, so can you tell me the largest pan they have in stock?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Chicago Metallic' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_608", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm not messing around, I need a big pan that can handle some serious heat... like 500 degrees serious. Show me the biggest one you got that can take the heat.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size >= 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size >= 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_609", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I got a thing for blue and green pans, but they need to withstand high heat. Show me the one with the highest oven-safe temperature you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"green\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"green\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"green\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('blue', 'green') \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_778", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the pan designed to prevent food from sticking during cooking?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed with a stick-resistant polished cooking surface, but optimal results in preventing food from sticking are achieved when the pan is properly preheated and fats or oils are used as required, in accordance with customer feedback.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_218", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Can this pan safely be used to sear meats on high heat?", "long_answer": "No, this pan is unsuitable for cooking techniques that require extremely high temperatures, such as searing meats, as the non-stick coating is sensitive and might be impaired. For cooking at high heat, it is advisable to opt for a pan devoid of non-stick surfaces, such as one made of cast iron or stainless steel.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with delicate non-stick coatings cannot be used for cooking methods that involve metal utensils or very high heat, to avoid damaging the surface.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_610", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I need a sizable pan, at least 10 inches, and I ain't paying more than 30 bucks for it. Get me the best deal you can find!", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND price <= 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND price <= 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND price <= 30 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_611", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I don't care for Chicago Metallic, and I want a green pan. Can you show me an option like that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" AND NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" AND NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'green' AND brand NOT LIKE 'Chicago Metallic';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_779", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is a lid included with the purchase of the Spirit Fry Pan?", "long_answer": "Upon review, the Spirit Fry Pan does not come with a lid as part of its standard package contents.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_219", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is this pan compatible with my new induction stove?", "long_answer": "If the pan you're interested in is constructed from copper, it will function on your induction cooktop only if it is equipped with a specifically designed base that is compatible with induction. Copper, being a non-magnetic material, is not intrinsically apt for induction cooking unless it possesses this adaptation.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with copper material cannot be used for induction cooking unless they are specially designed with an induction-compatible base, as copper itself is not magnetic.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "copper", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_780", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Are the liquid measure lines marked inside the cooking pot accurate?", "long_answer": "The cooking pot includes liquid measure lines that are designed to be accurate, providing a convenient way to measure liquids without the need for additional measuring cups or tools.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_781", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "How durable is the three-layer PFOA-free nonstick coating for cooking and cleaning?", "long_answer": "The three-layer PFOA-free nonstick coating is designed to be durable, offering effortless food release and easy cleanup, as confirmed by the majority of users who report that the coating is tough and long-lasting.", "short_answer": "durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_612", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm looking for a pan and green is my absolute favorite color. Can you find a green one for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"green\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'green';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_220", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I prefer to crisp my meat by using dry heat. Is this pan suitable for that purpose?", "long_answer": "Certainly, this pan isn't the ideal option for crisping meat using dry heat. Its tempered glass lid traps moisture, which is something you'd want to prevent in order to obtain the correct texture when crisping meat.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids are not suitable for recipes requiring “dry cooking” methods such as roasting or baking without moisture, as the lids are designed to retain moisture within the pan.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_782", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Does this fry pan provide even heat distribution during cooking?", "long_answer": "The majority of customer feedback suggests that the fry pan distributes heat evenly, ensuring that food is cooked uniformly without the presence of hot spots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_221", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I frequently have difficulty with pans that fail to heat evenly on my stove. Does this design assist in achieving uniform heating?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the pan's round shape helps to distribute heat more evenly across its surface, enhancing both compatibility and heating efficiency on all types of stovetops, ranging from classic to contemporary induction units, provided it is made from suitable magnetic material.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_222", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Can this cookware distribute heat evenly across all varieties of stovetops?", "long_answer": "Typically, ceramic pans are suitable for use on different types of stovetops; however, to achieve uniform heating on induction cooktops, the pan must have a magnetic base or a layer that is compatible with induction to guarantee efficient performance.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with ceramic material do not have a function of working on induction cooktops unless designed with a magnetic base or special induction-compatible layer.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "ceramic", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_613", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm only interested in Lodge or Tramontina brands and I'm a sucker for copper pans. Can you find me the cheapest one from those brands?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"Tramontina\") AND color = \"copper\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"Tramontina\") AND color = \"copper\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"Tramontina\") AND color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Lodge', 'Tramontina') AND color = 'copper' ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_614", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm trying to find a large-sized copper colored pan that's over 12 inches. Can you help me find one?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND color = \"copper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND color = \"copper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND color = 'copper';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_783", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is the weight of these pans comparable to that of traditional cast iron cookware?", "long_answer": "The pans are made from heavy-gauge die-cast aluminum, which gives them durability without being as heavy as traditional cast iron pans, resulting in a product that is easier to handle.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_615", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I'm cooking for a big family here and I need a large pan. Can you tell me the product id of the largest pan from Bialetti?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal` with asin: B000S6I4ZE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Bialetti\" AND size > 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Bialetti\" AND size > 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size = (SELECT size FROM all_pans WHERE brand = 'Bialetti' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1) AND brand = 'Bialetti';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_616", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I need a sturdy pan that can withstand high oven temperatures over 450F, but I'm just not into blue. Let me know the best one you got that meets this criteria.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND NOT color = \"blue\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND NOT color = \"blue\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND color != 'blue' ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_223", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Will I encounter any difficulty when preparing omelets or pancakes in this pan?", "long_answer": "Indeed, you may face some challenges since the pan's angular design disrupts the effortless swirling of the batter, which is crucial for these types of dishes. A pan with rounded edges would be more suitable for your specific culinary methods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with square shapes fail to meet the requirements for smooth swirling or whisking due to the angular nature, which can interrupt the fluid movement needed in some culinary techniques.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "square", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_784", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "What is the maximum temperature the pan can withstand in the oven?", "long_answer": "The pan can endure temperatures up to 400 degrees Fahrenheit while being oven-safe, thereby accommodating recipes that call for the transition from stovetop to oven without changing cookware.", "short_answer": "400 degrees Fahrenheit", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_785", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the saucepan's handle remain cool to the touch while cooking?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed with an ergonomically designed handle for comfort and safety, but like many cookware handles, it can become warm when cooking, and thus it is recommended to use pot holders to ensure safety.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_786", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Can the pans be safely used in an oven at high temperatures?", "long_answer": "The pans are capable of withstanding temperatures up to 500 degrees Fahrenheit when used in an oven. It is essential to use them without their accompanying lids, as the lids are not designed to be oven-safe.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_787", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is a recipe included in the packaging of the pan?", "long_answer": "The packaging of the pan itself typically does not contain a recipe; however, one can readily find recipes on the manufacturer's website or other culinary websites, such as the King Arthur Flour's site.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_617", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm looking for a heavy-duty pan that can handle more than 600 degrees in the oven. But only from USA Pan or Chicago Metallic. Got anything like that?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Chicago Metallic\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND brand IN (\"USA Pan\", \"Chicago Metallic\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('USA Pan', 'Chicago Metallic') \nAND oven_safe_temperature > 600;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_618", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I ain't passionate about black pans and need one that can handle over 600 degrees Fahrenheit. You got something different for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'black' AND oven_safe_temperature > 600;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_788", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is it safe to clean a cast iron skillet in the dishwasher?", "long_answer": "Cleaning a cast iron skillet in the dishwasher is discouraged because it can remove the protective seasoning layer and encourage rust formation. To preserve the skillet's condition, hand washing is the preferred method.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_789", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the 1 1/2 quart saucepan suitable for individuals or small households cooking for one or two people?", "long_answer": "The 1 1/2 quart saucepan is highly recommended for individuals or small households since customers report that its size is perfect for preparing small meals, making it an essential item in their kitchen.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_224", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is it safe to frequently wash this pan in the dishwasher without causing any harm?", "long_answer": "Certainly, you can wash this pan in your dishwasher with confidence. Our pans are crafted from robust materials such as stainless steel and aluminum, ensuring they can endure the intense conditions of a dishwasher without damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_790", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is the lid of the pan engineered to prevent spillage when using the pour spouts?", "long_answer": "The lid of the pan is designed specifically to fit securely, effectively preventing any spillage, and it comes equipped with straining holes that align with the pan's pour spouts for added convenience during pouring.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_791", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is the Lodge Cast Iron Skillet suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "long_answer": "The Lodge Cast Iron Skillet can indeed be used on induction cooktops. It is also versatile enough to be used with other heating sources such as electric and gas stoves, ovens, and even over campfires.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_225", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Could I encounter hot spots when I sauté vegetables in this pan?", "long_answer": "No, you should not encounter hot spots while sautéing vegetables. The round shape of the pan is designed to evenly distribute heat, which is essential for sautéing vegetables to perfection.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_792", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Will the pan show signs of discoloration after prolonged use?", "long_answer": "Over time and with use, there is a possibility for the pan to show signs of discoloration as reported by some users; however, this does not impact the pan's performance and it can be cleaned relatively easily.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_793", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is additional seasoning required for a pre-seasoned cast iron skillet?", "long_answer": "Although the cast iron skillet arrives pre-seasoned, it is recommended by the majority of users to season it further, particularly after initial uses, to enhance and maintain a non-stick cooking surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_794", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does the pan inherently have non-stick properties without seasoning?", "long_answer": "The pan itself does not have non-stick properties out of the box. It requires proper seasoning as per the manufacturer's instructions to achieve a nearly non-stick surface, and this process might demand some effort and repeated applications to obtain the best non-stick performance.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_619", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm partial to Lodge and USA Pan for cookware. Hook me up with the first pan you find from either of these brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"USA Pan\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Lodge\", \"USA Pan\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Lodge', 'USA Pan') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_795", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is a lid included with the ZWILLING Spirit 8\" Thermolon Fry Pan?", "long_answer": "The ZWILLING Spirit 8\" Thermolon Fry Pan is not sold with a lid; however, lids can be purchased separately if needed.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_796", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this stainless steel wok?", "long_answer": "While metal utensils can be used with the wok, it is generally advised to opt for wooden or silicone utensils instead to avoid scratching the stainless steel surface, thus preserving its integrity and non-stick properties.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_620", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm cooking big meals in this house and require larger size pans. What's the highest oven safe temperature of pans that are larger than average size?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_797", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does this pan function as a non-stick pan or more like a cast iron skillet?", "long_answer": "While the pan can potentially achieve a non-stick surface similar to Teflon pans after proper seasoning, it inherently behaves more like a cast iron skillet due to the necessity of seasoning, distinguishing it from the typical performance of stainless steel pans.", "short_answer": "cast iron skillet", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_621", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I tend to cook on high heat and I’m a fan of either Chicago Metallic or Ozeri. What's the first pan you can find from these brands which can tolerate a temperature above 450F?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND brand IN (\"Chicago Metallic\", \"Ozeri\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND brand IN (\"Chicago Metallic\", \"Ozeri\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (brand = 'Chicago Metallic' OR brand = 'Ozeri') AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_226", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is it alright if I use a steel wool scrubber to clean this pan and eliminate the stubborn food remains?", "long_answer": "It is advised not to use a steel wool scrubber on the pan. Since the pan is constructed of aluminum and may feature a non-stick coating or be anodized, abrasive scouring pads such as steel wool could harm the surface and impair its non-stick qualities.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's specific maintenance needs fail to meet the requirements for indiscriminate cleaning methods such as harsh scouring pads or certain dishwasher detergents, especially if they have a non-stick layer or are anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_798", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Can the saucepan be safely used in an oven for cooking?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is manufactured to withstand temperatures of up to 400 degrees Fahrenheit, which makes it suitable for oven use and compatible with recipes that necessitate finishing in the oven.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_799", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the Bialetti pan oven-safe?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti pan is specifically designed for stovetop use and not for the oven, featuring a handle that is heat-resistant but only suitable for conventional stovetops.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_800", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Can the pan's surface resist scratches when using metallic utensils?", "long_answer": "The pan is advertised as having a non-stick surface that should be maintained by using non-metallic utensils; however, some customers have reported scratching when using metal utensils, indicating that the surface may not be entirely scratch-proof against such materials.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_622", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I ain't looking to spend big bucks here. Dig me up the least expensive pan you have in your inventory.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_801", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it possible to initiate a warranty claim for my Copper Chef pan received as a gift without a receipt?", "long_answer": "In cases where the Copper Chef pan was received as a gift and you possess no receipt, initiating a warranty claim would require you to contact customer service. Provide them with a detailed explanation of the issue and, if possible, any proof of purchase or gift receipt.", "short_answer": "Contact customer service.", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_802", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Do the pans come with heat-resistant handles?", "long_answer": "Each pan comes equipped with a silicone-coated handle that is resistant to heat, which enhances safety and convenience while cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_623", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I frequently cook at high temperatures and like my pans big. What's your best pan that can handle over 400F and is larger than your average size?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_803", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Can metal utensils be safely used on this pan's nonstick cooking surface without causing damage?", "long_answer": "Using metal utensils on the nonstick cooking surface of this pan is not recommended because they can cause damage. To prevent damaging the surface, it is safe to use utensils made of nylon, silicone, or wood.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_804", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Will the T-fal pot sit completely flat on a glass stovetop?", "long_answer": "Due to the slightly raised T-fal emblem in the center of the pan bottom, the pot may not sit entirely flat on a glass stovetop, which in turn has the potential to impact the heating time as reported by some users.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_805", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are the pans resistant to staining over time?", "long_answer": "The majority of user experience indicates that the pans generally maintain their original appearance with proper care. However, there is a possibility of some staining over time, which greatly depends on usage and maintenance, particularly the promptness of cleaning after use.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_806", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the pan large enough to accommodate a 12 ounce steak?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be sufficiently sized to hold a 12 ounce steak, ensuring a good fit for cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_807", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is this wok suitable for deep-frying foods such as tempura?", "long_answer": "Yes, the wok is designed for various cooking methods, including deep-frying. It has been successfully used by many customers for deep-frying, although it should be noted that it does not include a dedicated tempura rack, so alternative draining methods such as paper towels will be necessary.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_808", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Does the Stone Earth Pan's non-stick coating contain any APEO, PFOA, NMP, or NEP chemicals?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Pan features a German-made stone-derived coating that is completely free of harmful chemicals such as APEO, PFOA, NMP, and NEP, offering a safe cooking experience without the risk of exposure to these perfluorinated chemicals.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_624", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I don't want anything from ZWILLING J.A. Henckels, but I need the biggest copper pan you got from any other brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND NOT brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' AND brand != 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_227", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is it possible to clean this pan with a steel wool scrubber to eliminate persistent food residue?", "long_answer": "It is advised against using a steel wool scrubber on this pan. As the pan is constructed from aluminum and might possess a non-stick coating or be anodized, abrasive scouring pads such as steel wool have the potential to harm the surface and diminish its non-stick qualities.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's specific maintenance needs fail to meet the requirements for indiscriminate cleaning methods such as harsh scouring pads or certain dishwasher detergents, especially if they have a non-stick layer or are anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_625", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm in the market for a green or grey pan, and size matters to me. What's the biggest one you sell in these colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"grey\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"grey\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"grey\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('green', 'grey') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_626", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm looking for a grey or black pan from either Matfer Bourgeat or Cuisinart that can handle the heat. Which one can withstand the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") AND brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"Cuisinart\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") AND brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"Cuisinart\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") AND brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"Cuisinart\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'black') \nAND brand IN ('Matfer Bourgeat', 'Cuisinart') \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_627", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm only interested in Tramontina and T-fal brands. Can you find me a pan from either of them?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"T-fal\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"T-fal\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Tramontina', 'T-fal') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_628", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I fancy ZWILLING J.A. Henckels stuff. Could you point me to a pan from this brand please?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_228", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I recently acquired a new cooktop and am keen to ensure that I purchase a pan that is compatible. Are there any specific features I should be on the lookout for?", "long_answer": "While in the market for a new pan, opt for one with a round shape since it offers superior compatibility with multiple cooktops, especially modern induction ones. Just verify that the pan is constructed from a magnetic material if you possess an induction cooktop, to guarantee optimal performance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_809", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the pan have a perfectly flat surface or are there any irregularities?", "long_answer": "Some customers have reported that the center of the pan is slightly elevated compared to the edges, which may influence how oil spreads across the surface; however, these observations are not consistent among all users.", "short_answer": "center slightly elevated", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_629", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I need a big pan, something bigger than 8 inches. But it has to be a Bialetti. Do you have anything that fits those specs?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal` with asin: B000S6I4ZE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND brand = \"Bialetti\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND brand = \"Bialetti\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Bialetti' AND size > 8;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_229", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is it okay if I clean this pan with a steel wool scrubber to eliminate stubborn food residue?", "long_answer": "It is advisable not to use a steel wool scrubber on this pan. Since it is constructed from aluminum and might possess a non-stick coating or be anodized, abrasive scouring materials such as steel wool have the potential to harm the surface and impair its non-stick qualities.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's specific maintenance needs fail to meet the requirements for indiscriminate cleaning methods such as harsh scouring pads or certain dishwasher detergents, especially if they have a non-stick layer or are anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_810", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is one pan sufficient for baking a standard Madeleine recipe?", "long_answer": "The necessity of purchasing extra pans for a standard Madeleine recipe depends on the size of the recipe. Often, recipes yield more than 12 Madeleines, thus prompting some customers to buy a second pan to accommodate the entire batch at once.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_811", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "What is the durability of the pot's material, and can it be expected to last with proper care?", "long_answer": "The pot is considered sturdy and well-made by numerous customers, suggesting that it is a durable option within its price range. Despite some customers feeling that the material is thin, with proper care and maintenance, the pot is expected to have good longevity and serve its purpose over time.", "short_answer": "very good, yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_230", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is this pan suitable for slow-cooking recipes if I use it a couple of times a week?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the pan is an outstanding selection for slow-cooking dishes. Owing to its material, which is not suited for dishwashers, it boasts exceptional heat retention capabilities, making it perfect for culinary techniques that demand steady, uniform heat for prolonged durations.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are ideally used for traditional or specialized cooking methods that take advantage of their unique material properties, such as the heat retention of cast iron.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_812", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is the Anolon saucepan compatible with induction stovetops?", "long_answer": "The Anolon saucepan is constructed from aluminum and lacks a magnetic base, rendering it incompatible with induction stovetops that require cookware to have magnetic properties for proper functionality.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_813", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the electric wok equipped with an adjustable temperature control feature?", "long_answer": "The electric wok is indeed outfitted with a feature that allows the temperature to be adjusted, granting you the flexibility to select the appropriate heat level for your cooking needs.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_814", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are Green Earth Pans suitable for a range of cooking methods such as frying, sautéing, baking, and boiling?", "long_answer": "Green Earth Pans are designed to handle various cooking methods, including frying, sautéing, baking, and boiling, making them a versatile addition to the kitchen that could potentially replace other non-stick pans used for these cooking techniques.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_231", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is the lid handle capable of withstanding high temperatures without emitting any toxic materials?", "long_answer": "This hinges on the specifics. If the pan features a tempered glass lid, and the handle’s coating degrades from exposure to high heat or other elements, it may cause undesirable substances to leach into your food, which would be less than optimal.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids fail to meet the requirements for completely non-reactive cooking conditions, especially if any sort of coating on the lid's handle or edges were to degrade and interact with the food.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_630", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "No Ozeri for me, thanks. And stick to blue or silver. What's the first pan you come across meeting these criteria?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"blue\") AND NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"blue\") AND NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Ozeri' AND (color = 'blue' OR color = 'silver') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_815", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the saucepan feature a design that facilitates drip-free pouring?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is indeed equipped with a drip-free pouring rim that is specifically tapered to enable clean and straightforward pouring, effectively minimizing the occurrence of spills and drips.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_816", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the lid of this cookware have a steam vent?", "long_answer": "The cookware's lid is equipped with a vent that enables steam to be released during the cooking process, which serves to avert overflowing and allows the cook to maintain clear visibility.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_232", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm in search of a pan that's user-friendly for my children during cooking – is this a suitable choice?", "long_answer": "Consider selecting a pan with a lighter lid, since the heavy stainless steel lid on this one might be less appropriate for young cooks due to its weight, potentially making it difficult for children to manage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a stainless steel lid are not recommended for lightweight applications where ease of handling is crucial, such as in settings that cater to individuals with limited strength or mobility as the moderate weight of the lids could pose a challenge.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "stainless steel lid", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_817", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the pot's handle designed to stay cool when cooking on the stovetop?", "long_answer": "The pot's handle is specifically designed to stay cool during cooking for safety and comfort, though it's advisable to use pot holders as a precautionary measure.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_631", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I need a big pan, but not from Ozeri. Show me the smallest product you got that's over 10 inches.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND NOT brand = \"Ozeri\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND brand != 'Ozeri' ORDER BY size ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_632", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm doing some heavy duty cooking and I need a pan that can withstand temperatures over 600F. What's the biggest one you have from either Tramontina or Lodge?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Lodge\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Lodge\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Lodge\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND (brand = 'Tramontina' OR brand = 'Lodge') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_633", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I've got a tight budget and for some reason, I just don't want a black one. Give me the largest non-black pan you have that's under 10 dollars.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND NOT color = \"black\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND NOT color = \"black\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND NOT color = \"black\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 10 AND color != 'black' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_634", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I usually cook at really high temperatures, like over 400F. What's the largest pan you guys have that can handle that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_818", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Does the crepe pan's handle remain cool and comfortable to hold while cooking?", "long_answer": "The crepe pan is equipped with a stay-cool stainless handle, which is specifically designed to remain cool and provide comfort as well as safety to the user during the cooking process.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_819", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Can this pan be safely cleaned in a dishwasher?", "long_answer": "This pan is not suitable for cleaning in a dishwasher. The recommended method for cleaning this kitchenware is by hand, using hot water and refraining from using soap to preserve its seasoning.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_635", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Not a fan of blue and I ain't dropping more than 50 bucks on this. What's the cheapest non-blue pan you can recommend?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" AND price < 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" AND price < 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'blue' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_820", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is this saucepan suitable for use on electric stovetops?", "long_answer": "Yes, this saucepan is specifically designed for compatibility with all types of stovetops, including electric ones. The aluminum base of the saucepan aids in evenly distributing heat, a crucial feature for cooking effectively on electric stovetops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_821", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does this pan have a naturally non-stick surface when properly seasoned and cared for?", "long_answer": "The pan, when properly seasoned and cared for, develops a non-stick surface gradually. This process may involve an initial learning period while the patina builds up on the surface.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_822", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Can these pans be safely washed in a dishwasher without damaging the non-stick coating?", "long_answer": "While these pans are constructed to be durable, washing them in a dishwasher may accelerate the wear and tear of the non-stick surface. To maintain the integrity of the coating and extend the lifespan of the pans, it is advised to wash them by hand.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_233", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for long-duration simmering of stews that include acidic ingredients such as wine or lemon juice?", "long_answer": "Given that sustained exposure to acidic agents like wine or lemon juice may damage the seasoning on a non-enameled cast iron lid, this pan is not ideal for extensive cooking of stews containing acidic elements. This practice might impair the seasoning, potentially compromising both the pan's functionality and the flavor of your dishes.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a cast iron lid are not suitable for acidic foods that can strip the seasoned coating unless the cast iron is enameled, as prolonged contact with acidic substances can lead to deterioration of the seasoning and the iron could react with the food, altering its taste.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "cast iron lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_823", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Can this pan be used for tasks other than broiling, such as roasting meats and vegetables?", "long_answer": "The pan is versatile and can be utilized for a variety of cooking methods including roasting meats, seafood, and vegetables, as affirmed by feedback from customers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_636", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm in need of a large pan, something that's at least 12 inches but I've had a bad experience with T-fal stuff. Also, it's gotta withstand high temperatures. Can you find the one that matches these requirements and can also withstand the highest temperature in the oven?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND NOT brand = \"T-fal\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND NOT brand = \"T-fal\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND NOT brand = \"T-fal\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND brand <> 'T-fal' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_234", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Can I safely place this pan in the dishwasher with my other dishes, or is it better to wash it by itself?", "long_answer": "Hand washing this pan is recommended, since some dishwasher detergents may be overly abrasive for aluminum pans, especially those with non-stick surfaces or anodized finishes, potentially impacting their durability and function.", "short_answer": "handwash", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's specific maintenance needs fail to meet the requirements for indiscriminate cleaning methods such as harsh scouring pads or certain dishwasher detergents, especially if they have a non-stick layer or are anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_824", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Does the lid provided with the skillet seal tightly to retain moisture and flavor?", "long_answer": "The lid accompanying the skillet is intended to provide a tight seal on the cookware to effectively retain moisture and preserve the flavor of dishes cooked within it.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_825", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does this pan tend to warp and develop a domed center according to customer reviews?", "long_answer": "According to customer reviews, there have been mentions of a domed center in the pan, which can be interpreted as warping, and may affect those needing a perfectly flat surface for cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_826", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is a warranty included with the purchase of the pot?", "long_answer": "The pot is accompanied by a Lifetime Limited Warranty as stated in the product's feature list.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_827", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Does the bread pan feature a non-stick coating that is free from PTFE, PFOA, and BPA?", "long_answer": "The bread pan uses Americoat for its non-stick surface, which is a silicone-based coating. Americoat is devoid of PTFE, PFOA, and BPA, thus ensuring that the coating is free from these potentially harmful chemicals.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_828", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the Prometal Pro nonstick coating on this pan resist scratches, and is it safe for use with metal utensils?", "long_answer": "The Prometal Pro nonstick interior of the pan is designed to be exceptionally durable and resists scratching, thus confirming its safe compatibility with metal utensils as stated in the product metadata.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_829", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Does the Lodge skillet come pre-seasoned?", "long_answer": "The Lodge skillet is pre-seasoned, ensuring a nonstick finish, yet it is recommended to spray or lightly coat it with vegetable oil prior to each use for optimal results.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_235", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is this pan suitable for cooking a creamy risotto that requires continuous stirring?", "long_answer": "No, this pan would not be suitable for recipes such as risotto that necessitate constant stirring. Its square shape could make stirring less effective compared to a rounded pan and might lead to food sticking in the corners.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with square shapes are not suitable for recipes requiring a continuous stirring motion, such as risottos or certain sauces, where a round bottom facilitates smoother movement and prevents sticking in corners.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "square", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_236", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Might the pan's shape render it challenging to stow in a drawer alongside other kitchen tools?", "long_answer": "The circular design of the pan may not fit neatly with the rectangular configuration of drawers, rendering it a less practical option for storage alongside different utensils. Opting for a pan design that matches the storage proportions of your drawers can assist in conserving space and maintaining organization.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_830", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is the skillet safe to use on a glass cooktop without causing scratches?", "long_answer": "The skillet is compatible with a glass cooktop; however, due to its heavy nature, caution is advised during use. To avoid scratching the cooktop surface, it's important to lift the skillet instead of sliding it.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_831", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is the Lodge skillet suitable for uses beyond frying, such as bread baking?", "long_answer": "The Lodge skillet is indeed a versatile piece of cookware designed to accommodate a variety of cooking methods, including deep frying, bread baking, and roasting, among others.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_832", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Does the domed glass lid of the cookware provide visibility for monitoring the cooking process?", "long_answer": "The domed glass lid of this cookware is designed to be transparent, enabling clear visibility while cooking. This feature allows you to watch your food as it cooks without needing to lift the lid, thereby retaining heat and moisture within the cookware.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_833", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Does the non-stick quality of this pan deteriorate with regular use over time?", "long_answer": "The pan's non-stick feature can decrease in efficiency after repeated use. To ensure the non-stick surface lasts as long as possible, it is important to follow the manufacturer's care instructions and use the pan as recommended.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_834", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is the nonstick coating of this fry pan free from PTFE and PFOA?", "long_answer": "The fry pan is designed with a nonstick ceramic coating that is completely free from both PTFE and PFOA, ensuring that it does not contain these chemicals.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_237", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is it safe to say that this pan can withstand frequent use for preparing various dishes without concerns over its durability?", "long_answer": "In most culinary situations, the pan should perform reliably. Nonetheless, should your cooking regularly involve acidic or alkaline components, you might have to opt for a treated or anodized pan to prevent metallic taste transfer and discoloration issues that could affect the pan's longevity due to consistent exposure to these substances.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with reactivity to acidic and alkaline foods feature a potential for metallic taste transfer and discoloration, rendering them less suitable for long-term cooking of tomato sauces or citrus-based dishes unless they're treated or anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_835", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Can the Matfer Bourgeat Black Steel Round Frying Pan be used on glass cooktops?", "long_answer": "The Matfer Bourgeat Black Steel Round Frying Pan is designed to work with all types of hobs, encompassing its compatibility with glass cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_637", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm looking for a Norpro pan, but it's got to be either in copper or black. Can you find me one?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"black\") AND brand = \"Norpro\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"black\") AND brand = \"Norpro\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Norpro' AND (color = 'copper' OR color = 'black');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_836", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "What is the durability of the carbon steel madeleine pan?", "long_answer": "The madeleine pan, constructed from carbon steel, is designed to be highly durable and to facilitate baking over a significant number of years.", "short_answer": "high durability", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_638", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm doing some heavy duty cooking and need a pan that's not going to melt in the oven and big enough too. Find me a pan that can handle more than 600F in the oven and is larger than 8 inches.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND size > 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND size > 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND size > 8;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_238", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Will this pan withstand frequent washing in the dishwasher if I tend to clean my kitchenware in it often?", "long_answer": "Certainly. This pan is designed for such regular usage. It is built to withstand the high temperatures and harsh chemical detergents commonly found in dishwashers, ensuring it remains resistant to warping, rusting, or deteriorating, even when subjected to daily machine washing.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute feature resistance to both the high temperatures and strong chemicals typical in dishwashers, which ensures they do not warp, rust, or degrade quickly when exposed to such conditions regularly.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_837", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Are acidic foods likely to remove the seasoning from this pan?", "long_answer": "Cooking acidic foods has the potential to strip away the seasoning from the pan, particularly if these foods are cooked for an extended duration.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_639", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm redoing my kitchen and only want copper or blue pans. Show me the biggest one you got in those colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"blue\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"blue\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"blue\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('copper', 'blue') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_838", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is the saucepan's bottom designed to be suitable for glass cooktops?", "long_answer": "The saucepan has a heavy-gauge, hard-anodized aluminum bottom that is flat and uncoated. This design ensures quick heat conduction and prevents the formation of hot spots, making it specifically suitable for use on glass cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_839", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the stainless steel handle of the pan prone to heating up during cooking?", "long_answer": "The stainless steel handle on the pan can become hot during use, particularly if it is used in the oven or placed over high heat for a prolonged period of time. It is advisable to use an oven mitt for safety purposes when touching the handle during and after cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_840", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is this wok suitable for cooking at high temperatures?", "long_answer": "The wok is specifically designed to accommodate the high temperatures typically required for stir-fry cooking. While it can handle these temperatures well, it is recommended to begin cooking at a medium heat and then make adjustments as needed to prevent food from burning and to achieve the desired cooking outcomes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_841", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is it safe to cook with a well-seasoned black steel pan in terms of health risks?", "long_answer": "Cooking with a well-seasoned black steel pan is considered safe and does not present known health concerns, especially when compared to non-stick coatings such as Teflon that have been associated with certain health risks.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_640", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I ain't breaking the bank for a pan. Give me a mid-range priced one that can take the heat, I'm talking over 600F oven safe. What you got?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price BETWEEN 50 AND 100 AND oven_safe_temperature > 600;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_842", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is the Lodge cast iron skillet priced competitively when compared to other high-end cookware brands?", "long_answer": "The Lodge cast iron skillet is considered a great value by many customers as it is durable, versatile, and usually more affordable than other cookware from upscale brands, thus making it competitive in pricing.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_843", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is a lid included with the Bialetti 12-inch saute pan?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti 12-inch saute pan is not accompanied by a lid, as per the product metadata.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_844", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the saucepan designed for use in professional cooking and classic culinary techniques?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is indeed designed to yield professional results, making it appropriate for a variety of classic culinary techniques used in professional settings.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_239", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I aim to acquire sustainable cookware. Would purchasing these pans align with that objective?", "long_answer": "Indeed, purchasing these pans aligns with your objective of sustainable cookware. Made from aluminum, these pans are notable for their high recyclability and contribution to environmental conservation, consistent with sustainable principles.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's environmental considerations are not recommended for those who prefer to minimize their environmental footprint through recyclable and sustainable cookware options, highlighting aluminum's advantage as it can be recycled effectively.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_641", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm after a pan that's either green or black, and it's gotta be able to withstand some serious heat in the oven. What's the highest oven-safe temperature for these?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"black\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"black\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"black\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('green', 'black') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_845", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Do Green Earth Pans by Ozeri release toxic fumes due to PTFE, PFOA, or APEO?", "long_answer": "The Green Earth Pans by Ozeri are designed with GREBLON ceramic, which is completely free of PTFE, PFOA, and APEO, ensuring that no toxic fumes are released during their use, thus providing a safer option for both consumers and the environment.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_846", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is sticking an issue with this new cast iron skillet?", "long_answer": "Minimal sticking may occur initially with any new cast iron skillet. However, with appropriate maintenance, regular seasoning, and the use of proper cooking methods, the amount of sticking typically diminishes as the pan becomes more seasoned over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_847", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the non-stick coating on this pot durable when used as recommended?", "long_answer": "The non-stick coating on this pot is designed to facilitate easy cooking and cleanup, and when proper care is taken and the recommended utensils are used, it has proven to be durable according to customer feedback.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_642", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm tired of the same old black pans. Find me the cheapest colored pan you have that's not black.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'black' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_643", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm all about that sleek silver look for my cookware. Hunt down the cheapest silver pan you have in stock, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color='silver' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_848", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "How durable is the non-stick coating on the pan with proper care and usage?", "long_answer": "The non-stick coating on the pan tends to be durable when the provided care instructions are followed, which include cooking at a low to medium heat and avoiding overheating. Customers generally report satisfaction with the coating's performance over time under these conditions.", "short_answer": "durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_644", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I'm cooking some high-heat meals and I want a copper pan that can withstand over 450F in the oven. What's the most affordable one you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND color = \"copper\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND color = \"copper\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' AND oven_safe_temperature > 450 ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_645", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I ain't gonna pay more than 30 bucks and need a pan that can handle oven heat up to at least 500 degrees F. Show me the biggest one that suits my needs.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_646", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I cook a lot of high-heat dishes, so I need a sturdy pan that can take a beat. What's the first pan you can find that can withstand over 600 degrees?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_647", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Look, I specifically want a Cuisinart pan and I only got 50 bucks to spend. Find me one that can withstand the highest oven temperature.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Cuisinart\" AND price < 50 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Cuisinart\" AND price < 50 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Cuisinart\" AND price < 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Cuisinart' AND price <= 50 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_849", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Does the weight of the pan made with heavy-gauge die-cast aluminum impact its handling during cooking?", "long_answer": "The pan, constructed from heavy-gauge die-cast aluminum, offers a sturdy feel without being excessively weighty. The balance in weight is reported to be comfortable by users, ensuring ease in handling without the sensation of being too light or burdensome.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_850", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set compatible with convection toaster ovens?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set is indeed designed to be used within most convection toaster ovens due to its size and functionality, rendering it suitable for compact oven owners who wish to broil or roast with it.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_240", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Will this pan withstand frequent use at high temperatures?", "long_answer": "Due to the saute pan's lightweight design, it is not recommended to cook frequently at high temperatures as this could cause warping and potentially damage the pan over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a lightweight construction are not recommended for heavy-duty tasks such as long simmering or cooking very dense foods as they may not have the heat retention required and could be prone to warping under prolonged high heat.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saute pan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_851", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "How durable is the nonstick surface of this cookware when used for cooking various foods?", "long_answer": "According to customer feedback, the nonstick surface of this cookware is highly durable and is particularly effective for cooking a variety of foods, with eggs being a common example cited for its performance.", "short_answer": "highly durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_648", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm toying with the idea of buying a Matfer Bourgeat pan larger than 12 inches. Can you recommend the one with the highest oven-safe temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND size > 12 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND size > 12 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND size > 12 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Matfer Bourgeat' AND size > 12 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_649", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm partial to ZWILLING J.A. Henckels gear, but cash is tight. Can you find their cheapest pan under 30 dollars?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND price < 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND price < 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand='ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' AND price < 30 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_650", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I'm trying to cook up a storm but I need a big pan, at least 12 inches, and I'd like to keep the budget under 50 dollars. What's the highest oven-safe temperature I can go for a pan in this range?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND price <= 50 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND price <= 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND price < 50 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_852", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Can the ergonomically designed handles of this product withstand temperatures of up to 350°F in an oven?", "long_answer": "The ergonomically designed handles of this product are indeed oven-safe and can tolerate temperatures reaching up to 350°F, ensuring both comfort and safety during oven use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_853", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is there a warranty provided with the purchase of the Cuisinart French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan?", "long_answer": "Cuisinart provides a lifetime warranty on their French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan, ensuring long-term customer satisfaction and product reliability.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_854", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is this wok suitable for preparing a variety of dishes such as egg dishes or French toast?", "long_answer": "Yes, the wok is designed to be versatile and can handle cooking a wide range of dishes, including but not limited to egg-based dishes and French toast.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_651", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I’m looking for a pan from ZWILLING J.A. Henckels, and it's gotta be either black or grey. Can you recommend one from your inventory?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND color IN (\"black\", \"grey\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" AND color IN (\"black\", \"grey\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' AND (color = 'black' OR color = 'grey');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_855", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan is designed in a way that makes it incompatible with induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_652", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I need a new pan, a big one, at least 8 inches, but I'm picky when it comes to color - nothing flashy, only black or grey will do. Get me the first one that meets these conditions.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND color IN ('black', 'grey') LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_653", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I've had enough of Matfer Bourgeat's stuff. Give me a pan that can withstand the highest oven temperature from any other brand.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Matfer Bourgeat' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_856", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is a steaming rack included with the wok for steaming purposes?", "long_answer": "The wok can be adapted for steaming by using a steaming rack, but it must be noted that the steaming rack does not come with the wok and would need to be purchased separately.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_857", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "What is the maximum meal size that can be prepared in a 9.5-inch square pan?", "long_answer": "A 9.5-inch square pan typically offers sufficient space for cooking meals sized adequately for a family, benefiting from its larger surface area in comparison to round pans.", "short_answer": "family-sized meals", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_858", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is it safe to use high heat when cooking with this non-stick pan?", "long_answer": "It is not advisable to cook at high temperatures with this non-stick pan; doing so may jeopardize the integrity of the non-stick coating. To maintain the pan’s condition and ensure longevity, it is generally recommended to cook at low to medium heat, which prevents overheating and potential damage.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_654", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I'm after a pan that's copper or silver in color. What's the cheapest one you got in those colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"silver\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"silver\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"silver\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('copper', 'silver') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_655", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm looking for a good size pan - at least 8 inches - but I don't want to pay above the average price. Give me your best option.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND size >= 8 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND size >= 8 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 \n  AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) \n                FROM all_pans)\nORDER BY price ASC\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_859", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the saucepan come with a transparent lid that allows visibility of contents during cooking?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is equipped with a non-transparent lid, which means that you cannot see the contents inside while cooking without removing the lid.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_860", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the pan suitable for cooking at high temperatures without damaging its non-stick surface?", "long_answer": "The pan is crafted from durable aluminum, which can withstand typical cooking temperatures, but to maintain the non-stick surface's integrity, cooking at moderate heat is recommended.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_656", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I'm not too fond of black and need to replace my large-sized pans. Whats's the highest oven safe temperature for the 8 inch or larger-size pan you got that's not black?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND size >= 8 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND size >= 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'black' AND size >= 8 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_861", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are the pans from the Green Earth Frying Pan Set oven-safe?", "long_answer": "The pans from the Green Earth Frying Pan Set are not suitable for oven use because their handles are coated with silicone, a material that is heat-resistant but intended solely for stovetop cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_862", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is it advisable to use high heat when cooking with this 3.2mm gauge aluminum pan?", "long_answer": "The 3.2mm gauge aluminum pan is crafted to conduct heat swiftly and uniformly. Despite its good heat conduction properties, it is generally recommended to refrain from cooking on high heat in order to preserve the non-stick coating and extend the life of the pan.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_863", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the Presto 5900 wok suitable for deep frying?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 wok is intended for stir-frying, which involves cooking with a minimal amount of oil, hence it is not recommended for deep frying purposes that require submerging food in large quantities of oil.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_864", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Are the pans designed to resist warping over time with regular use?", "long_answer": "The pans have a stainless-steel bonded Anti-Warp base, and the majority of users have not experienced any warping, suggesting that the pans maintain their flat shape throughout regular use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_657", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I'm not a fan of Norpro so don't bother showing me anything from them. I need the largest pan from any other brand ya got.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Norpro\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Norpro\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Norpro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Norpro' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_865", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the All-Clad D3 Fry Pan manufactured in the United States?", "long_answer": "The All-Clad D3 Fry Pan is manufactured in the United States, ensuring a product that is designed with warp-resistant strength and exhibits high-quality craftsmanship.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_658", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm only interested in Tramontina and Copper Chef pans, and nothing smaller than 10 inches. What's the first option you have for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch` with asin: B009HBKQR0", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Copper Chef\") AND size >= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Copper Chef\") AND size >= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Tramontina', 'Copper Chef') AND size >= 10 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_866", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "What is the specific diameter measurement of this skillet?", "long_answer": "The specific diameter measurement of this skillet is 12.5 inches, which allows for the preparation of a wide range of dishes due to its sizable cooking surface.", "short_answer": "12.5 inches", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_659", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm after a silver or grey pan, but I've had bad experiences with Utopia Kitchen before. What's the cheapest pan you have that's not from them?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"grey\") AND NOT brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"grey\") AND NOT brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"grey\") AND NOT brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('silver', 'grey') AND brand != 'Utopia Kitchen' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_867", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is it advisable to use cooking spray on these non-stick pans?", "long_answer": "Using cooking spray on these non-stick pans is not advised because it can accumulate and ultimately impair the pan's non-stick qualities. Instead, it's better to use a small amount of oil or butter for cooking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_660", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I don't want to spend more than 30 bucks for a pan. Find me the cheapest one you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_661", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I'm looking to get a good-sized pan without breaking the bank, can you pick out a pan that's larger than 12 inches and doesn't cost more than 20 bucks?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND price <= 20 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND price <= 20 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 12 AND price <= 20 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_662", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm in the market for a big pan, preferably grey or copper-colored. Which one of those do you have that's the largest?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'copper') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_663", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I've been using Tramontina pans for years now. What's the biggest size you have that can withstand a good 500 degrees in the oven?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Tramontina\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Tramontina\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Tramontina\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Tramontina' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_868", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the nonstick coating effective when using low-fat or no-fat cooking methods?", "long_answer": "The nonstick surface of the cookware is designed to enable cooking with minimal or no added fats or oils, promoting healthier cooking practices that align with low-fat or no-fat cooking methods.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_664", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I'm looking for a big blue pan to match my kitchen - hit me up with the largest one you've got in stock.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"blue\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color='blue' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_241", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is this pan suitable for rapidly cooling my dishes by immersing them in cold water post-cooking?", "long_answer": "No, this pan wouldn't be the optimal choice for that technique. The cast iron lid is particularly susceptible to thermal shock, which may happen when a hot pan is abruptly introduced to cold water and could lead to the lid warping or cracking.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a cast iron lid cannot be used for quick cooking methods that rely on rapid temperature changes, as cast iron can be prone to thermal shock when exposed to sudden shifts in temperature, potentially leading to cracking or warping.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "cast iron lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_665", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I've got this weird thing about copper colored pans, just can't stand 'em. What's the biggest non-copper pan you've got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'copper' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_869", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the T-fal saucepan resistant to stains from burnt food?", "long_answer": "The T-fal saucepan is designed for ease of cleaning and generally does not retain stains, as reported by customers, even in instances where food has been burnt inside it.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_666", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Look, I only trust Tramontina and T-fal when it comes to pans. Find me the biggest pan these brands offer.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"T-fal\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"T-fal\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"T-fal\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Tramontina', 'T-fal') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_870", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does the steel strip handle of the pan offer a comfortable grip?", "long_answer": "The steel strip handle of the pan is made from high-quality, durable materials, but user experiences indicate that it can be uncomfortable or unwieldy, particularly when the pan is heavy with contents. It is often suggested to use a silicone grip to enhance comfort during use.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_242", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is this pan ideal for those seeking low-maintenance cookware?", "long_answer": "Given that this pan is not suitable for the dishwasher, it might not suit those who prefer low-maintenance cookware. This pan needs particular attention, such as periodic re-seasoning and gentle hand-washing, to maintain its prime condition.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" fail to meet the requirements for easy maintenance and may involve extra steps like re-seasoning or careful hand-polishing to uphold their performance and appearance standards.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_667", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Hey, I'm frequently cooking with an oven-safe pan from All-Clad, but it's not handling the average oven temperature well. Can you find me one from the same brand that does?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black` with asin: B0170TFNXM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND brand = \"All-Clad\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND brand = \"All-Clad\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'All-Clad' AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans WHERE brand = 'All-Clad');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_871", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Does the cooking surface area of the pan measure less than the advertised dimensions of 12 inches by 9 inches?", "long_answer": "The cooking surface of the pan is indeed reduced from the stated 12\" x 9\" due to the design of the indented edges, resulting in a usable cooking area that is smaller than the overall dimensions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_668", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I want something from USA Pan that doesn't bleed my wallet. You got a big size one that's 30 bucks or less?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"USA Pan\" AND price <= 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"USA Pan\" AND price <= 30 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"USA Pan\" AND price <= 30 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'USA Pan' AND price <= 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_872", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with this non-stick pan?", "long_answer": "It is not advisable to use metal utensils with this non-stick pan as they have the potential to damage the surface of the pan. To maintain the pan's condition and extend its lifespan, it is recommended to use utensils made of wood or plastic instead.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_243", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I've recently acquired a new cooktop and want to ensure I purchase a pan that is compatible. Are there specific features I should be on the lookout for?", "long_answer": "When searching for a new pan, opt for one with a circular design to ensure greater compatibility with different types of stovetops, particularly the latest induction models. Make sure the pan is constructed from a magnetic-grade material if you intend to use it on an induction cooktop, which will guarantee seamless performance.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_873", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it necessary to cook on a high heat setting with the Copper Chef pan?", "long_answer": "The Copper Chef pan is engineered to distribute heat rapidly and uniformly, thus it is advised to utilize a lower heat setting than you might normally use with other cookware to achieve optimal cooking outcomes.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_874", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is this wok suitable for high-temperature cooking methods such as searing meat?", "long_answer": "This wok can be used for high-temperature cooking including searing meat, but it is important to note that it may develop hot spots or burn food if not closely watched. Users should stir frequently and keep a close eye on the temperature to avoid these issues.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_875", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is seasoning required before the first use of a stainless-steel wok?", "long_answer": "Seasoning a stainless-steel wok prior to its initial use is recommended by some customers. The process enhances the wok's non-stick qualities and makes it easier to clean. The user manual usually contains the necessary instructions for seasoning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_876", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is there a Madeleine pan available that has a capacity greater than 12 cups?", "long_answer": "We currently only provide a Madeleine pan that comes with 12 cups. If you are looking to bake more Madeleines at the same time, you might need to purchase additional 12-cup pans.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_244", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Can this pan be easily accommodated in a compact oven while ensuring adequate circulation of heat?", "long_answer": "Due to the design of this product, it may be incompatible with compact countertop ovens, since its form could obstruct the oven door from sealing properly or may restrict airflow and heat distribution on account of its dimensions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with rectangular shapes are not suitable for small countertop ovens where their size might prevent the door from closing or limit the circulation of heat due to limited space.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "rectangular", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_669", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Look, I'm not about to fork over more than 20 dollars for a pan. Find me the cheapest one you got that can handle the most heat in the oven.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_877", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Are Copper Chef pans free from PFOS, PTFE, and PFOA?", "long_answer": "Copper Chef pans are manufactured to be completely devoid of PFOS, PTFE, and PFOA, which ensures that they are an environmentally friendly option for cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_670", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I'm kind of picky with my kitchen stuff. I'm only interested in \"Chicago Metallic\" or \"Cuisinart\" brands. And it has to be in blue or green. Can you find a pan that meets these once in a blue moon preferences of mine?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Chicago Metallic\", \"Cuisinart\") AND color IN (\"blue\", \"green\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Chicago Metallic\", \"Cuisinart\") AND color IN (\"blue\", \"green\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (brand = 'Chicago Metallic' OR brand = 'Cuisinart') AND (color = 'blue' OR color = 'green');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_878", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with the Copper Chef pan?", "long_answer": "It is not advised to use metal utensils with the Copper Chef pan, as doing so can damage the non-stick ceramic coating. To preserve the pan's surface, one should use utensils made from materials such as wood, plastic, silicone, or bamboo.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_671", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Look, I ain't a fan of Anolon and I'm only interested in copper or grey pans. So what's the least expensive pan you got in those colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"grey\") AND NOT brand = \"Anolon\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"grey\") AND NOT brand = \"Anolon\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"grey\") AND NOT brand = \"Anolon\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'Anolon' AND color IN ('copper', 'grey') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_672", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm not crazy about T-fal, but I need a bigger than average pan that can handle the heat. Can you find me the one that can tolerate the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"T-fal\" AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"T-fal\" AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"T-fal\" AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'T-fal' AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_879", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is this pan suitable for cooking methods apart from broiling, such as roasting or grilling?", "long_answer": "Yes, the pan is versatile and can be used for a variety of cooking methods, including roasting and grilling, in both conventional and convection ovens, allowing you to choose the appropriate technique based on your culinary requirements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_673", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I cook at high temperatures and I don't care for brands other than Utopia Kitchen or Norpro. So, can you find me a pan from one of these brands that can withstand more than 450 F?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Norpro\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 450 AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Norpro\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Utopia Kitchen', 'Norpro') AND oven_safe_temperature > 450;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_674", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Look, I've only got 30 bucks and I need a pan that's either grey or copper. Find me the cheapest one you've got in those colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND color IN (\"grey\", \"copper\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'copper') AND price <= 30 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_245", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Do I require specific tools or methods to thoroughly clean this pan?", "long_answer": "Certainly, a pan featuring a complex, novelty design might necessitate special tools or methods for thorough cleaning. These are essential for accessing every crevice and recess while maintaining the non-stick surface and ensuring the pan's integrity.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with novelty shapes fail to meet the requirements for easy maintenance if the design is too intricate, leading to challenging cleaning processes to preserve the pan’s integrity and non-stick coating.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "novelty shapes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_880", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is it safe to use metal utensils with the Matfer Bourgeat Black Steel Frying Pan?", "long_answer": "The Matfer Bourgeat Black Steel Frying Pan is built to be durable, allowing the use of metal utensils. While metal utensils can be used, it is recommended to use them gently in order to preserve the seasoning of the pan over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_881", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Do buns made with this hot dog pan typically result in smaller buns compared to standard store-bought buns?", "long_answer": "Customers have observed that the buns produced by this hot dog bun pan are often smaller than the average store-bought hot dog buns. For those who wish to make larger buns to fit bigger hot dogs, it is advisable to increase the amount of dough used for each bun.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_246", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Could this pan enhance the flavors when I cook dishes such as stews or braised meats?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the cast iron lid of this pan plays a vital role in improving the flavor of your meals. It retains moisture and seasoning inside the pan, bolstering the taste of stews and braised meats through a gradual and uniform cooking method.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a cast iron lid feature a tight seal due to the weight of the lid, which helps in locking in moisture and flavor—a crucial aspect for many cooking methods such as simmering or braising.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "cast iron lid", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_882", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Is the silicone rubber on the saucepan's handles designed to stay cool while cooking?", "long_answer": "The silicone rubber material used on the saucepan's handles is specifically designed to resist heat and stay cool to the touch, even when the saucepan is being used for cooking on a heated stove.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_675", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I ain't dropping mad cash on this and I need a pan that's at least 8 inches. Fetch me your cheapest option that fits the requirements.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND price < 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND price < 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_676", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I've been loyal to T-fal for a while now. Find me their cheapest pan.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'T-fal' \nORDER BY price \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_247", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Will this pan provide even cooking, particularly when searing meat?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the pan's round design aids in even heat distribution, making it especially useful for searing meats. This feature helps ensure that the food cooks evenly without the formation of hot spots.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_248", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Might the shape of the pan render it difficult to fit in a drawer alongside other kitchen implements?", "long_answer": "The circular design of the pan may not fit neatly with the square contours of drawers, which could make it more cumbersome to store with other kitchen tools. Opting for a pan whose shape matches your drawer's storage capacity can aid in conserving space and maintaining organization.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_883", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "How long does the nonstick surface of this product typically last with proper use?", "long_answer": "According to customer feedback, the nonstick surface of the product tends to be very durable and maintains its quality over time when the care and usage instructions are followed correctly, which satisfies many users in terms of its longevity.", "short_answer": "very durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_884", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the bottom pan of the broiler set suitable for reheating food?", "long_answer": "The bottom pan of the broiler set is designed to be used independently and is suitable for reheating food. To enhance the reheating process and prevent food from sticking, it is recommended to add a small amount of water to the pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_249", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is this pan suitable for use on my induction stove?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the pan should function effectively on an induction cooktop, provided it is constructed from a magnetic material. Its circular design enhances its suitability for various types of stovetops, induction ones included.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_885", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is it necessary to use pot holders to handle the saucepan after cooking?", "long_answer": "It is recommended to use pot holders when handling the saucepan or its lid after cooking because, despite the handle design which stays cool on the stovetop, the handle and lid can become hot.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_677", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I need a pan that can handle the heat, at least 500F, and doesn't feel like a toy in my hands. Size has to be 10 inches or more. Find me the cheapest one you have on display.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size >= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size >= 10 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size >= 10 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size >= 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_678", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "I like Anolon and Presto brands but I'm fed up with the same old silver color. Can you show me the highest oven safe temperature pan these brands offer in any but silver?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray` with asin: B000069RBK", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Presto\") AND NOT color = \"silver\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Presto\") AND NOT color = \"silver\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Anolon\", \"Presto\") AND NOT color = \"silver\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Anolon', 'Presto') AND color != 'silver' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_886", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is the Madeleine Pan suitable for baking various types of tea and dessert cakes beyond Madeleines?", "long_answer": "Yes, the Madeleine Pan is explicitly designed for Madeleines; however, it is versatile enough to accommodate a variety of other tea and dessert cake recipes, offering room for culinary creativity.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_679", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I've had it up to here with Chicago Metallic stuff. Point me to the pan from a different brand that can handle the highest oven temperature.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Chicago Metallic' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_887", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the saucepan require special care or cleaners to maintain its condition according to customer feedback?", "long_answer": "Customer feedback has indicated that while there may be spots or marks appearing after use, the saucepan can be maintained in excellent condition with proper care and the use of a cleaner such as Bar Keepers Friend.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_680", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I ain't splurging more than 20 and want a green-colored pan. And it's gotta handle heat well. What's the highest oven-safe temperature for such a pan you got?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND color = \"green\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND color = \"green\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 20 AND color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 20 AND color = 'green' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_888", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the exterior of the pan prone to staining over time, particularly when used on high heat?", "long_answer": "The performance of the pan is generally appreciated, but it is noted that the exterior may suffer from staining over time, an issue exacerbated by exposure to high heat, as evident from reviews.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_681", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm not looking to splurge on some fancy colored pans, basic grey or black will do. And keep it average or below average in terms of pricing. What's the first pan you got that fits those conditions?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND color IN (\"grey\", \"black\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'black') AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY product_id ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_250", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is there any special equipment required to utilize this pan on various stovetops?", "long_answer": "If you are transitioning between various kinds of stovetops, our aluminum and copper fry pans are suitable for use on gas, electric, and glass ceramic cooktops. However, for induction cooktops, a separate ferrous disk is required for compatibility with the induction system, as these materials do not possess magnetic properties.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum or copper construction do not have a function of magnetic induction compatibility and are therefore not suitable for use on induction stovetops without an additional ferrous disk.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_889", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Does the pot come with a vented glass lid to monitor the cooking process?", "long_answer": "The pot features a vented glass lid that allows you to observe the food during the cooking process without lifting the lid, which can help maintain a constant temperature and prevent spills.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_682", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Cooking at high temperatures is my thing and I need a pan that can handle the heat in my oven. Plus, it has to be at least 8 inches. Can you help me find the most affordable one?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_683", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm looking to add some flair to my kitchen with a copper or blue pan, but I also need it to survive high heats of over 600F. What's the cheapest option you have that fits all my requirements?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"blue\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"blue\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"copper\", \"blue\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (color = 'copper' OR color = 'blue') \nAND oven_safe_temperature > 600 \nORDER BY price ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_684", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm sick of my small pans and I only want black or blue ones. Show me the largest pan you got in those colors.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") AND size > 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"blue\") AND size > 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('black', 'blue') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_890", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the saucepan suitable for beginners or individuals living in dormitories?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is designed with a focus on ease of use and ease of cleaning, making it an ideal and practical option for beginners or individuals residing in dormitory settings, catering to a range of cooking requirements.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_685", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I'm angling for a steal here, looking for a pan that's below the average price, preferably from T-fal or Presto. I need the biggest one you got that fits these conditions.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Presto\") ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Presto\") AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Presto\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND (brand = 'T-fal' OR brand = 'Presto') ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_686", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm whipping up some high-heat dishes in a big pan. Which is your biggest pan that can withstand at least 500 degrees in the oven?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size >= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND size >= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_687", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm all about T-fal and need a pan that can withstand a 400-degree oven. What's the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black` with asin: B004VJMT78", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'T-fal' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_688", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I do a lot of oven cooking, so I need a pan that can resist at least the average temperature around here. Can you find me the largest one that can handle the heat?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) \nORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_689", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm not looking to splurge, but I need a pan that can withstand at least 600F in the oven and doesn't cost more than 50 bucks. What's my best option?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND price <= 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND price <= 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND price <= 50 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_690", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I can't stand Presto products. What's the first non-Presto brand pan in your list?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Presto\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Presto' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_891", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Is the Norpro 273 Pan Set compatible with both regular and toaster ovens?", "long_answer": "The Norpro 273 Pan Set is designed to be versatile and can be used in both regular ovens and toaster ovens, as evidenced by customer experiences who have used it in these different types of ovens successfully.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_892", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the silicone handle on this product resist heat?", "long_answer": "The silicone handle, designed with rivets, ensures that it stays cool and provides a secure, comfortable grip without transferring heat to the user's hand.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_691", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I'm not too fond of Copper Chef pans, I'm looking for something else. Give me the pan with the highest oven safe temperature that is more than 8 inches, just not a Copper Chef.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND size > 8 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND size > 8 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Copper Chef\" AND size > 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Copper Chef' AND size > 8 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_893", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is a lid provided with the purchase of the Stone Earth Frying Pan?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Frying Pan does not come with a lid. However, standard-sized lids are compatible with the pan, and those requiring a lid can purchase one separately.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_894", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Does this bread pan require greasing before use?", "long_answer": "The bread pan is equipped with a non-stick Americoat coating that typically allows for easy release of baked goods. Despite this, the manufacturer suggests that a light application of grease may be beneficial for optimal results with some recipes.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_895", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "How does the Presto 5900 electric wok's durability compare to other electric woks on the market?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 electric wok is perceived by most customers as being very sturdy and long-lasting, often providing several years of reliable usage, indicating that its durability is generally considered to be high compared to other electric woks available.", "short_answer": "high", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_896", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Do the rivets in the pan's interior disrupt the stirring process?", "long_answer": "The rivets are present in the pan to secure the handle and might mildly interfere with stirring, as reported by some users, but this does not detract significantly from the pan's quality according to overall user feedback.", "short_answer": "slightly", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_897", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Does the red silicone sleeve on the pan's handle resist heat and aid in handling?", "long_answer": "The red silicone sleeve on the pan's handle is specifically designed to resist heat, thereby providing a cooler touch and offering a comfortable grip that assists in safely maneuvering the pan during use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_898", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Can this pan be used in the oven as well as on the stovetop?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be versatile and heat resistant up to 850°F, thus it is suitable for use on both the stovetop and in the oven, enabling a seamless cooking experience between the two.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_692", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm sick of the same old black pans. Show me the non-black one that can take the most heat in the oven.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"black\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'black' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_693", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I'm looking for a good-sized pan, has to be more than 8 inches, in either green or grey. What's my best option here?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND color IN (\"green\", \"grey\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND color IN (\"green\", \"grey\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND (color = 'green' OR color = 'grey') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_899", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "What is the specific depth of the pan, and can it accommodate the flipping of foods such as omelets and pancakes?", "long_answer": "The pan is specifically designed with the ideal depth and size conducive to cooking crepes, pancakes, and similar foods, thereby facilitating effortless flipping and removal of these items.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_694", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm not interested in those pans that can't take a good bake. Give me one that can withstand higher than your average oven safe temperature.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_900", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is a lid included with the purchase of this pan?", "long_answer": "The pan itself does not come with a lid when purchased. However, it has been designed to be compatible with separately available lids that are of the appropriate size.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_901", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is it recommended to use metal utensils with this non-stick ceramic-coated pan?", "long_answer": "It is not recommended to use metal utensils with this pan; instead, the use of non-metallic utensils such as wood, plastic, silicone, or bamboo is advised to protect the non-stick ceramic coating.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_251", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "What kind of maintenance will be needed for this pan in the long run?", "long_answer": "As time goes by, this pan will demand additional care compared to other alternatives, as it is not dishwasher safe. For optimal performance and appearance, it is imperative to hand wash it and adhere to specific maintenance procedures, such as periodic re-seasoning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" fail to meet the requirements for easy maintenance and may involve extra steps like re-seasoning or careful hand-polishing to uphold their performance and appearance standards.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_902", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is the large aluminum pan easy to handle due to its weight?", "long_answer": "The large pan is manufactured from aluminum, which is a lighter material compared to other metals. This quality ensures that despite its substantial size, the pan remains manageable to handle.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_903", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is there a Lifetime Warranty included with the purchase of this Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan?", "long_answer": "The Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan comes with a Lifetime Warranty, ensuring that it is covered for defects under normal use for the duration of the product's life.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_252", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Can this pan function effectively on my induction cooktop?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the pan should function effectively on an induction stovetop provided that it is constructed from a magnetic material. Its circular design ensures it is compatible with various types of stovetops, including those that are induction-based.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_253", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is it safe to routinely wash this pan in my dishwasher without causing it harm?", "long_answer": "Certainly, you can effortlessly cleanse this pan in your dishwasher with confidence. Our pans are crafted from resilient materials such as stainless steel and aluminum, ensuring they can endure the vigorous conditions within a dishwasher without diminishing in quality.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute typically mean that they are composed of durable materials such as stainless steel, aluminum, or certain coated or anodized metals, capable of withstanding the rigorous conditions of a dishwasher without deteriorating.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_904", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is this bread pan suitable for baking various types of food such as hot dog buns and cornbread?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed to be versatile, allowing for the baking of different food items including, but not limited to, hot dog buns and cornbread.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_905", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Does the corrugated surface design of the bakeware alter the shape of the baked goods?", "long_answer": "The corrugated surface design of the bakeware is implemented to enhance circulation and heat distribution during baking. It is not intended to significantly change the shape of the baked goods but instead assists in providing a uniform bake and facilitates easy removal of the items from the bakeware.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_254", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "My cupboard space is quite limited; is it possible to store this pan conveniently when it's not in use?", "long_answer": "Round-shaped pans may not be the most space-efficient for storage in cramped kitchens, which could be a disadvantage if optimizing every inch is essential for you. Square or angular pans may be a more suitable option if you need to fit them into a tight cupboard or shelf.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_906", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Are metal utensils safe to use with these non-stick ceramic pans?", "long_answer": "Using metal utensils with these non-stick ceramic pans is discouraged because it can damage the integrity of the non-stick surface. To avoid scratches and abrasions, it is recommended to use utensils made from plastic, wood, or silicone when handling the pans.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_907", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is the Stone Earth Pan by Ozeri compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Pan by Ozeri features a magnetized base that facilitates rapid heat transfer, ensuring that it is suitable not only for induction cooktops but also for various other kinds of cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_695", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "I'm only interested in Ozeri and All-Clad brands. What's the cheapest pan you have from either of them? Don't make me wait around.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Ozeri\", \"All-Clad\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Ozeri\", \"All-Clad\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Ozeri\", \"All-Clad\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Ozeri', 'All-Clad') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_696", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm looking for a blue or copper pan, but it needs to take the heat, like above 500F oven safe. Let me know what you have.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 500 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (color = 'blue' OR color = 'copper') AND oven_safe_temperature > 500;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_908", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the lid of this stainless steel pan constructed from the same material and does it provide a tight fit?", "long_answer": "The lid of the pan is indeed fabricated from stainless steel and its design ensures a tight fit, highly beneficial for simmering foods as it effectively traps heat and moisture within the pan.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_697", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm not a fan of Matfer Bourgeat, but I need a grey pan, and it has to be the biggest one you have. Can you find that for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND color = \"grey\" ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND color = \"grey\" AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Matfer Bourgeat\" AND color = \"grey\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'grey' AND brand != 'Matfer Bourgeat' \nORDER BY size DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_909", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Does the pan's construction with commercial grade, heavy gauge aluminized steel ensure resistance to warping and durability?", "long_answer": "The pan is manufactured using commercial grade, heavy gauge aluminized steel, which is known for providing uniform heat distribution. Additionally, the pan's unique fluted surface enhances its structural integrity, making it more resistant to warping and contributing to its overall durability.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_910", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Is it necessary to grease the pan when using the AMERICOAT Plus non-stick coating?", "long_answer": "The AMERICOAT Plus non-stick coating is engineered to release baked goods easily without the requirement of additional greasing. While the coating should perform effectively on its own, some users opt for a light greasing as a precautionary measure for guaranteed release of their baked items.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_911", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "What heat setting should be used when cooking with this pan to avoid damaging it?", "long_answer": "To maintain the pan's condition and prevent any potential damage, it is advised to utilize medium heat settings during cooking. High heat should be avoided to ensure the pan's longevity and optimal performance.", "short_answer": "medium heat", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_912", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Does the included lid create a secure seal to retain moisture and flavor during cooking?", "long_answer": "The included lid is designed to fit tightly, ensuring that moisture and flavor are locked in during the cooking process.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_698", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm loyal to T-fal and Cuisinart, and I need a pan that's larger than 12 inches. Sort it out and tell me which is the least expensive from these brands.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Cuisinart\") AND size > 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Cuisinart\") AND size > 12 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"T-fal\", \"Cuisinart\") AND size > 12 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('T-fal', 'Cuisinart') AND size > 12 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_699", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I'm trying to save some cash and need a pan for under $30. What's the hottest oven temperature safe one you got for that price?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_700", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I like my pans to be copper-colored. Which one can endure the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper' ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_701", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Need a new pan. Not anything flashy, just grey or silver. What's the cheapest one you got in those colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"grey\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"grey\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"grey\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'silver') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_913", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Does the USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan include a warranty?", "long_answer": "The USA Pan Hearth Bread Pan comes with a limited lifetime warranty, offering assurance against defects and workmanship under normal use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_914", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the Cuisinart saucepan come with a lifetime warranty?", "long_answer": "Cuisinart offers a lifetime warranty for its cookware collection, which includes the saucepan in question, ensuring customers can rely on the cookware's durability over time.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_702", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm trying to find a grey or silver pan that's larger than average yet affordable. What's my best bet?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"silver\") AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"silver\") AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"silver\") AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'silver') AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_915", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Does the honeycomb textured surface of the pans improve heat distribution and non-stick performance without compromising cooking quality?", "long_answer": "The honeycomb textured surface of the pans is engineered to improve heat distribution across the cooking surface while also enhancing non-stick capabilities, resulting in a performance that does not detract from the cooking quality of the pans.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_916", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Is the Presto 5900 electric wok able to achieve the high temperatures needed for authentic wok cooking?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 electric wok is designed to sear foods at high temperatures, mimicking the cooking conditions of traditional wok cooking. However, users recommend careful monitoring and adjustment of the temperature settings to avoid unintentionally burning the food during cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_255", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I understand certain pans require specific maintenance post-cooking. What would be entailed in caring for this particular pan?", "long_answer": "This specific pan requires special attention, as it is not dishwasher-safe. Once you've finished cooking, it must be manually washed with the appropriate methods and promptly dried to avoid any harm. If you prefer not to devote time to such upkeep routinely, you might consider opting for a dishwasher-friendly pan.", "short_answer": "handwash", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are not recommended for use by consumers who may not be willing or able to invest the time and effort into the careful maintenance these pans require, which includes correct hand-washing techniques and immediate drying to prevent damage.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_703", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm not going to splash out more than 30 dollars for a pan. Get me the cheapest one from Utopia Kitchen or Presto.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Presto\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 30 AND brand IN (\"Utopia Kitchen\", \"Presto\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND (brand = 'Utopia Kitchen' OR brand = 'Presto') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_256", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Can this pan be conveniently stored in unconventional kitchen spaces while maintaining its versatility?", "long_answer": "It is worth mentioning that the round shape of the pan may present difficulties fitting into atypical kitchen spaces, potentially restricting your storage possibilities if your kitchen features a unique design.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape lack the capability to efficiently fit into square or awkward kitchen spaces, which may be a consideration for storage in small kitchens where every inch of space counts.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_917", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "What is the weight or ease of handling of the Presto 5900 Electric Wok like?", "long_answer": "The Presto 5900 Electric Wok, crafted from stainless steel, brings with it a sense of durability and weight. However, it is not overly heavy and is typically deemed manageable for the average user. Additionally, it includes side loop handles that aid in its transportation and maneuvering.", "short_answer": "manageable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_918", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is the skillet's weight suitable for use on a glass top stove without causing damage?", "long_answer": "The skillet can be safely used on glass top stoves; however, its heavy weight necessitates careful handling. Users must lift the skillet instead of sliding it across the stove's surface to prevent scratching or other forms of damage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_704", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I do some heavy cooking and need a pan that can handle the heat, specifically, temperatures of 400 degrees Fahrenheit or more. Give me the details of your biggest one that can take it.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_705", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I've had a bad run with Bialetti pans, I want something different. What's the cheapest pan you've got that's not from Bialetti?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Bialetti\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Bialetti\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"Bialetti\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price = (SELECT price FROM all_pans WHERE brand != 'Bialetti' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1);"}}
{"id": "search_qa_706", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm whipping up a storm in the kitchen a lot and usually with a hot oven. Grab me the product ID of the first pan you find that's bigger than 10 inches and can handle at least 400°F.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n` USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan` with asin: B002UNMZPS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 10 AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_707", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm into the retro aesthetic, you know? Hook me up with a copper-colored pan if you've got any.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'copper';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_257", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Is this pan appropriate for use under the broiler in the oven?", "long_answer": "No, this pan should not be used for broiling in the oven. The aluminum composition of the pan lacks the resilience needed to endure the high temperatures involved in broiling. This could result in damage or a compromise in its structural integrity, in contrast to pans made from stainless steel or cast iron.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's lack of high heat tolerance lack the capability to withstand searing and broiling applications that require maintaining structural integrity at very high temperatures, unlike cookware made of materials like stainless steel or cast iron.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_919", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Are these pans suitable for use in professional cooking environments?", "long_answer": "These pans are of high-quality construction, designed to cater to the demands of both home and professional cooking environments, thereby making them appropriate for professional cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_708", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "I like to cook at high temperatures, and I need a big pan that can handle at least 600F in the oven. Which is the largest one you have that fits my needs?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 600 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_709", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Listen pal, I ain't about to spend a fortune and I need a pan that can handle some serious heat, hotter than what most pans can take. Can you hunt up the biggest pan you got that won't cost me more than 50 bucks and can handle an above-average oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND price < 50 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND price < 50 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) AND price < 50 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature > (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_920", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the handle designed to stay cool while cooking?", "long_answer": "The handle has an ergonomic design engineered to remain cool for safety and comfort during cooking, as substantiated by numerous customer testimonials indicating that it doesn't become hot while in use.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_258", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Can this pan be used to roast a chicken?", "long_answer": "No, this pan is not suitable for \"dry cooking\" methods like roasting because it is equipped with a tempered glass lid. This type of lid is meant to keep moisture in, which can disrupt the necessary dry heat for correctly roasting a chicken.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with tempered glass lids are not suitable for recipes requiring “dry cooking” methods such as roasting or baking without moisture, as the lids are designed to retain moisture within the pan.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "tempered glass lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_921", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "What is the expected lifespan of a Bialetti non-stick pan with proper usage and care?", "long_answer": "The lifespan of a Bialetti non-stick pan can extend to several years when taken care of correctly. The durability is influenced by several factors including the frequency of use and how well the care instructions are followed, which involve using appropriate utensils and avoiding high heating settings.", "short_answer": "several years", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_710", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I cook a lot and need a pan that can endure high oven temperatures, over 600F actually. But please, no \"USA Pan\" brand. Can you find me the least expensive option?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'USA Pan' AND oven_safe_temperature > 600 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_711", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm not shelling out more than 30 dollars for a pan and I want a silver one. What's the biggest one you have that doesn't cost more than that?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok` with asin: B0017UTSLY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND price <= 30 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND price <= 30 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"silver\" AND price <= 30 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 30 AND color = 'silver' ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_712", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I only got 50 dollars to blow and I need a pan that can take some heat. Get me the cheapest one you got that can stand at least the average oven safe temperature.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 50 AND oven_safe_temperature >= (SELECT AVG(oven_safe_temperature) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_259", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is this pan suitable for regularly cooking diverse dishes without concerns over its durability?", "long_answer": "The pan should be suitable for most types of cooking. Nevertheless, if you frequently cook with acidic or alkaline ingredients, it's wise to opt for a treated or anodized pan to prevent metallic taste transfer and discoloration. This could also affect the pan's longevity with regular exposure to these substances.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with reactivity to acidic and alkaline foods feature a potential for metallic taste transfer and discoloration, rendering them less suitable for long-term cooking of tomato sauces or citrus-based dishes unless they're treated or anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_922", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "How durable is the nonstick surface with proper usage and care?", "long_answer": "With proper usage and care, which includes utilizing non-metal utensils and avoiding high heat, the nonstick surface tends to be durable, as reported by the majority of customers.", "short_answer": "very durable", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_923", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is the Stone Earth Frying Pan compatible with induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Frying Pan is designed with a magnetized base that ensures rapid heat transfer, making it fully compatible for use on induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_260", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm concerned about burning chocolate when I melt it; does this pan have a feature that prevents this?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the uniform heat distribution in a saucepan reduces the likelihood of hot spots, crucial when melting chocolate to prevent scorching and maintain a smooth texture.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being a saucepan are known for their even heat distribution which is essential for preventing hot spots that could scorch delicate sauces or custards.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "saucepan", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_261", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I frequently encounter issues with pans that fail to heat evenly on my stove. Is this design engineered to assist with uniform heating?", "long_answer": "Indeed, the pan's round shape helps to distribute heat more uniformly across its surface, enhancing compatibility and heating efficiency on various stovetops—from conventional to contemporary induction cooktops—provided it is made from suitable magnetic material.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_924", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Is the Bialetti 12-inch pan suitable for professional cooks and advanced cooking techniques?", "long_answer": "The Bialetti 12-inch pan is designed to be versatile for various cooking styles, but professional cooks or individuals skilled in advanced cooking techniques may prefer specialized cookware tailored to their specific culinary requirements.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_713", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I'm looking for a copper pan that won't break the bank. Got anything under 50 dollars?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND price <= 50 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = \"copper\" AND price <= 50 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price < 50 AND color = 'copper';"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_925", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Does the Stone Earth Pan provide even heat distribution for cooking?", "long_answer": "The Stone Earth Pan is specifically designed to distribute heat evenly, ensuring uniform cooking and browning without the presence of hot spots. This feature is noted in the product's description and is also reflected in the positive reports from customers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_926", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Do the handles remain secure and maintain durability over time?", "long_answer": "Based on customer feedback, the handles are generally comfortable and remain secure initially; however, some customers have reported that they may become loose with prolonged use. It is advised to routinely inspect and tighten any screws to ensure continued durability and security. Should any issues arise, reaching out to the manufacturer is recommended.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_714", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Look, I'm trying to stick to Utopia Kitchen for my cooking ware but I don't want to pay more than the average price. Can you find me a pan that withstands high oven temperatures?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch` with asin: B00X4WQMAS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" AND price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" AND price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Utopia Kitchen\" AND price < (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Utopia Kitchen' AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans WHERE brand = 'Utopia Kitchen') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_715", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm not a fan of blue and I dig T-fal's stuff. Hit me up with the first non-blue T-fal pan you find.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND NOT color = \"blue\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"T-fal\" AND NOT color = \"blue\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'T-fal' AND color != 'blue' LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_262", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "My apartment features a compact kitchen with minimal storage. Is this pan low-maintenance and suitable for small spaces?", "long_answer": "The pan in question is not suitable for the dishwasher, requiring slightly more attention than simply placing it among your other dishes. It necessitates an area for hand-washing, along with space to dry it right after cleaning. Should your kitchen space be at a premium and unable to afford the additional space needed for this upkeep, you may wish to opt for a pan that demands less in terms of maintenance and storage post-use.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute \"Dishwasher Safe: no\" are not recommended for use by consumers who may not be willing or able to invest the time and effort into the careful maintenance these pans require, which includes correct hand-washing techniques and immediate drying to prevent damage.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "no", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_927", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Is it suitable to use high heat when cooking with this pan?", "long_answer": "Utilizing high heat with this pan is not advised. To avoid burning food and to preserve the pan's non-stick coating, it is better to use low to medium heat.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_263", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I need a pan that's suitable for both the stovetop and oven use. Can you recommend a type for that purpose?", "long_answer": "Certainly, a cast iron skillet is an ideal selection for recipes beginning on the stovetop and transitioning to the oven, thanks to its high-temperature endurance and superior heat retention capabilities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the attribute of being made from cast iron typically mean that they are a preferred choice for recipes that benefit from steady heat and long cooking times, such as stews and braises, due to their excellent heat retention.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "cast iron", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_928", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is the nonstick coating on this product certified to be free from PFOA, Lead, and Cadmium?", "long_answer": "According to the product metadata, the nonstick coating on this product is confirmed to be free of harmful substances such as PFOA, Lead, and Cadmium, which assures that it is safe for cooking purposes.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_929", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is using a metal spatula safe for the nonstick surface of a pan?", "long_answer": "Using a metal spatula on the nonstick surface of a pan is not recommended as it can damage the surface and reduce the pan's longevity.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_930", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "How can I fix a Matfer Bourgeat Black Steel Frying Pan that starts sticking?", "long_answer": "If the Matfer Bourgeat Black Steel Frying Pan begins to exhibit sticking issues, re-seasoning the pan is recommended. You should clean the pan to remove any cooking residue, apply a thin layer of oil, and heat the pan until smoke appears. This process may need to be repeated following the initial seasoning instructions to restore the pan's non-stick properties.", "short_answer": "Re-season the pan.", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_931", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Are metal utensils likely to cause scratches on the non-stick coating of this pan?", "long_answer": "Sharp-edged metal utensils, including knives, have the potential to scratch and damage the non-stick coating of the pan. To preserve the pan's surface and ensure its longevity, it is recommended to use tools made from silicone, plastic, or wood instead of metal.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_932", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is there currently a promotion that offers a discount on this pan?", "long_answer": "A promotion is in place offering a 5% discount on this pan, but it is available exclusively when purchasing from the designated retailer and may be subject to additional terms or conditions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_933", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "Does the pan provide even heat distribution across its cooking surface?", "long_answer": "The pan is constructed with a 3-ply design that includes a thick aluminum core, which is responsible for conducting heat quickly and distributing it evenly across the cooking surface, ensuring an even cooking experience.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_264", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Will this pan assist in optimizing oven space while preparing sizeable meals?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the square design of these pans optimizes oven space utilization, fitting precisely with the oven's dimensions and enabling more efficient cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with square shapes feature a geometry that lends itself to more efficient use of oven space and storage, thanks to their ability to align with the straight edges of shelves and cabinets.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "square", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_934", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is the cast iron skillet suitable for outdoor cooking activities such as grilling or campfire cooking?", "long_answer": "Cast iron skillets are well-suited for outdoor cooking owing to their excellent heat retention properties and robustness, which allow them to perform optimally when exposed to the high temperatures often encountered with grills or campfires. However, they should be adequately seasoned to ensure their durability and non-stick performance in these cooking conditions.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_265", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Should I follow any specific precautions while cleaning this pan to preserve its surface integrity?", "long_answer": "To preserve the integrity of this pan's surface, refrain from using abrasive cleaners or scouring pads that can scratch the anodized aluminum. It is recommended to clean gently with a soft sponge or cloth to maintain the pan's non-reactive and non-stick qualities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with anodized aluminum are not suitable for use with metal utensils that can scratch the hardened surface, potentially compromising its non-reactive properties.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "search_qa_716", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I'm on the hunt for a decent sized pan, probably something over 8 inches. Also, I'd prefer something in either green or silver. Oh, and it should be able to withstand high oven temperatures. What's the best you got in this category?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"silver\") AND size > 8 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"silver\") AND size > 8 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"silver\") AND size > 8 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size > 8 AND (color = 'green' OR color = 'silver') AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ORDER BY price DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_935", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Does the pan come with a recipe for making Madeleines?", "long_answer": "The pan is accompanied by a recipe specifically for Madeleines, which has proven to be beneficial for individuals attempting to bake them for the first time, yielding positive results.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_936", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is the nonstick ceramic coating on this pan durable and suitable for long-term use?", "long_answer": "The nonstick ceramic coating on the pan has been designed with durability in mind. For optimal long-term performance, it is advisable that users steer clear of metal utensils and abrasive cleaning products, and treat the pan with care in order to properly preserve its nonstick qualities.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_937", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Where is the Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan manufactured?", "long_answer": "The Tramontina Professional Restaurant Fry Pan is manufactured in the USA, using components that are imported from other countries.", "short_answer": "USA", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_717", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "I'm only looking for pans made by Matfer Bourgeat or Chicago Metallic. Show me the one that can stand the hottest oven.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray` with asin: B00076QWUY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"Chicago Metallic\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"Chicago Metallic\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Matfer Bourgeat\", \"Chicago Metallic\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Matfer Bourgeat', 'Chicago Metallic') \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_718", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm looking for a sizable pan, at least 10 inches. Give me the first result from either Bialetti or Chicago Metallic, would you?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Chicago Metallic\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Chicago Metallic\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Bialetti', 'Chicago Metallic') AND size >= 10 ORDER BY product_id LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_938", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Does the T-fal E93897 Fry Pan exhibit even heat distribution compared to other nonstick pans?", "long_answer": "The T-fal E93897 Fry Pan is recognized for its even and consistent heat distribution according to users, distinguishing it as having a superior performance for cooking meals uniformly when compared to other nonstick pans.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_719", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "I don't want any blue pans and I'm only willing to shell out less than ten dollars. Find me the least expensive non-blue pan you have in stock.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" AND price < 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"blue\" AND price < 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'blue' AND price < 10 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_939", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the lid of the Cuisinart 719-16 Saucepan transparent?", "long_answer": "The lid of the Cuisinart 719-16 Saucepan is not designed to be transparent, making it impossible to view the contents within the saucepan without physically lifting the lid to take a look.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_940", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Does the saucepan's handle remain cool to the touch when used on the stovetop?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is equipped with a Cool Grip Handle, crafted from solid stainless steel, which is specifically designed to stay cool even when the saucepan is used on the stovetop.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_941", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "Is this pan designed for both stovetop and oven use?", "long_answer": "This pan is specifically designed to be versatile, allowing it to be used on the stovetop and then transferred to the oven for baking, which is perfect for dishes that require both searing and baking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_942", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does the non-stick coating on this product emit odors during its initial use?", "long_answer": "There have been instances where customers noticed a strong odor during the initial use of the product with a non-stick coating. It is advisable to take precautions, particularly for individuals with sensitivities or those who own pet birds, since non-stick coatings can release harmful fumes if overheated.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_943", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is the Green Earth Frying Pan Set made of heavyweight or lightweight material?", "long_answer": "The Green Earth Frying Pan Set is constructed from durable heavy-gauge die-cast aluminum, ensuring that the pans are robust but not excessively heavy, striking a balance between sturdiness and manageable weight.", "short_answer": "heavyweight", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_944", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Is it advisable to use aerosol cooking sprays like PAM on this nonstick pan?", "long_answer": "Using aerosol cooking sprays such as PAM on this nonstick pan is discouraged because these sprays can leave behind a residue that is challenging to clean off, which could potentially compromise the pan's nonstick qualities over time.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_945", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the pot considered heavy or lightweight by users?", "long_answer": "Users report differing opinions regarding the weight of the pot, yet it is commonly characterized as lightweight, yet possessing a substantial and durable feel suitable for regular use.", "short_answer": "lightweight", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_266", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "Is this pan suitable for use over a campfire?", "long_answer": "No, this pan wouldn't be optimal for use over a campfire. Since it's constructed from ceramic, it isn't suited for the intense heat typical of open flames associated with campfire conditions.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pan with ceramic material fail to meet the requirements for high-heat applications such as cooking on an open flame where durable, uncoated metal pans might be necessary.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "ceramic", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_720", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I only trust Norpro and Lodge when it comes to pans. Tell me which of their products can endure the highest oven heat.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking.` with asin: B00006JSUE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"Lodge\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"Lodge\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Norpro\", \"Lodge\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Norpro', 'Lodge') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_721", "asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "question": "I'm hunting for a large T-fal pan, something 8 inches or bigger. What's the cheapest option you can offer me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND brand = \"T-fal\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND brand = \"T-fal\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 8 AND brand = \"T-fal\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'T-fal' AND size >= 8 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_946", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is the pan with a heat-resistant handle oven-safe?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed with a heat-resistant handle, allowing for some degree of oven use. However, the user must refer to the product guidelines to determine specific temperature limits for safe usage and to preserve the pan's condition.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_267", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Will this pan withstand frequent washing in the dishwasher if I regularly clean my kitchenware that way?", "long_answer": "Certainly. This pan is designed specifically for such regular usage. Built to withstand high temperatures and the chemical detergents commonly found in dishwashers, it's resistant to warping, rusting, or quick deterioration, ensuring durability even when washed daily in the machine.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute feature resistance to both the high temperatures and strong chemicals typical in dishwashers, which ensures they do not warp, rust, or degrade quickly when exposed to such conditions regularly.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_947", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Do the pans prevent eggs from sticking during cooking?", "long_answer": "These pans are designed in a way that ensures eggs do not stick, which is supported by numerous user experiences indicating their effectiveness in cooking omelets and scrambled eggs without issues of sticking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_722", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm not fussed about fancy colors. As long as it's either silver or copper and doesn't break my bank of 20 dollars, I'm good. Now show me the pan that can handle the highest oven temperature.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart` with asin: B00008CM69", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"copper\") AND price <= 20 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"copper\") AND price <= 20 AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"silver\", \"copper\") AND price <= 20 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('silver', 'copper') \nAND price <= 20 \nORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_723", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I've got a thing for Bialetti and Tramontina gear, especially if it's blue or copper. Show me the cheapest pan you got from these brands that match my preferences.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Tramontina\") AND color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Tramontina\") AND color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Bialetti\", \"Tramontina\") AND color IN (\"blue\", \"copper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Bialetti', 'Tramontina') AND color IN ('blue', 'copper') ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_268", "asin": "B004YV61AE", "question": "Is this pan safe for searing meats at high temperatures?", "long_answer": "No, this pan is unsuitable for cooking techniques that require extremely high temperatures, like searing meats, as the sensitive non-stick layer might get damaged. Opt for non-coated cookware such as cast iron or stainless steel when dealing with high heat.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with delicate non-stick coatings cannot be used for cooking methods that involve metal utensils or very high heat, to avoid damaging the surface.", "feature_name": "Pan Type", "feature_value": "frying pan / skillet", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_948", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is the pan susceptible to rust if left wet after washing?", "long_answer": "The pan, similar to cast iron cookware, is susceptible to rusting if it isn't dried thoroughly and given a light re-seasoning after washing. It is crucial to maintain proper drying to preserve its quality.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_949", "asin": "B0012BR1XU", "question": "Are there any customer reviews indicating that food cooks unevenly in this pan due to its slanted sides?", "long_answer": "According to customer reviews, there is no prevalent issue regarding uneven cooking associated with this pan's slanted sides, although its design might slightly reduce the usable cooking space.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_269", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Will the taste of my meal stay the same, even if it's cooked for a long time in this pan?", "long_answer": "For foods that are neither acidic nor alkaline, the taste should stay uniform. Yet, with acidic or alkaline items, there's a chance the taste may change owing to the possibility of the pan material reacting, especially if it is aluminum and hasn't been suitably treated or anodized.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with reactivity to acidic and alkaline foods feature a potential for metallic taste transfer and discoloration, rendering them less suitable for long-term cooking of tomato sauces or citrus-based dishes unless they're treated or anodized.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_724", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm fed up with every pan being silver. Get me a pan that isn't silver from either Presto or ZWILLING J.A. Henckels.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "The product that fits your requirements is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" AND brand IN (\"Presto\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"silver\" AND brand IN (\"Presto\", \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Presto', 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels') AND color != 'silver';"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_270", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "Is it safe to put this pan in the dishwasher without risking damage over time?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this pan is engineered to resist the elevated temperatures and strong detergents typical in dishwashers, thereby maintaining its form and quality through numerous washing cycles without succumbing to warping, rusting, or deterioration.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with the \"Dishwasher Safe: yes\" attribute feature resistance to both the high temperatures and strong chemicals typical in dishwashers, which ensures they do not warp, rust, or degrade quickly when exposed to such conditions regularly.", "feature_name": "Dishwasher Safe", "feature_value": "yes", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "search_qa_725", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm always frying up something! I need a pan that can handle heat over 500F, but don't show me any Norpro. What's the cheapest one you got?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND NOT brand = \"Norpro\" ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND NOT brand = \"Norpro\" AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND NOT brand = \"Norpro\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND brand != 'Norpro' ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_726", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "I need a pan that can withstand a high oven temperature. But I'm picky about colors, only grey or silver for me. What's the best option you have?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"silver\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"silver\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"grey\", \"silver\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('grey', 'silver') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_950", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Does the pan's non-stick coating effectively prevent food from sticking?", "long_answer": "The pan is engineered with a high-performance, PFOA-free nonstick coating, which is designed to prevent food from sticking when the pan is used and cared for correctly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_951", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Can the Matfer Bourgeat Black Steel Round Frying Pan be used on induction cooktops?", "long_answer": "The Matfer Bourgeat Black Steel Round Frying Pan is designed to be compatible with various types of hobs, and that includes its suitability for use on induction cooktops.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_727", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm planning a big family dinner and I need a pan that's at least 10 inches. Can you point me to the first one your system finds?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B002UNMZPS", "title": " USA Pan Bakeware Aluminized Steel Hearth Bread Pan"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_952", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Do customers report that the lid's vent hole on this cookware releases excessive steam?", "long_answer": "Some customers have indicated a preference for a non-vented lid as they have experienced issues with the vent hole allowing too much steam to escape during the cooking process, particularly when cooking rice or vegetables where retaining steam is desired.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_728", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I'm looking for a Copper Chef pan that can handle the heat, at least 400°F in the oven. Which one should I go for?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND brand = \"Copper Chef\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 400 AND brand = \"Copper Chef\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Copper Chef' AND oven_safe_temperature >= 400;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_729", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm not a fan of those copper colored pans and my budget is tight, around 20 dollars. Can you find me the largest non-copper pan you have that's affordable?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid` with asin: B0027MF964", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" AND price < 20 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" AND price < 20 AND size = (SELECT MAX(size) FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT color = \"copper\" AND price < 20 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color != 'copper' AND price <= 20 \nORDER BY size DESC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_730", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I'm not about to let my pans burn in my super high heat oven. Give me the most heat-tolerant pan from either Ozeri or All-Clad.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black` with asin: B0170TFNXM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND brand IN (\"Ozeri\", \"All-Clad\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 500 AND brand IN (\"Ozeri\", \"All-Clad\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Ozeri', 'All-Clad') ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_953", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Does the wok feature an easy way to adjust the cooking temperature?", "long_answer": "The wok is equipped with a temperature control dial, making it simple to adjust the heat settings. However, due to the rapid heating capability of the wok, it is essential for users to prepare all ingredients in advance and remain vigilant to prevent any chances of the food overheating.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_731", "asin": "B0068SEQJE", "question": "I'm needing a new pan, but it's gotta be bigger than your average size and I only dig copper and blue ones. What's the cheapest one you have that hits those marks?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND color IN (\"copper\", \"blue\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND color IN (\"copper\", \"blue\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND color IN (\"copper\", \"blue\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('copper', 'blue') AND size > (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_732", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "I'd love to switch it up in my kitchen and get a pan that's either green or copper. Can you find me the least expensive one you got in those colors?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"copper\") ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"copper\") AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"green\", \"copper\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('green', 'copper') \nORDER BY price ASC \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_954", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "Is the pot capable of being used safely in an oven?", "long_answer": "The pot is designed to be oven-safe and can withstand temperatures up to 350 degrees Fahrenheit. It is crucial to follow safety guidelines when moving the pot from the stove to the oven to avoid any accidents or injuries.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_733", "asin": "B0027MF964", "question": "I ain't using Bialetti no more but still gotta have a pan that can handle more than 600F in the oven. Tell me what you got in stock.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT brand = \"Bialetti\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 600 AND NOT brand = \"Bialetti\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand != 'Bialetti' AND oven_safe_temperature > 600;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_734", "asin": "B00134LXEY", "question": "I do a lot of high-heat cooking and need a pan that can withstand at least 450 degrees. What's the cheapest option you got for me?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan` with asin: B004YV61AE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 AND price = (SELECT MIN(price) FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature >= 450 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_271", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "Is it possible for me to recycle this cookware effortlessly when it's due for replacement?", "long_answer": "Certainly, you can readily recycle this cookware once it's due for replacement. Given that these pans are crafted from aluminum, they make an outstanding choice for recycling efforts and can be repurposed repeatedly with reduced energy usage.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with aluminum's environmental considerations are not recommended for those who prefer to minimize their environmental footprint through recyclable and sustainable cookware options, highlighting aluminum's advantage as it can be recycled effectively.", "feature_name": "Material", "feature_value": "aluminum", "type": "experience"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_955", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Is the pan dishwasher safe, or is hand-washing recommended?", "long_answer": "The pan is constructed to be dishwasher safe. However, hand-washing is recommended to avoid corrosion of the rivets and to preserve the pan's appearance over time.", "short_answer": "hand-washing recommended", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_735", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I like using larger pans and I'm fond of stuff from Chicago Metallic. Can you find me a product from them that's at least the average size?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}], "long_answer": "The product that would suit your preferences is:\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Chicago Metallic\" AND size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= (SELECT AVG(size) FROM all_pans) AND brand = 'Chicago Metallic';"}}
{"id": "search_qa_736", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm a fan of Copper Chef and Bialetti, and I prefer to use pans that can tolerate high oven temperatures. Can you find me a pan from either of these brands that can withstand over 400 degrees F in the oven?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill` with asin: B01FMIU0MM", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Bialetti\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Copper Chef\", \"Bialetti\") AND oven_safe_temperature > 400 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (brand = 'Copper Chef' OR brand = 'Bialetti') AND oven_safe_temperature > 400;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_956", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Does the pan have a flat cooking surface according to its design specifications?", "long_answer": "The pan is designed with a flat cooking surface as per the manufacturer's quality standards. In the event that a customer receives a pan with a raised center causing uneven distribution of oils, the manufacturer provides replacements to ensure that customers have the flat surface that is expected.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_957", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "Can the pans accommodate large food items such as big pancakes?", "long_answer": "The pans come with a wide flat base, making them suitable for cooking large food items, including big pancakes, as noted by several customers.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_958", "asin": "B000069RBK", "question": "Does the pan feature a nonstick coating on its bottom?", "long_answer": "The saucepan's bottom is intentionally left uncoated to facilitate rapid heat conduction and prevent the formation of hot spots, which contributes to an even cooking process.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_737", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "I'm only interested in the blue or black pans from ZWILLING J.A. Henckels. Hook me up with one of those, will ya?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"black\") AND brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"blue\", \"black\") AND brand = \"ZWILLING J.A. Henckels\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'ZWILLING J.A. Henckels' AND (color = 'blue' OR color = 'black');"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_959", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "Can the pan still work effectively on a burner with a smaller diameter than the pan itself?", "long_answer": "Although the pan is designed to be most effective when matched with a burner of equivalent size to ensure even heating, it can still function effectively even when used on a smaller diameter burner.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_272", "asin": "B0170TFNXM", "question": "I've recently acquired a new cooktop and am eager to ensure I purchase a pan that is compatible. Are there particular features I should look for?", "long_answer": "When looking for a new pan, opt for one with a round shape since it's more compatible with a range of cooktops, including the latest induction types. Just make sure that the pan is constructed from a magnetic material if you're using an induction cooktop, and it will function seamlessly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape feature a better compatibility with stovetops of all kinds, including induction cooktops, provided they are made of an appropriate magnetic material.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_960", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does the white ceramic interior of the Bialetti pan facilitate easy cleaning?", "long_answer": "The design of the Bialetti pan features a white ceramic non-stick interior that is appreciated by many customers for its ease of cleaning. The non-stick quality prevents food from clinging to the surface, while the white color helps in spotting any leftover food particles, making the cleaning process more efficient.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_961", "asin": "B00008CM69", "question": "Do the handles of this saucepan remain cool to the touch during cooking?", "long_answer": "The saucepan is equipped with a Cool Grip Handle, specifically designed to stay cool while on the stovetop, ensuring safe handling.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_738", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm looking for a green pan that's at least 10 inches. Can you recommend the one that can withstand the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND color = \"green\" ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND color = \"green\" AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 10 AND color = \"green\" );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color = 'green' AND size >= 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_739", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "I do a lot of high heat cooking and need a big pan that can handle it. Which is your biggest pan safe to use in the oven at over 500 degrees?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver` with asin: B00FUF5OIS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND size >= 10 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 AND size >= 10 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE oven_safe_temperature > 500 ORDER BY size DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_740", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm not paying more than 20 bucks for an Ozeri pan. Whip out the cheapest one you've got on the list.", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Ozeri\" AND price < 20 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = \"Ozeri\" AND price < 20 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand = 'Ozeri' AND price <= 20 ORDER BY price ASC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_962", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is there a warranty included with the purchase of an All-Clad D3 Fry Pan?", "long_answer": "The All-Clad D3 Fry Pan comes with a limited lifetime warranty, which showcases the company's dedication to delivering high-quality products and ensuring customer satisfaction.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_963", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "Does this 12-inch saute pan have a significant weight that some customers might find too heavy?", "long_answer": "The 12-inch saute pan is constructed to be sturdy, which imparts a certain weightiness to the product. While some customers interpret the heft as an indicator of quality, others may find the pan excessively heavy, implying that perceptions of the pan's weight vary according to individual preferences.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_964", "asin": "B0017UTSLY", "question": "Are metal utensils safe to use with this electric stainless steel wok without causing damage?", "long_answer": "Though the electric wok is constructed from stainless steel, it is advisable to use non-metal utensils to prevent scratching or otherwise compromising the integrity of the wok's surface.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_741", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "I only want a cooking pan from Tramontina or Copper Chef, and yeah, it's got to be under 30 dollars. Can you find it for me?", "short_answer": [], "long_answer": "Sorry, we do not have any products that meet your requirements", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Copper Chef\") AND price < 30 LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN (\"Tramontina\", \"Copper Chef\") AND price < 30 ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand IN ('Tramontina', 'Copper Chef') AND price < 30;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_742", "asin": "B004VJMT78", "question": "I'm after either a black or silver pan but only from Chicago Metallic or Presto. What's the first product you got that meets those specifications?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}], "long_answer": "The product that meets your requirements is as follows.\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"silver\") AND brand IN (\"Chicago Metallic\", \"Presto\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN (\"black\", \"silver\") AND brand IN (\"Chicago Metallic\", \"Presto\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE (brand = 'Chicago Metallic' OR brand = 'Presto')\nAND (color = 'black' OR color = 'silver')\nORDER BY product_id \nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "search_qa_743", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I'm looking for a big enough pan, something around or bigger than 12 inches. But only if it's in copper or green. Can you check which product that is?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}], "long_answer": "I've got an option for you.\n`Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)` with asin: B0068SEQJE", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND color IN (\"copper\", \"green\") LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND color IN (\"copper\", \"green\") ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE size >= 12 AND (color = 'copper' OR color = 'green');"}}
{"id": "search_qa_744", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "I'm looking for a pan that's either silver or blue and within my $10 budget. Can you recommend one that can withstand the highest oven temperature?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}], "long_answer": "The best option for you is:\n`Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan` with asin: B0056FTO2Y", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND color IN (\"silver\", \"blue\") ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND color IN (\"silver\", \"blue\") AND oven_safe_temperature = (SELECT MAX(oven_safe_temperature) FROM `all_pans` WHERE price <= 10 AND color IN (\"silver\", \"blue\") );", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE color IN ('silver', 'blue') AND price <= 10 ORDER BY oven_safe_temperature DESC LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_965", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Is this pan a suitable replacement for a cast iron skillet based on its weight and cooking performance?", "long_answer": "This pan has been favored by numerous reviewers as a substitute for a cast iron skillet, attributing its lighter weight and comparable cooking capabilities. To achieve optimal performance akin to that of cast iron, it requires seasoning.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_966", "asin": "B00BK89AYS", "question": "Is seasoning required for optimal non-stick performance when using this pan for the first time?", "long_answer": "Seasoning the pan prior to its initial use is advisable to achieve the best non-stick results. The typical process for seasoning involves coating the pan with a small amount of oil.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_745", "asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "question": "I'm not a fan of USA Pan brand and I'm not looking to splurge either. What's the most affordable non-USA Pan product you have that is not pricier than your average pan?", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "Here is an option for you:\n`Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch` with asin: B00134LXEY", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'USA Pan' AND price <= (SELECT AVG(price) FROM all_pans) ORDER BY price LIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_967", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is it safe to use a metal spatula with this skillet without damaging its seasoning?", "long_answer": "While using a metal spatula on this skillet is possible, care must be taken to avoid being too aggressive, as this could damage the skillet's seasoning. Preferably, using wooden or silicone spatulas is recommended to preserve the seasoning of the skillet.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_968", "asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "question": "Is a special brush required to clean this skillet?", "long_answer": "There is no requirement for a special cleaning brush for this skillet; however, some customers opt to use a stiff-bristled brush or a chainmail scrubber that is specifically made for cast iron surfaces. It is important to apply oil to the skillet after the cleaning process.", "short_answer": "no", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "search_qa_746", "asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "question": "I've had enough with USA Pan's stuff. Show me a different brand’s pan, any will do.", "short_answer": [{"asin": "B00BK89AYS", "title": "10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany"}, {"asin": "B00134LXEY", "title": "Chicago Metallic Professional 12-Cup Non-Stick Madeleine Pan, 15.75-Inch-by-7.75-Inch"}, {"asin": "B000S6I4ZE", "title": "Bialetti 6168 Italian Collection Fry Pan, 12-inch, Charcoal"}, {"asin": "B00006JSUE", "title": "Lodge 3 Quart Cast Iron Deep Skillet with Lid. Covered Cast Iron Skillet for Deep Frying and and Bread Baking."}, {"asin": "B00076QWUY", "title": "Matfer Bourgeat 062006 Black Steel Round Frying Pan, 12 5/8-Inch, Gray"}, {"asin": "B0170TFNXM", "title": "All-Clad 2100090557 00485005996 E785S264 HA1 Hard Anodized Nonstick Dishwaher Safe PFOA Free 8 10-Inch Fry Pan Cookware Set, 2-Piece, Black"}, {"asin": "B000069RBK", "title": "Anolon Advanced Hard-Anodized Nonstick 2-Quart Covered Saucepan, Gray"}, {"asin": "B00008CM69", "title": "Cuisinart 719-16 Chef's Classic Stainless Saucepan with Cover, 1 1/2 Quart"}, {"asin": "B0027MF964", "title": "T-Fal Specialty 3 Quart Handy Pot w/Glass Lid"}, {"asin": "B01FMIU0MM", "title": "Copper Chef 9.5 Inch Square Frying Pan With Lid -&nbsp;Skillet with Ceramic Non Stick Coating. Perfect Cookware&nbsp;For&nbsp;Saute And Grill"}, {"asin": "B0017UTSLY", "title": "Presto 5900 1500-Watt Stainless-Steel Electric Wok"}, {"asin": "B0068SEQJE", "title": "Green Earth Frying Pan 3-Piece Set by Ozeri (8&quot;, 10&quot;, 12&quot;), with Textured Ceramic Non-Stick Coating from Germany (100% PTFE, PFOA and APEO Free)"}, {"asin": "B00X4WQMAS", "title": "Utopia Kitchen Pre-Seasoned Cast Iron Skillet - 12.5 Inch"}, {"asin": "B0056FTO2Y", "title": "Spirit 8&quot; Thermolon Fry Pan"}, {"asin": "B009HBKQR0", "title": "Tramontina 80114/536DS Aluminum Nonstick, 12&quot;, NSF-Certified, Made in USA Professional Restaurant Fry Pan, inch"}, {"asin": "B004YV61AE", "title": "Cuisinart FCT23-24NS French Classic Tri-Ply Stainless 10-Inch Nonstick Crepe Pan"}, {"asin": "B004VJMT78", "title": "T-fal E93897 Professional Total Nonstick Thermo-Spot Heat Indicator Fry Pan with Glass Lid Cookware, 10-Inch, Black"}, {"asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "title": "All-Clad D3 Fry Pan with Lid, 10 Inch Pan, Dishwasher Safe Stainless Steel Cookware, Silver"}, {"asin": "B0012BR1XU", "title": "Norpro 273 Broil/Roast Pan Set, 12 inches"}], "long_answer": "I found a product that matches your criteria.\n`10&quot; Stone Earth Frying Pan by Ozeri, with 100% APEO &amp; PFOA-Free Stone-Derived Non-Stick Coating from Germany` with asin: B00BK89AYS", "type": "search_qa", "extra_data": {"sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" LIMIT 1;", "answer": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE NOT brand = \"USA Pan\" ;", "question2sql": "SELECT product_id FROM `all_pans` WHERE brand <> 'USA Pan'\nLIMIT 1;"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_969", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is a cast iron skillet suitable for use on an induction cooktop?", "long_answer": "A cast iron skillet is indeed suitable for use on an induction cooktop. This compatibility stems from the magnetic properties of cast iron, which allow it to work effectively with the induction technology.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_273", "asin": "B00006JSUE", "question": "Is this pan compatible with both an induction cooktop and a campfire for when I'm camping?", "long_answer": "Indeed, this pan is compatible with both an induction cooktop and an open flame such as a campfire. Its cast iron lid contributes to its adaptability to different heat sources, providing exceptional cooking versatility regardless of your location.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a cast iron lid are ideally used for cooking on various types of heat sources, including induction and open flame, providing versatility across different cooking environments.", "feature_name": "Lid Type", "feature_value": "cast iron lid", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_970", "asin": "B002UNMZPS", "question": "Does the AMERICOAT Plus coating on the bread pan allow for easy release of bread?", "long_answer": "The AMERICOAT Plus coating, which is silicone-based, is designed to ensure that bread can be released effortlessly from the pan when instructions for use are followed properly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "reasoning_qa_274", "asin": "B009HBKQR0", "question": "I enjoy preparing omelets; would this pan be appropriate for that?", "long_answer": "Certainly, the pan's round design promotes uniform heat distribution across its surface, which is perfect for preparing sensitive dishes such as omelets, guaranteeing they are cooked evenly and softly.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "reasoning_qa", "extra_data": {"knowledge": "pans with a round shape typically mean that they provide an even heat distribution which plays a crucial role in cooking processes like frying and sautéing, ensuring that food cooks uniformly without any hot spots.", "feature_name": "Shape", "feature_value": "round", "type": "functionality"}}
{"id": "fact_qa_971", "asin": "B00076QWUY", "question": "Does a well-seasoned black steel pan provide a better non-stick surface compared to Teflon non-stick pans?", "long_answer": "A well-seasoned black steel pan is often reported by users to offer a reliable non-stick surface, which may be considered superior due to the absence of associated health risks that some non-stick coatings carry.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
{"id": "fact_qa_972", "asin": "B00FUF5OIS", "question": "Is the All-Clad fry pan's interior designed to be non-stick?", "long_answer": "The interior of the All-Clad fry pan has a starburst finish designed to reduce food sticking; however, its effectiveness may not match that of Teflon coatings. Users suggest that to optimize non-stick performance, it is important to use suitable heat settings and to properly preheat the pan with oil before cooking.", "short_answer": "yes", "type": "fact_qa", "extra_data": null}
